<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB &amp; REX Postprocess -- version V3.1.1.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
  <channel id="OSN Series First HD">
    <display-name lang="en">OSN Series First HD</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/OFH.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="OSN Series HD">
    <display-name lang="en">OSN Series HD</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/obg.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="OSN Comedy HD">
    <display-name lang="en">OSN Comedy HD</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/OCO.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Comedy Central">
    <display-name lang="en">Comedy Central</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/CCE.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Star World HD">
    <display-name lang="en">Star World HD</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/STW.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="OSN Mezze">
    <display-name lang="en">OSN Mezze</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/OMZ.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="TLC HD">
    <display-name lang="en">TLC HD</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/TLC.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="E! Entertainment HD">
    <display-name lang="en">E! Entertainment HD</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/ETV.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="OSN Living HD">
    <display-name lang="en">OSN Living HD</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/OLH.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20200919020500" stop="20200919030000" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">Mayans M.C.</title>
    <title lang="ar">مايانز أم.سي.</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dramatic revelations carve out different paths to vengeance. تكشف النقاشات المثيرة عن مسارات مختلفة للانتقام.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919030000" stop="20200919034500" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">The View</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا فيو</title>
    <desc lang="en">Emmy award winner for "Outstanding Talk Show" this chat-fest features a team of dynamic women of different ages, experiences and backgrounds discussing the most topical events of the day. يتضمن هذا البرنامج الحواري الفائز بجائزة إيمي مجموعة من النساء من أعمار وتجارب وخلفيات مختلفة حيث يتناقشن في أهم الأحداث التي تحصل.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919034500" stop="20200919043000" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">Magnum P.I.</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماغنوم بي. آي.</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Junior is kidnapped as leverage to retrieve the stolen list of undercover CIA agents, and most of Five-0 is rounded up by the CIA to prevent them from interfering, Tani and Quinn ask Magnum and Higgins for their help. عندما يتم اختطاف جونيور كأداة ضغط لاسترداد القائمة المسروقة من عملاء وكالة المخابرات المركزية السريين ، ويتم جمع معظم أفراد الـ فايف-0 من قبل وكالة المخابرات المركزية لمنعهم من التدخل، وتطلب تاني وكوين من ماغنوم وهيجنز مساعدتهما.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919043000" stop="20200919051500" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">Marvel's Agents Of S.H.I.E.L.D.</title>
    <title lang="ar">مارفيلز إيجينتس أوف ش. ي. ل. د.</title>
    <desc lang="en">With the identity of the timeline-unravelling "thread" revealed, the team's mission to protect him at all costs leads each agent to question their own values. Is preserving the future of the world as they know it worth the destruction they could prevent? مع الكشف عن هوية واضع الجدول الزمني، فإن مهمة الفريق لحمايته بأي ثمن، تدفع كل وكيل إلى التشكيك في قيمته الخاصة. هل الحفاظ على مستقبل العالم كما يعلمونه يستحق الدمار الذي يمكنهم منعه؟.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919051500" stop="20200919060000" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">Pearson</title>
    <title lang="ar">بيرسون</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jessica is split between her personal and professional life. Keri comes to a decision about her future. جيسيكا منقسمة بين حياتها الشخصية والمهنية. تتخذ كيري قرارا بشأن مستقبلها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919060000" stop="20200919070000" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">The View</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا فيو</title>
    <desc lang="en">Emmy award winner for "Outstanding Talk Show" this chat-fest features a team of dynamic women of different ages, experiences and backgrounds discussing the most topical events of the day. يتضمن هذا البرنامج الحواري الفائز بجائزة إيمي مجموعة من النساء من أعمار وتجارب وخلفيات مختلفة حيث يتناقشن في أهم الأحداث التي تحصل.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919070000" stop="20200919075000" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">Marvel's Agents Of S.H.I.E.L.D.</title>
    <title lang="ar">مارفيلز إيجينتس أوف ش. ي. ل. د.</title>
    <desc lang="en">With the identity of the timeline-unravelling "thread" revealed, the team's mission to protect him at all costs leads each agent to question their own values. Is preserving the future of the world as they know it worth the destruction they could prevent? مع الكشف عن هوية واضع الجدول الزمني، فإن مهمة الفريق لحمايته بأي ثمن، تدفع كل وكيل إلى التشكيك في قيمته الخاصة. هل الحفاظ على مستقبل العالم كما يعلمونه يستحق الدمار الذي يمكنهم منعه؟.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919075000" stop="20200919084000" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">Council Of Dads</title>
    <title lang="ar">كاونسيل اوف دادز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Anthony contemplates a job offer that would mean a move to Las Vegas. Evan finds his loyalties tested between Luly and his strong-willed mother. Oliver confronts Anthony about a deeply held personal secret that will rock the Perry family. يفكر أنتوني في عرض عمل قد يعني الانتقال إلى لاس فيغاس. يجد إيفان أن ولاءاته تختبر بين لولي وأمه القوية الإرادة. يواجه أوليفر، أنتوني بشأن سر شخصي راسخ سيهز عائلة بيري.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919084000" stop="20200919093000" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">Magnum P.I.</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماغنوم بي. آي.</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Junior is kidnapped as leverage to retrieve the stolen list of undercover CIA agents, and most of Five-0 is rounded up by the CIA to prevent them from interfering, Tani and Quinn ask Magnum and Higgins for their help. عندما يتم اختطاف جونيور كأداة ضغط لاسترداد القائمة المسروقة من عملاء وكالة المخابرات المركزية السريين ، ويتم جمع معظم أفراد الـ فايف-0 من قبل وكالة المخابرات المركزية لمنعهم من التدخل، وتطلب تاني وكوين من ماغنوم وهيجنز مساعدتهما.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919093000" stop="20200919101500" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">Magnum P.I.</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماغنوم بي. آي.</title>
    <desc lang="en">Magnum and TC go undercover as efficiency experts when a corporate manager is murdered and everyone in the office is a suspect. Also, Rick is curious why Higgins faked an injury to prevent her from investigating the case with Thomas. يعمل ماجنوم و تي سي كخبراء في الكفاءة عندما يتم قتل مدير شركة وكل شخص في المكتب مشتبه فيه. كما أن لدى ريك فضول لمعرفة سبب قيام هيجينز بتزييف إصابتها لمنعها من التحقيق في القضية مع توماس.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919101500" stop="20200919110000" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">Marvel's Agents Of S.H.I.E.L.D.</title>
    <title lang="ar">مارفيلز إيجينتس أوف ش. ي. ل. د.</title>
    <desc lang="en">A surprise leap forward in time strands Enoch in 1931 and lands the team in another unfamiliar decade. Now, in order to stop the Chronicoms from launching their future-dismantling plan, the agents must infiltrate one of S.H.I.E.L.D.'s most secure bases. قفزة زمنية مفاجئة إلى الأمام تجعل انوك يعلق في عام 1931 وتهبط الفريق في عقد آخر غير مألوف. الآن ، من أجل منع الـ كرونيكومز من إطلاق خطة التفكيك المستقبلية ، يجب على العملاء التسلل إلى إحدى القواعد الأكثر أمانًا لـ شيلد.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919110000" stop="20200919120000" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">His Dark Materials</title>
    <title lang="ar">هيز دارك ماتيرليز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Separated from her friends, Lyra must use all of her methods of deception to thwart a formidable foe. Meanwhile, Mrs Coulter plots her next move. بعد أن فصلت عن أصدقائها، يتعين على ليرا استخدام كل أساليب الخداع لإحباط عدو كبير. في هذه الأثناء تخطط السيدة كولتر لخطوتها التالية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919120000" stop="20200919130000" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">The View</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا فيو</title>
    <desc lang="en">Emmy award winner for "Outstanding Talk Show" this chat-fest features a team of dynamic women of different ages, experiences and backgrounds discussing the most topical events of the day. يتضمن هذا البرنامج الحواري الفائز بجائزة إيمي مجموعة من النساء من أعمار وتجارب وخلفيات مختلفة حيث يتناقشن في أهم الأحداث التي تحصل.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919130000" stop="20200919135000" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">Council Of Dads</title>
    <title lang="ar">كاونسيل اوف دادز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Anthony contemplates a job offer that would mean a move to Las Vegas. Evan finds his loyalties tested between Luly and his strong-willed mother. Oliver confronts Anthony about a deeply held personal secret that will rock the Perry family. يفكر أنتوني في عرض عمل قد يعني الانتقال إلى لاس فيغاس. يجد إيفان أن ولاءاته تختبر بين لولي وأمه القوية الإرادة. يواجه أوليفر، أنتوني بشأن سر شخصي راسخ سيهز عائلة بيري.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919135000" stop="20200919144000" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Med</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو ميد</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dr. Charles and Goodwin fear Dr. Halstead is repeating past mistakes when a patient with early-onset Alzheimer's is brought into the E.D. Maggie and Ben become concerned when one of Ben's students is admitted. Dr. Manning and Dr. Marcel treat a terminally ill patient. يخشى الدكتور تشارلز والدكتور جودوين من تكرار الدكتور هالستيد لأخطاءه السابقة عندما يتم إحضار مريض مصاب بداء الزهايمر المبكر إلى قسم المخ ويشعر ماجي وبن بالقلق عندما يتم قبول أحد طلاب بن و يقوم الدكتور مانينغ والدكتور مارسيل بمعالجة مريضاً مصاباً بمرض عضال.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919144000" stop="20200919153000" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو بي.دي.</title>
    <desc lang="en">Intelligence does everything they can to build a case against the elusive leader of a drug ring, but things get complicated when Rojas realises someone she cares about might be involved. تبذل المخابرات كل ما في وسعها للقضاء على زعيم عصابة مخدرات يصعب الوصول اليه و لكن تتعقد الأمور عندما تدرك روجاس أن شخصا يعنيها متورط بالقضية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919153000" stop="20200919163000" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">His Dark Materials</title>
    <title lang="ar">هيز دارك ماتيرليز</title>
    <desc lang="en">As the Magisterium closes in, Lyra learns more about Asriel's rebellion; but her assistance to him comes at great personal cost…. مع إغلاق ماغسترام ، يكتشف ليرا المزيد عن تمرد اسريل؛ ولكن مساعدتها له تأتي بتكلفة شخصية كبيرة ...</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919163000" stop="20200919174000" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">Mayans M.C.</title>
    <title lang="ar">مايانز أم.سي.</title>
    <desc lang="en">The need for justice ignites tough decisions for the Reyes brothers and the MC. تشعل الحاجة إلى تحقيق العدالة قرارات صعبة بالنسبة إلى الإخوة رييس والـ أم سي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919174000" stop="20200919183000" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">Motherland: Fort Salem</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماذرلاند فورت سالم</title>
    <desc lang="en">The unit travels to Salem Town for an annual witch celebration, but an unexpected disturbance throws the proceedings into chaos. Tally wonders if she made the right choice to embark on a military career when witch-hate and her own mother stand in her way. تسافر الوحدة إلى سالم تاون من أجل احتفال سنوي بالساحرة ، لكن اضطرابًا غير متوقع يؤدي إلى فوضى في الإجراءات. تتساءل تالي عما إذا كانت قد اتخذت الخيار الصحيح للشروع في مهنة عسكرية عندما تقف الساحرة ووالدتها في طريقها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919183000" stop="20200919191500" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <title lang="ar">لوو أند أوردر: سبيشال فيكتمز يونيت</title>
    <desc lang="en">The SVU struggles to find a serial predator who uses a date rape drug that leaves no evidence behind. Rollins receives some good news. تحاول شعبة مكافحة الجريمة  العثور على مجرم مغتصب يقوم باستخدام عقار  لا يترك أي اثر ويتلقى رولينز بعض الأخبار الجيدة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919191500" stop="20200919200000" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lt. Severide teams up with Seager and the OFI when a motel structure fire turns suspicious. Firehouse 51 members become amateur sleuths following a Reddit post involving one of their own. Brett continues to get invested in her birth mother, Julie. يتعاون الملازم سيفرايد مع سيجر ومكتب تحقيقات الحرائق للتحقيق في حريق فندق مريب و يقوم أعضاء مركز الإطفاء 51 بالتجسس على رديت بعد نشره لخبر يخص أحدهم و تتولى بريت رعاية أمها جولي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919200000" stop="20200919205000" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">Preacher</title>
    <title lang="ar">بريتشر</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cassidy and Tulip hide Humperdoo from The Grail, whose operatives are now searching both for their Messiah - and Starr. Meanwhile, a tempted Jesse considers a powerful offer…. يقوم كل من كاسيدي وتوليب بإخفاء هامبردو عن ذا غرايل، الذي يبحث عملاؤه الآن عن كل من ماسيا - و ستار. في هذه الأثناء، يفكر جيسي في قبول عرض مغر جداً.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919205000" stop="20200919215500" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">Get Shorty</title>
    <title lang="ar">غيت شورتي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Miles is questioned by detectives. Rick connects with a long-lost friend and finds comfort at a very 'loving' commune. Yago and Ed search out Amara's hidden stash. يتم استجواب مايلز من قبل المحققين. يتصل ريك بصديق ضائع منذ فترة طويلة ويجد راحة في مجتمع "محب" للغاية. ياجو وإد يبحثان عن مخبأ أمارا الخفي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919215500" stop="20200919225000" channel="OSN Series First HD">
    <title lang="en">Euphoria</title>
    <title lang="ar">يوفوريا</title>
    <desc lang="en">Seventeen-year-old Rue returns home from rehab with no plans to stay clean. She meets Jules at a party at McKay's house. Nate gets in McKay's head when McKay takes an interest in Cassie. Nate and Maddy, who have broken up once again, attempt to make each other jealous. تعود روو البالغة من العمر سبعة عشر عامًا إلى المنزل بعد إعادة التأهيل دون أي خطط للبقاء بعيدة عن المخدرات. تلتقي جول في حفل في منزل مكاي. يدخل نيت في رأس مكاي عندما يهتم مكاي بكاسي. بعد انفصال نيت ومادي، يحاول الإثنان أن يغضبا بعضهما البعض.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919020000" stop="20200919024500" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">The doctors treat a 25-year-old runner suffering from severe swelling, but when things take a turn for the worse, Shaun enlists the help of Carly. Meanwhile, Park, Browne and Melendez treat two 16-year-old cancer patients who are dating. يعالج الأطباء عداءًا يبلغ من العمر 25 عامًا يعاني من تورم شديد ، ولكن عندما تتحول الأمور إلى الأسوأ ، يطلب شون مساعدة كارلي. وفي الوقت نفسه ، يعالج بارك وبراون وميليندز إثنان من مرضى السرطان يبلغان من العمر 16 عامًا.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919024500" stop="20200919033000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">A terminal cancer patient is determined to live the last few months of his life without inhibition. Dr. Reznik must confront her relationship with her mother when she comes in for a third opinion from Dr. Glassman. ينوي مريض سرطان على عيش الأشهر القليلة الأخيرة من حياته دون تثبيط. يجب على الدكتورة رزنيك مواجهة علاقتها مع والدتها عندما تأتي كثالث خيار من دكتور غلاسمان.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919033000" stop="20200919041500" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">While working with Melendez and Claire, Shaun proposes a radical and risky new surgery to treat a young bride with a devastating cancer diagnosis. Morgan and Park compete over who gets to take the lead on an elderly patient's tumour removal surgery. أثناء العمل مع ميلينديز وكلير ، يقترح شون إجراء عملية جراحية جديدة محفوفة بالمخاطر لعلاج عروس شابة بعد تشخيص إصابتها بالسرطان. يتنافس مورغان وبارك على من سيحصل على مركز الصدارة في جراحة إزالة ورم لمريض مسن.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919041500" stop="20200919050000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">As Dr. Andrews vows to help a good Samaritan who was injured while stopping a sexual assault, Dr. Lim faces a difficult decision when a young patient's parents suspect that Dr. Melendez made a mistake. Meanwhile, Dr. Murphy fields advice following his disastrous date. بينما يتعهد الدكتور أندروز بمساعدة السامري الصالح الذي أُصيب أثناء إيقاف الاعتداء الجنسي ، يواجه الدكتور ليم قرارًا صعبًا عندما يشتبه آباء أحد المرضى في أن الدكتور ميلينديز ارتكب خطأ. وفي الوقت نفسه ، يطلب الدكتور مورفي النصائح بعد موعده الكارثي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919050000" stop="20200919062000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Good Morning America</title>
    <title lang="ar">غود مورنينغ أميريكا</title>
    <desc lang="en">Broadcasting from the ABC studios in New York, this Emmy award-winning news show brings viewers daily, up-to-the-minute breaking news and weather, as well as topical feature stories. يقدم البرنامج في بث يومي مباشر من استوديوهات إي بي سي في نيويورك. يجلب هذا البرنامج الإخباري الفائز بجائزة إيمي الأخبار العاجلة يومياً وأخبار حالة الطقس، فضلاً عن الكثير من القصص المختلفة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919062000" stop="20200919070500" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dr. Claire Brown faces complications at home and work as she prepares to lead her first surgery. Meanwhile, a sports fishing accident challenges the rest of the staff as they look to treat the fisherman's injuries without damaging his prize catch. تواجه الدكتورة كلير براون مضاعفات في المنزل وتعمل أثناء استعدادها لقيادة أول عملية جراحية لها. وفي الوقت نفسه ، يتحدى حادث صيد رياضي بقية الموظفين وهم يتطلعون إلى علاج إصابات الصياد دون الإضرار بصيده.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919070500" stop="20200919075000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">As a conspiracy theorist questions Dr. Melendez's of his liver damage, Dr. Brown treats a woman whose inability to feel pain is threatening both her marriage and her life. Meanwhile, Dr. Murphy and Dr. Glassman each face crises in their romantic relationships. بينما هناك من يشكك بإصابة الدكتور ميلينديز بتلف الكبد ، يعالج الدكتور براون امرأة يشكل عجزها عن الشعور بالألم تهديداً لزواجها وحياتها. في هذه الأثناء ، يواجه كل من الدكتور مورفي والدكتور غلاسمان أزمات في علاقاتهما الرومانسية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919075000" stop="20200919083500" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dr. Murphy has been assigned his first surgery by Dr. Lim, but Dr. Andrews questions whether he is really ready. As Dr. Brown continues to avoid her complicated emotions about her mother, she and Dr. Reznick have a patient whose diagnosis has them doubting his story. قام الدكتور ليم بتعيين الدكتور مورفي في أول عملية جراحية له ، لكن الدكتور أندروز يتساءل عما إذا كان مستعدًا حقًا. وبينما تستمر الدكتورة براون في تجنب مشاعرها المعقدة تجاه والدتها ، فإنها والدكتور ريزنيك لديهما مريض يشكك التشخيص الذي أجري له في قصته.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919083500" stop="20200919092000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">While performing his first solo surgery, Dr. Murphy alienates a nurse, which puts his residency in jeopardy. Dr. Melendez disagrees with Dr. Lim on a risky surgery. Dr. Brown spirals into self-destructive behaviours, causing negative ramifications in the workplace. أثناء إجراء أول عملية جراحية منفردة ، ينفي الدكتور مورفي ممرضة ، مما يعرض إقامته للخطر. الدكتور ميلينديز يختلف مع الدكتور ليم في عملية جراحية محفوفة بالمخاطر. يلجأ الدكتور براون إلى سلوكيات التدمير الذاتي ، مما تسبب في تداعيات سلبية في مكان العمل.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919092000" stop="20200919100500" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dr. Murphy's unique ability to relate to a patient isolated by an immune deficiency yields an unexpected result. Dr. Browne, Dr. Reznick and Dr. Andrews treat a 12-year-old patient who is about to become blind, and tension builds between Dr. Melendez and Dr. Lim. قدرة الدكتور مورفي الفريدة على التواصل مع مريض معزول بسبب نقص المناعة تعطي نتيجة غير متوقعة. الدكتور براون والدكتور ريزنيك والدكتور أندروز يعالجون مريضًا يبلغ من العمر 12 عامًا على وشك أن يصبح أعمى ، ويتفاقم التوتر بين الدكتور ميلينديز والدكتور ليم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919100500" stop="20200919105000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">Carly's attempts at increasing her intimacy with Shaun are becoming more of a frustration than either of them expected. Meanwhile, Lim and Melendez struggle in their relationship as they work to separate their work from their personal life. أصبحت محاولات كارلي لتوطيد علاقتها الحميمة بشون أكثر إحباطًا مما توقعه أي منهما. في هذه الأثناء ، يناضل "ليم" و "ميلينديز" في علاقتهما وهما يعملان على فصل عملهما عن حياتهما الشخصية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919105000" stop="20200919113500" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">Shaun is ready for the next step in his relationship with Carly; however, he continues to struggle as they grow closer and more intimate. Meanwhile, a young patient must decide on a treatment that could save her life or possibly destroy her marriage. شون مستعد للخطوة التالية في علاقته مع كارلي ؛ ومع ذلك ، يواصل النضال مع تقدمه في تقارب أكثر وأكثر حميمية. في هذه الأثناء ، يجب على مريضة شابة اتخاذ قرار بشأن العلاج الذي يمكن أن ينقذ حياتها أو ربما يدمر زواجها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919113500" stop="20200919122000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">Shaun visits his father on his deathbed and the family reunion reveals unexpected results. Melendez, Park, Reznick and Browne treat an injured star NFL player with severe spinal damage. Claire addresses her mental health. يزور شون والده وهو على فراش الموت ويكشف لم شمل الأسرة عن نتائج غير متوقعة. ميلينديز ، بارك ، ريزنيك وبراون يعالجون لاعب كرة قدم نجم مصاب بأضرار بالغة في العمود الفقري. كلير تتحدث عن صحتها العقلية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919122000" stop="20200919130500" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">Following his father's death, Shaun must deal with the effects his intimacy with Lea will have on his relationship with Carly. Meanwhile, the team operates on a patient who is refusing all anaesthesia during surgery for fear of relapsing. بعد وفاة والده ، يجب على شون التعامل مع الآثار المترتبة على علاقته مع ليا في علاقته مع كارلي. وفي الوقت نفسه ، يعمل الفريق على مريض يرفض كل عمليات التخدير أثناء الجراحة خوفًا من الانتكاس.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919130500" stop="20200919135000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">The doctors treat a 25-year-old runner suffering from severe swelling, but when things take a turn for the worse, Shaun enlists the help of Carly. Meanwhile, Park, Browne and Melendez treat two 16-year-old cancer patients who are dating. يعالج الأطباء عداءًا يبلغ من العمر 25 عامًا يعاني من تورم شديد ، ولكن عندما تتحول الأمور إلى الأسوأ ، يطلب شون مساعدة كارلي. وفي الوقت نفسه ، يعالج بارك وبراون وميليندز إثنان من مرضى السرطان يبلغان من العمر 16 عامًا.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919135000" stop="20200919143500" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">A terminal cancer patient is determined to live the last few months of his life without inhibition. Dr. Reznik must confront her relationship with her mother when she comes in for a third opinion from Dr. Glassman. ينوي مريض سرطان على عيش الأشهر القليلة الأخيرة من حياته دون تثبيط. يجب على الدكتورة رزنيك مواجهة علاقتها مع والدتها عندما تأتي كثالث خيار من دكتور غلاسمان.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919143500" stop="20200919152000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">Shaun deals with unwanted attention after treating a patient who is a social influencer. Meanwhile, the team treats a woman who is in abdominal distress after an at-home faecal transplant; and Carly's efforts to separate Shaun from Lea are challenged. يتعامل شون مع الاهتمام غير المرغوب فيه بعد علاج مريض له تأثير اجتماعي. وفي الوقت نفسه ، يعالج الفريق امرأة تعاني من ضائقة في البطن بعد عملية جراحية في المنزل. وجهود كارلي لفصل شون عن ليا يتم تحديها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919152000" stop="20200919160500" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">Despite everyone else's doubts, Shaun is hopeful that Carly is truly fine with his friendship with Lea. The team treats a young boy born without a fully formed trachea and unable to speak, and who may be a good candidate for an experimental procedure. على الرغم من شكوك الجميع ، يأمل شون أن يكون كارلي مقتنعاً بصداقته مع ليا. يعالج الفريق صبيًا صغيرًا ولد بدون قصبة هوائية كاملة وغير قادر على الكلام ، والذي قد يكون مرشحًا جيدًا لإجراء تجريبي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919160500" stop="20200919165000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Shaun makes an emotional confession, the result may not be as desired. Meanwhile, he becomes obsessed with performing an autopsy on a Jane Doe. Browne, Reznick and Andrews treat a male college student with a mysterious split personality disorder. عندما يقوم شون باعتراف عاطفي، قد لا تكون النتيجة كما هو مرغوب. في هذه الأثناء ، أصبح مهووسًا بإجراء تشريح لشخص مجهول. يعالج براون ، وريزنك ، وأندروز طالبًا جامعيًا يعاني من انفصام غامض في الشخصية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919165000" stop="20200919173500" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">A patient with a mysterious and undiagnosed illness that has baffled other doctors for years forces Shaun and the team to take some big risks. Claire and Melendez continue to cautiously navigate their feelings for each other as colleagues and friends. مريض يعاني من مرض غامض وغير مشخص حير الأطباء الآخرين لسنوات يجبر شون والفريق على تحمل بعض المخاطر الكبيرة. تواصل كلير وميليندز التنقل بحذر تجاه مشاعر بعضهما البعض كزملاء وأصدقاء.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919173500" stop="20200919182000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">Claire and Shaun treat a patient with a rare form of dwarfism. Reznick, Lim and Park treat a young man who had both arms torn off in a previous farming accident. Shaun reacts to an emotional situation. تعالج كلير وشون مريضا يعاني من شكل نادر من التقزم. رزنيك و ليم و بارك يعالجون شابًا بترت ذراعاه في حادث أثناء عمله في الزراعة. يتفاعل شون مع موقف عاطفي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919182000" stop="20200919190500" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">Bonaventure Hospital on high alert as they race to assess the damage and account for the safety of their colleagues and friends. مستشفى بونافنشر في حالة تأهب قصوى أثناء تسابق الأطباء لتقييم الضرر ومراعاة سلامة زملائهم وأصدقائهم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919190500" stop="20200919200000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Doctor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غوود دكتور</title>
    <desc lang="en">The staff of St. Bonaventure Hospital works against time and their own personal safety to save the lives of those around them. يسابق موظفو مستشفى سانت بونافنشر الوقت وأمانهم الشخصي لإنقاذ حياة من حولهم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919200000" stop="20200919210000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Succession</title>
    <title lang="ar">ساكساشين</title>
    <desc lang="en">With the vote of no confidence against Logan approaching, Roman attempts to sway a neutral board member, while Kendall shores up his "yea" votes. Logan arrives in Washington to meet with the president, but worries he's been snubbed following a last-minute cancellation. مع اقتراب موعد التصويت بعدم الثقة ضد لوجان ، يحاول رومان التأثير على عضو مجلس إدارة محايد ، في حين أن كيندال يشجع التصويت "نعم". يصل لوغان إلى واشنطن للاجتماع مع الرئيس ، لكنه قلق من أنه تم تجاهله بعد إلغاء الاجتماع في اللحظة الأخيرة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919210000" stop="20200919220000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Reprisal</title>
    <title lang="ar">ريبريزال</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ethan fears being found out, as Burt comes home and declares war. Having lost control, Joel does what's best for his daughter. Doris and the Monster Ring prepare to take the fight to the Brawlers. Out on her own, Meredith is forced to save herself. يخشى إيثان أن يتم اكتشاف مكانه، عندما يعود بيرت إلى الديار ويعلن الحرب. بعد أن فقد السيطرة ، يقوم جويل بما هو أفضل لابنته. تستعد دوريس ومونستر رينغ لنقل المعركة إلى الـ برولرز. تجبر ميريديث على إنقاذ نفسها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919220000" stop="20200919223500" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Sex And The City</title>
    <title lang="ar">سيكس آند ذا سيتي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Carrie wonders if luck has deserted her when she's mugged and trips down some stairs. Meanwhile, Samantha handles the needs of an inexperienced college student, Miranda drinks a little too heavily whilst on a date, and Charlotte suggests a trial separation with Trey. تتساءل كاري ما إذا كان الحظ قد ابتعد عنها عندما تتعثر على السلالم. في هذه الأثناء، تتكفل سامانثا بحاجات طالب كلية بدون أي خبرة تذكر، بينما تشرب ميراندا بشكل كبير أثناء مواعدة أحد الشبان، وتطالب شارلوت بالانفصال عن تراي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919020000" stop="20200919030000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <title lang="ar">لايت نايت ويذ سيث مييرز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hosted by Seth Myers, an Emmy Award-winning writer and former head writer on “Saturday Night Live”, this legendary late-night talk show is home to A-list celebrity guests, memorable comedy and topical monologue jokes. برنامج حواري يومي أمريكي يستضيف كوكبة من نجوم هوليوود، يقدمه المؤلف والفنان الكوميدي سيث مايرز نجم برنامج ساترداي نايت لايف.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919030000" stop="20200919040000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا تونايت شو ستيرينغ جيمي فالون</title>
    <desc lang="en">Comedian and Saturday Night Live star Jimmy Fallon welcomes some of the biggest names in showbiz for an entertaining hour of music, chat and comedy. يستضيف الفنان الكوميدي جيمي فالون نجم ساترداي نايت لايف كوكبة من ألمع الأسماء في عالم الفن في ساعة كاملة تحفل بالموسيقى، الحوار والضحك.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919040000" stop="20200919050000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">The Ellen DeGeneres Show</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذي إيلين ديجينرس شو</title>
    <desc lang="en">Emmy Award-winning comedian and television pioneer Ellen DeGeneres brings her unique brand of hilarity to daytime talk with a dazzling array of celebrity interviews, an eclectic mix of musical performances and ordinary people with extraordinary stories and talents. تجلب الكوميدية والرائدة التلفزيونية الحائزة على جائزة إيمي إيلين ديجينيرز، علامتها التجارية الفريدة من نوعها إلى الحديث النهاري مع مجموعة رائعة من المقابلات مع المشاهير ، ومزيج انتقائي من العروض الموسيقية والأشخاص العاديين مع قصص ومواهب استثنائية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919050000" stop="20200919053000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">Web Therapy</title>
    <title lang="ar">ويب ثيرابي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jeb Masters calls Fiona and complains about her behaviour, which he says borders on sexual harassment. Meanwhile, Gina returns with examples of her new business venture, and Steve Olson tells Fiona that she is the one who should have trust issues. يتصل جيب ماسترز بـ فيونا للتذمر من تصرفاتها والتي تقترب من حدود التحرش الجنسي. وفي هذه الأثناء، تعود جينا وفي جعبتها أمثلة من مشروعها الجديد، ويقوم ستيف اولسون بإخبار فيونا بأنها هي من تعاني من مشاكل في الثقة بالآخرين.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919053000" stop="20200919055500" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">Married With Children</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماريد ويذ تشيلدرين</title>
    <desc lang="en">Al Bundy is an unsuccessful middle aged shoe salesman with a miserable life and an equally dysfunctional family. He hates his job, his wife is lazy, his son is dysfunctional (especially with women), and his daughter is dim-witted and promiscuous. فكاهة قاسية وبلا رحمة، مع عائلة أبعد ما تكون عن المفيد والنافع صحيا - بأميركا- كسولة، هادرة للوقت. تضم والدين مبتذلين: آل وبيغي، مع ولديهما المراهقين اللذين لا يرتجى منهما خيرا  أبداً.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919055500" stop="20200919062000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">Married With Children</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماريد ويذ تشيلدرين</title>
    <desc lang="en">Al Bundy is an unsuccessful middle aged shoe salesman with a miserable life and an equally dysfunctional family. He hates his job, his wife is lazy, his son is dysfunctional (especially with women), and his daughter is dim-witted and promiscuous. فكاهة قاسية وبلا رحمة، مع عائلة أبعد ما تكون عن المفيد والنافع صحيا - بأميركا- كسولة، هادرة للوقت. تضم والدين مبتذلين: آل وبيغي، مع ولديهما المراهقين اللذين لا يرتجى منهما خيرا  أبداً.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919062000" stop="20200919071000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <title lang="ar">لايت نايت ويذ سيث مييرز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hosted by Seth Myers, an Emmy Award-winning writer and former head writer on “Saturday Night Live”, this legendary late-night talk show is home to A-list celebrity guests, memorable comedy and topical monologue jokes. برنامج حواري يومي أمريكي يستضيف كوكبة من نجوم هوليوود، يقدمه المؤلف والفنان الكوميدي سيث مايرز نجم برنامج ساترداي نايت لايف.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919071000" stop="20200919080000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">The Ellen DeGeneres Show</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذي إيلين ديجينرس شو</title>
    <desc lang="en">Emmy Award-winning comedian and television pioneer Ellen DeGeneres brings her unique brand of hilarity to daytime talk with a dazzling array of celebrity interviews, an eclectic mix of musical performances and ordinary people with extraordinary stories and talents. تجلب الكوميدية والرائدة التلفزيونية الحائزة على جائزة إيمي إيلين ديجينيرز، علامتها التجارية الفريدة من نوعها إلى الحديث النهاري مع مجموعة رائعة من المقابلات مع المشاهير ، ومزيج انتقائي من العروض الموسيقية والأشخاص العاديين مع قصص ومواهب استثنائية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919080000" stop="20200919090000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا تونايت شو ستيرينغ جيمي فالون</title>
    <desc lang="en">Comedian and Saturday Night Live star Jimmy Fallon welcomes some of the biggest names in showbiz for an entertaining hour of music, chat and comedy. يستضيف الفنان الكوميدي جيمي فالون نجم ساترداي نايت لايف كوكبة من ألمع الأسماء في عالم الفن في ساعة كاملة تحفل بالموسيقى، الحوار والضحك.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919090000" stop="20200919093000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">Married With Children</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماريد ويذ تشيلدرين</title>
    <desc lang="en">Al Bundy is an unsuccessful middle aged shoe salesman with a miserable life and an equally dysfunctional family. He hates his job, his wife is lazy, his son is dysfunctional (especially with women), and his daughter is dim-witted and promiscuous. فكاهة قاسية وبلا رحمة، مع عائلة أبعد ما تكون عن المفيد والنافع صحيا - بأميركا- كسولة، هادرة للوقت. تضم والدين مبتذلين: آل وبيغي، مع ولديهما المراهقين اللذين لا يرتجى منهما خيرا  أبداً.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919093000" stop="20200919100000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">Married With Children</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماريد ويذ تشيلدرين</title>
    <desc lang="en">Al Bundy is an unsuccessful middle aged shoe salesman with a miserable life and an equally dysfunctional family. He hates his job, his wife is lazy, his son is dysfunctional (especially with women), and his daughter is dim-witted and promiscuous. فكاهة قاسية وبلا رحمة، مع عائلة أبعد ما تكون عن المفيد والنافع صحيا - بأميركا- كسولة، هادرة للوقت. تضم والدين مبتذلين: آل وبيغي، مع ولديهما المراهقين اللذين لا يرتجى منهما خيرا  أبداً.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919100000" stop="20200919103000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">The Last O.G.</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا لاست او.جاي.</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ex-con Tray is shocked to see how much the world has changed when he's released from prison for good behaviour after a 15-year stint. صُدم تراي بمدى تغير العالم عندما أطلق سراحه من السجن بسبب سلوكه الجيد بعد قضاء 15 عامًا.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919103000" stop="20200919113000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">The Ellen DeGeneres Show</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذي إيلين ديجينرس شو</title>
    <desc lang="en">Emmy Award-winning comedian and television pioneer Ellen DeGeneres brings her unique brand of hilarity to daytime talk with a dazzling array of celebrity interviews, an eclectic mix of musical performances and ordinary people with extraordinary stories and talents. تجلب الكوميدية والرائدة التلفزيونية الحائزة على جائزة إيمي إيلين ديجينيرز، علامتها التجارية الفريدة من نوعها إلى الحديث النهاري مع مجموعة رائعة من المقابلات مع المشاهير ، ومزيج انتقائي من العروض الموسيقية والأشخاص العاديين مع قصص ومواهب استثنائية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919113000" stop="20200919120000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">How I Met Your Mother</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو آي مت يور ماذر</title>
    <desc lang="en">The gang tries to kick the smoking habit. Meanwhile, Robin deals with her new co-anchor at Channel 1, who's clearly given up on the job. تحاول الفرقة الإقلاع عن التدخين. وتتحدث روبن إلى زميلتها المذيعة الجديدة في القناة الأولى والتي فقدت ثقتها بوظيفتها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919120000" stop="20200919123000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">How I Met Your Mother</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو آي مت يور ماذر</title>
    <desc lang="en">Barney chooses between wearing suits and sleeping with a sexy bartender. Meanwhile, Ted dates a student from Columbia and reveals she's the roommate of his future wife. يختار بارني ما بين ارتداء بذلة ومواعدة ساقية مثيرة. يواعد تيد تلميذة من كولومبيا والتي تكشف بأنها تشارك زوجته العتيدة غرفتها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919123000" stop="20200919130000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">Married With Children</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماريد ويذ تشيلدرين</title>
    <desc lang="en">Al Bundy is an unsuccessful middle aged shoe salesman with a miserable life and an equally dysfunctional family. He hates his job, his wife is lazy, his son is dysfunctional (especially with women), and his daughter is dim-witted and promiscuous. فكاهة قاسية وبلا رحمة، مع عائلة أبعد ما تكون عن المفيد والنافع صحيا - بأميركا- كسولة، هادرة للوقت. تضم والدين مبتذلين: آل وبيغي، مع ولديهما المراهقين اللذين لا يرتجى منهما خيرا  أبداً.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919130000" stop="20200919133000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">Married With Children</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماريد ويذ تشيلدرين</title>
    <desc lang="en">Al Bundy is an unsuccessful middle aged shoe salesman with a miserable life and an equally dysfunctional family. He hates his job, his wife is lazy, his son is dysfunctional (especially with women), and his daughter is dim-witted and promiscuous. فكاهة قاسية وبلا رحمة، مع عائلة أبعد ما تكون عن المفيد والنافع صحيا - بأميركا- كسولة، هادرة للوقت. تضم والدين مبتذلين: آل وبيغي، مع ولديهما المراهقين اللذين لا يرتجى منهما خيرا  أبداً.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919133000" stop="20200919135500" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">Bless This Mess</title>
    <title lang="ar">بلس ذيس ميس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mike and Rio get a taste of the parenting life when they are forced to take care of Portia's six piglets; Kay and Beau may have found common ground during the annual euchre tournament party. يتذوق مايك وريو حياة الأبوة والأمومة عندما يضطران لرعاية خنازير بورتيا الستة ؛ ربما وجد كاي وبو أرضية مشتركة خلال حفل البطولة السنوي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919135500" stop="20200919142000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">Bless This Mess</title>
    <title lang="ar">بلس ذيس ميس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rio tries to help Kay get over jealousy of her sister Stacey; Rio learns that Mike and Stacey used to date; Rudy and Constance want to take their relationship to the next level. تحاول ريو مساعدة كاي في التغلب على غيرتها من أختها ستايسي. يعلم ريو أن مايك وستايسي كانا يتواعدان. يريد رودي وكونستانس نقل علاقتهما إلى المستوى التالي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919142000" stop="20200919144500" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">The Last O.G.</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا لاست او.جاي.</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ex-con Tray is shocked to see how much the world has changed when he's released from prison for good behaviour after a 15-year stint. صُدم تراي بمدى تغير العالم عندما أطلق سراحه من السجن بسبب سلوكه الجيد بعد قضاء 15 عامًا.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919144500" stop="20200919151000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">The Last O.G.</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا لاست او.جاي.</title>
    <desc lang="en">After getting turned down for a job at a high-end restaurant, Tray stumbles into a position at a chain coffee shop. The twist - it's owned by Wavy, the drug dealer that Tray took the fall for. بعد أن تم رفض طلبه في الحصول على وظيفة في مطعم راقي، يحصل تراي على عمل في مقهى. لكن الأمر الغريب أن صاحب المقهى هو ويفي، تاجر المخدرات الذي دخل بسببه تراي السجن.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919151000" stop="20200919160000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">The Ellen DeGeneres Show</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذي إيلين ديجينرس شو</title>
    <desc lang="en">Emmy Award-winning comedian and television pioneer Ellen DeGeneres brings her unique brand of hilarity to daytime talk with a dazzling array of celebrity interviews, an eclectic mix of musical performances and ordinary people with extraordinary stories and talents. تجلب الكوميدية والرائدة التلفزيونية الحائزة على جائزة إيمي إيلين ديجينيرز، علامتها التجارية الفريدة من نوعها إلى الحديث النهاري مع مجموعة رائعة من المقابلات مع المشاهير ، ومزيج انتقائي من العروض الموسيقية والأشخاص العاديين مع قصص ومواهب استثنائية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919160000" stop="20200919163000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">Married With Children</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماريد ويذ تشيلدرين</title>
    <desc lang="en">Al Bundy is an unsuccessful middle aged shoe salesman with a miserable life and an equally dysfunctional family. He hates his job, his wife is lazy, his son is dysfunctional (especially with women), and his daughter is dim-witted and promiscuous. فكاهة قاسية وبلا رحمة، مع عائلة أبعد ما تكون عن المفيد والنافع صحيا - بأميركا- كسولة، هادرة للوقت. تضم والدين مبتذلين: آل وبيغي، مع ولديهما المراهقين اللذين لا يرتجى منهما خيرا  أبداً.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919163000" stop="20200919170000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">Married With Children</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماريد ويذ تشيلدرين</title>
    <desc lang="en">Al Bundy is an unsuccessful middle aged shoe salesman with a miserable life and an equally dysfunctional family. He hates his job, his wife is lazy, his son is dysfunctional (especially with women), and his daughter is dim-witted and promiscuous. فكاهة قاسية وبلا رحمة، مع عائلة أبعد ما تكون عن المفيد والنافع صحيا - بأميركا- كسولة، هادرة للوقت. تضم والدين مبتذلين: آل وبيغي، مع ولديهما المراهقين اللذين لا يرتجى منهما خيرا  أبداً.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919170000" stop="20200919173000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">How I Met Your Mother</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو آي مت يور ماذر</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Marshall's co-worker Jenkins kisses him, he can't get Lily to believe it happened. Robin discovers she's the subject of a drinking game played by people watching her talk show. عندما تقوم جينكينز زميلة مارشال بتقبيله، لم يستطع إقناع ليلي بحدوث ذلك. تكتشف روبن أنها موضوع لعبة شراب يلعبها أشخاص يشاهدون برنامجها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919173000" stop="20200919180000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">How I Met Your Mother</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو آي مت يور ماذر</title>
    <desc lang="en">Depressed over their own lousy weeks, the rest of the gang cheer Barney on towards a 'perfect week': seven girls in seven days with no rejections. بعد شعورهم بالإحباط من الأسابيع السيئة التي أمضوها، يقوم بقية الفريق بتحضير أسبوع مميز لـ بارني، 7 فتيات في 7 أيام.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919180000" stop="20200919183000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">Bless This Mess</title>
    <title lang="ar">بلس ذيس ميس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mike and Rio are thrilled about having their first Christmas alone as a married couple, but a wrench is thrown into their romanticized holiday plans as they are interrupted by crisis after crisis; Kay invites Beau home for Christmas. يشعر مايك وريو بسعادة غامرة حيال أول عيد ميلاد لهما كزوجين فقط ، ولكنهما يتعرضان لبعض المشاكل خلال عطلتهما الرومانسية حيث واجها العديد من الأزمات؛ كاي تدعو بو إلى منزلها بعيد الميلاد.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919183000" stop="20200919190000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">Bless This Mess</title>
    <title lang="ar">بلس ذيس ميس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mike and Rio must decide what seed to start growing on their farm; Rio tries to get Beau and Kay's relationship to set sail; Jacob shadows Constance for a school project, making Rudy a nervous wreck while they discuss catching criminals. يجب على مايك وريو تحديد نوع البذور لزرعها في مزرعتهم ؛ يحاول ريو جعل علاقة بيو وكاي تنجح؛ يساعد يعقوب كونستانس في مشروع مدرسي ، مما يجعل رودي عصبيًا أثناء مناقشة القبض على المجرمين.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919190000" stop="20200919193000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <title lang="ar">بروكلن ناين-ناين</title>
    <desc lang="en">Back with season seven,"Brooklyn Nine-Nine" follows the exploits of hilarious Det, Jake Peralta (Andy Samberg) and his diverse, lovable colleagues as they police the NYPD's 99th Precinct. مع عودته بالموسم السابع، بروكلن ناين-ناين يروي بطولات العظماء ديت، جيك بيرالتا (آندي سامبرج) وزملاؤه المحبوبون أثناء تأدية خدمتهم مع شرطة نيويورك.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919193000" stop="20200919200000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">What We Do In The Shadows</title>
    <title lang="ar">وات وي دو إن ذا شادوز</title>
    <desc lang="en">The vampires offer shelter to an old nemesis who’s down on his luck. يوفر مصاصوا الدماء المأوى لخصم قديم لم يحالفه الحظ.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919200000" stop="20200919210000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا تونايت شو ستيرينغ جيمي فالون</title>
    <desc lang="en">Comedian and Saturday Night Live star Jimmy Fallon welcomes some of the biggest names in showbiz for an entertaining hour of music, chat and comedy. يستضيف الفنان الكوميدي جيمي فالون نجم ساترداي نايت لايف كوكبة من ألمع الأسماء في عالم الفن في ساعة كاملة تحفل بالموسيقى، الحوار والضحك.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919210000" stop="20200919213000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">Web Therapy</title>
    <title lang="ar">ويب ثيرابي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hayley returns from Bali with big news....and an even bigger confession. تعود هايلي من بالي وفي جعبتها أخبار مهمة... بالإضافة إلى سر أهم للإفصاح عنه.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919213000" stop="20200919220000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">Silicon Valley</title>
    <title lang="ar">سيليكون فالي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Richard fumes when Gavin gains new notoriety for spreading a message of tech accountability. Dinesh's trip to Hawaii quickly turns into a nightmare. Gilfoyle and Monica set out to improve their peer review scores in the office. Holden braces for a showdown with Jared. يغضب ريتشارد عندما يكتسب جافين سمعة جديدة لنشره رسالة المساءلة التقنية. تتحول رحلة دينيش إلى هاواي بسرعة إلى كابوس. بدأ غلفويل و مونيكا في تحسين نتائج مراجعة النظراء في المكتب. هولدن يستعد لمواجهة مع جاريد.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919220000" stop="20200919223000" channel="OSN Comedy HD">
    <title lang="en">Dollface</title>
    <title lang="ar">دولفايس</title>
    <desc lang="en">After being dumped by her longtime boyfriend, a young woman must deal with her own imagination in order to literally and metaphorically re-enter the world of women, and rekindle the female friendships she left behind. بعد أن تخلى عنها صديقها القديم ، يجب على المرأة الشابة أن تتعامل مع خيالها من أجل العودة إلى عالم النساء حرفيًا واستعاريًا ، وإحياء الصداقات النسائية التي تركتها وراءها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919020000" stop="20200919023000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Tosh.0</title>
    <title lang="ar">توش.0</title>
    <desc lang="en">Daniel talks to a man who enjoys acting like a horse, makes the case for celebrating all birthdays on the same day and exposes celebrities without their makeup. يتحدث دانيال إلى رجل يستمتع بالتصرف كالحصان ويعرف عن كل الأشخاص الذين يقومون بالاحتفال بأعياد ميلادهم بنفس  اليوم ويعرض صور للمشاهير بدون مكياج.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919023000" stop="20200919030000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Tosh.0</title>
    <title lang="ar">توش.0</title>
    <desc lang="en">Daniel meets a low-energy energy drink reviewer, explores the fine art of balloon popping and breaks down video of a man getting a "purple shower.". يلتقي دانيال بمراقب جودة لمشروبات الطاقة ليشاهدا معا الفن الجميل لفرقعة البالون ومشاهدة فيديو عن رجل يستخدم حمام بنفسجي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919030000" stop="20200919033000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Tosh.0</title>
    <title lang="ar">توش.0</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tosh.0 is a weekly topical series hosted by comedian Daniel Tosh that delves into all aspects of the internet, from the ingenious - to the absurd - to the medically inadvisable. توش.0 هو مسلسل موضوعي أسبوعي من تقديم الكوميدي دانيل توش، يغوص في كافة تفاصيل الإنترنت، المبتكر منها والسخيف، إلى جانب غير المستحسن طبيا.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919033000" stop="20200919040000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Tosh.0</title>
    <title lang="ar">توش.0</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tosh.0 is a weekly topical series hosted by comedian Daniel Tosh that delves into all aspects of the internet, from the ingenious - to the absurd - to the medically inadvisable. توش.0 هو مسلسل موضوعي أسبوعي من تقديم الكوميدي دانيل توش، يغوص في كافة تفاصيل الإنترنت، المبتكر منها والسخيف، إلى جانب غير المستحسن طبيا.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919040000" stop="20200919043000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Takeshis Castle Thailand</title>
    <title lang="ar">تايكشيس كاسل تايلاند</title>
    <desc lang="en">A Thai revival of the cult classic Japanese comedy gameshow. The evil Shogun Takeshi has kidnapped Princess Woonsen and imprisoned her in his castle. Contestants aim to storm Takeshi's castle and free her. إحياء تايلندي للعبة كوميدية يابانية كلاسيكية. خطف شوغون تاكيشي الشرير الأميرة فونسين وسجنها في قلعته. يهدف المتسابقون إلى اقتحام قلعة تاكيشي وإطلاق سراحها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919043000" stop="20200919050000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Takeshis Castle Thailand</title>
    <title lang="ar">تايكشيس كاسل تايلاند</title>
    <desc lang="en">A Thai revival of the cult classic Japanese comedy gameshow. The evil Shogun Takeshi has kidnapped Princess Woonsen and imprisoned her in his castle. Contestants aim to storm Takeshi's castle and free her. إحياء تايلندي للعبة كوميدية يابانية كلاسيكية. خطف شوغون تاكيشي الشرير الأميرة فونسين وسجنها في قلعته. يهدف المتسابقون إلى اقتحام قلعة تاكيشي وإطلاق سراحها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919050000" stop="20200919053000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Takeshis Castle Thailand</title>
    <title lang="ar">تايكشيس كاسل تايلاند</title>
    <desc lang="en">A Thai revival of the cult classic Japanese comedy gameshow. The evil Shogun Takeshi has kidnapped Princess Woonsen and imprisoned her in his castle. Contestants aim to storm Takeshi's castle and free her. إحياء تايلندي للعبة كوميدية يابانية كلاسيكية. خطف شوغون تاكيشي الشرير الأميرة فونسين وسجنها في قلعته. يهدف المتسابقون إلى اقتحام قلعة تاكيشي وإطلاق سراحها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919053000" stop="20200919060000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Takeshis Castle Thailand</title>
    <title lang="ar">تايكشيس كاسل تايلاند</title>
    <desc lang="en">A Thai revival of the cult classic Japanese comedy gameshow. The evil Shogun Takeshi has kidnapped Princess Woonsen and imprisoned her in his castle. Contestants aim to storm Takeshi's castle and free her. إحياء تايلندي للعبة كوميدية يابانية كلاسيكية. خطف شوغون تاكيشي الشرير الأميرة فونسين وسجنها في قلعته. يهدف المتسابقون إلى اقتحام قلعة تاكيشي وإطلاق سراحها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919060000" stop="20200919063000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Key And Peele</title>
    <title lang="ar">كي آند بيل</title>
    <desc lang="en">Key &amp; Peele showcases the fearless wit of stars Keegan-Michael Key and Jordan Peele. With an array of sketches as wide-reaching as they are cringingly accurate, the pair has created a bevy of classic characters. يعرض برنامج كي أند بيل خفة الدم الجريئة للنجمين كيغان-مايكل كي وجوردان بيل، فمن خلال مجموعة من الاسكتشات المنوعة، تمكن الاثنان من خلق مجموعة من الشخصيات الكلاسيكية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919063000" stop="20200919070000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Key And Peele</title>
    <title lang="ar">كي آند بيل</title>
    <desc lang="en">Key &amp; Peele showcases the fearless wit of stars Keegan-Michael Key and Jordan Peele. With an array of sketches as wide-reaching as they are cringingly accurate, the pair has created a bevy of classic characters. يعرض برنامج كي أند بيل خفة الدم الجريئة للنجمين كيغان-مايكل كي وجوردان بيل، فمن خلال مجموعة من الاسكتشات المنوعة، تمكن الاثنان من خلق مجموعة من الشخصيات الكلاسيكية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919070000" stop="20200919073000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Key And Peele</title>
    <title lang="ar">كي آند بيل</title>
    <desc lang="en">Key &amp; Peele showcases the fearless wit of stars Keegan-Michael Key and Jordan Peele. With an array of sketches as wide-reaching as they are cringingly accurate, the pair has created a bevy of classic characters. يعرض برنامج كي أند بيل خفة الدم الجريئة للنجمين كيغان-مايكل كي وجوردان بيل، فمن خلال مجموعة من الاسكتشات المنوعة، تمكن الاثنان من خلق مجموعة من الشخصيات الكلاسيكية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919073000" stop="20200919075500" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Key And Peele</title>
    <title lang="ar">كي آند بيل</title>
    <desc lang="en">Key &amp; Peele showcases the fearless wit of stars Keegan-Michael Key and Jordan Peele. With an array of sketches as wide-reaching as they are cringingly accurate, the pair has created a bevy of classic characters. يعرض برنامج كي أند بيل خفة الدم الجريئة للنجمين كيغان-مايكل كي وجوردان بيل، فمن خلال مجموعة من الاسكتشات المنوعة، تمكن الاثنان من خلق مجموعة من الشخصيات الكلاسيكية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919075500" stop="20200919082000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Key And Peele</title>
    <title lang="ar">كي آند بيل</title>
    <desc lang="en">Key &amp; Peele showcases the fearless wit of stars Keegan-Michael Key and Jordan Peele. With an array of sketches as wide-reaching as they are cringingly accurate, the pair has created a bevy of classic characters. يعرض برنامج كي أند بيل خفة الدم الجريئة للنجمين كيغان-مايكل كي وجوردان بيل، فمن خلال مجموعة من الاسكتشات المنوعة، تمكن الاثنان من خلق مجموعة من الشخصيات الكلاسيكية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919082000" stop="20200919085000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Friends</title>
    <title lang="ar">فريندز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Joey attempts ballroom dancing in order to help Monica and Rachel keep their illegal sublet. Phoebe is attracted to one of her massage clients and Chandler has trouble attempting to quit a gym. يقوم جوي بممارسة الرقص من أجل مساعدة مونيكا وراشيل في الحفاظ على أجرهما غير الشرعي. تنجذب فيبي لأحد زبائن التدليك ويجد تشاندلر صعوبة في الامتناع عن الذهاب إلى قاعة الرياضة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919085000" stop="20200919091500" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Friends</title>
    <title lang="ar">فريندز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Chandler hits on a woman at Central Perk, not realising she's Joey's new girlfriend. Ross and Rachel play the jealousy game in their relationships &amp; Phoebe tries to catch a cold to make her voice and singing more sexy. يغازل تشاندلر امرأة في الحديقة العامة دون أن يدرك انها صديقة جوي الجديدة. يمارس روس وراشيل لعبة الغيرة في علاقتهما وتحاول فيبي المستحيل كي تصاب بالزكام لجعل صوتها يبدو مثيراً.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919091500" stop="20200919094000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Friends</title>
    <title lang="ar">فريندز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ross's new girlfriend seems nearly perfect, until he discovers her apartment is incredibly dirty. Chandler helps Joey pick out a thoughtful present for Kathy's birthday whilst Phoebe helps Monica cater a funeral. تبدو صديقة روس الجديدة كاملة، إلى أن يكتشف أن شقتها متسخة بشكل كبير. يساعد تشاندلر جوي في انتقاء هدية لعيد ميلاد كاثي، بينما تساعد فيبي مونيكا في تلبية حاجات إحدى الجنازات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919094000" stop="20200919100500" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Friends</title>
    <title lang="ar">فريندز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Chandler must decide between the girl of his dreams and his best friend when he and Kathy share a kiss. Needless to say Joey is not happy to find out and nobody wants to tell Ross how awful his keyboard playing is. على تشاندلر الاختيار ما بين فتاة أحلامه وصديقه المفضل عندما يتشارك بقبلة مع كاثي. جوي غير مسرور لاكتشاف ذلك ولا أحد يريد مصارحة روس بأن عزفه سيئ جداً.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919100500" stop="20200919103000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Friends</title>
    <title lang="ar">فريندز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Chandler agrees to spend Thanksgiving in a shipping crate as penance for kissing Kathy and the gang decide on Secret Santa gifts. Monica injures her eye preparing dinner &amp; gets a shock when she goes to the eye-doctor. يوافق شاندلر على قضاء عيد الشكر في صندوق شحن كنوع من معاقبة لنفسه على تقبيله لكاتي، وتقرر المجموعة على هدايا بابا نويل السرّي. تؤذي مونيكا عينها بينما تحضر العشاء، وتصاب بصدمة عند ذهابها لطبيب العيون.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919103000" stop="20200919105500" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Workaholics</title>
    <title lang="ar">ووركاهولكس</title>
    <desc lang="en">For Blake, Adam and Anders, making the transition from slacker students to professional telemarketers isn't a smooth one, considering dress codes, deadlines and actually using an alarm clock are foreign concepts to them! لم يكن الانتقال بالنسبة لبليك، آدم وأندرز من طلاب كسولين إلى مُسوّقين محترفين بالأمر السهل، نظرا إلى أن قواعد اللباس، المواعيد واستخدام المنبه هي أفكار غريبة بالنسبة لهم!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919105500" stop="20200919112000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Workaholics</title>
    <title lang="ar">ووركاهولكس</title>
    <desc lang="en">For Blake, Adam and Anders, making the transition from slacker students to professional telemarketers isn't a smooth one, considering dress codes, deadlines and actually using an alarm clock are foreign concepts to them! لم يكن الانتقال بالنسبة لبليك، آدم وأندرز من طلاب كسولين إلى مُسوّقين محترفين بالأمر السهل، نظرا إلى أن قواعد اللباس، المواعيد واستخدام المنبه هي أفكار غريبة بالنسبة لهم!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919112000" stop="20200919114500" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Workaholics</title>
    <title lang="ar">ووركاهولكس</title>
    <desc lang="en">For Blake, Adam and Anders, making the transition from slacker students to professional telemarketers isn't a smooth one, considering dress codes, deadlines and actually using an alarm clock are foreign concepts to them! لم يكن الانتقال بالنسبة لبليك، آدم وأندرز من طلاب كسولين إلى مُسوّقين محترفين بالأمر السهل، نظرا إلى أن قواعد اللباس، المواعيد واستخدام المنبه هي أفكار غريبة بالنسبة لهم!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919114500" stop="20200919121000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Workaholics</title>
    <title lang="ar">ووركاهولكس</title>
    <desc lang="en">For Blake, Adam and Anders, making the transition from slacker students to professional telemarketers isn't a smooth one, considering dress codes, deadlines and actually using an alarm clock are foreign concepts to them! لم يكن الانتقال بالنسبة لبليك، آدم وأندرز من طلاب كسولين إلى مُسوّقين محترفين بالأمر السهل، نظرا إلى أن قواعد اللباس، المواعيد واستخدام المنبه هي أفكار غريبة بالنسبة لهم!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919121000" stop="20200919123500" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Workaholics</title>
    <title lang="ar">ووركاهولكس</title>
    <desc lang="en">For Blake, Adam and Anders, making the transition from slacker students to professional telemarketers isn't a smooth one, considering dress codes, deadlines and actually using an alarm clock are foreign concepts to them! لم يكن الانتقال بالنسبة لبليك، آدم وأندرز من طلاب كسولين إلى مُسوّقين محترفين بالأمر السهل، نظرا إلى أن قواعد اللباس، المواعيد واستخدام المنبه هي أفكار غريبة بالنسبة لهم!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919123500" stop="20200919130000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Key And Peele</title>
    <title lang="ar">كي آند بيل</title>
    <desc lang="en">Key &amp; Peele showcases the fearless wit of stars Keegan-Michael Key and Jordan Peele. With an array of sketches as wide-reaching as they are cringingly accurate, the pair has created a bevy of classic characters. يعرض برنامج كي أند بيل خفة الدم الجريئة للنجمين كيغان-مايكل كي وجوردان بيل، فمن خلال مجموعة من الاسكتشات المنوعة، تمكن الاثنان من خلق مجموعة من الشخصيات الكلاسيكية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919130000" stop="20200919133000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Key And Peele</title>
    <title lang="ar">كي آند بيل</title>
    <desc lang="en">Key &amp; Peele showcases the fearless wit of stars Keegan-Michael Key and Jordan Peele. With an array of sketches as wide-reaching as they are cringingly accurate, the pair has created a bevy of classic characters. يعرض برنامج كي أند بيل خفة الدم الجريئة للنجمين كيغان-مايكل كي وجوردان بيل، فمن خلال مجموعة من الاسكتشات المنوعة، تمكن الاثنان من خلق مجموعة من الشخصيات الكلاسيكية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919133000" stop="20200919140000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Key And Peele</title>
    <title lang="ar">كي آند بيل</title>
    <desc lang="en">Key &amp; Peele showcases the fearless wit of stars Keegan-Michael Key and Jordan Peele. With an array of sketches as wide-reaching as they are cringingly accurate, the pair has created a bevy of classic characters. يعرض برنامج كي أند بيل خفة الدم الجريئة للنجمين كيغان-مايكل كي وجوردان بيل، فمن خلال مجموعة من الاسكتشات المنوعة، تمكن الاثنان من خلق مجموعة من الشخصيات الكلاسيكية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919140000" stop="20200919142500" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Key And Peele</title>
    <title lang="ar">كي آند بيل</title>
    <desc lang="en">Key &amp; Peele showcases the fearless wit of stars Keegan-Michael Key and Jordan Peele. With an array of sketches as wide-reaching as they are cringingly accurate, the pair has created a bevy of classic characters. يعرض برنامج كي أند بيل خفة الدم الجريئة للنجمين كيغان-مايكل كي وجوردان بيل، فمن خلال مجموعة من الاسكتشات المنوعة، تمكن الاثنان من خلق مجموعة من الشخصيات الكلاسيكية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919142500" stop="20200919145000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Key And Peele</title>
    <title lang="ar">كي آند بيل</title>
    <desc lang="en">Key &amp; Peele showcases the fearless wit of stars Keegan-Michael Key and Jordan Peele. With an array of sketches as wide-reaching as they are cringingly accurate, the pair has created a bevy of classic characters. يعرض برنامج كي أند بيل خفة الدم الجريئة للنجمين كيغان-مايكل كي وجوردان بيل، فمن خلال مجموعة من الاسكتشات المنوعة، تمكن الاثنان من خلق مجموعة من الشخصيات الكلاسيكية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919145000" stop="20200919151500" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Real Husbands Of Hollywood</title>
    <title lang="ar">ريل هازبندز اوف هوليوود</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kevin Hart and all-star cast of Hollywood husbands play fictionalised versions of themselves in this semi-scripted reality show spoof. يقوم كيفن هارت وأهم النجوم الأزواج في هوليوود بتمثيل بعض المشاهد الخيالية في هذه المحاكاة الساخرة الشبه مكتوبة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919151500" stop="20200919154000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Real Husbands Of Hollywood</title>
    <title lang="ar">ريل هازبندز اوف هوليوود</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kevin Hart and all-star cast of Hollywood husbands play fictionalised versions of themselves in this semi-scripted reality show spoof. يقوم كيفن هارت وأهم النجوم الأزواج في هوليوود بتمثيل بعض المشاهد الخيالية في هذه المحاكاة الساخرة الشبه مكتوبة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919154000" stop="20200919161000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Real Husbands Of Hollywood</title>
    <title lang="ar">ريل هازبندز اوف هوليوود</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kevin Hart and all-star cast of Hollywood husbands play fictionalised versions of themselves in this semi-scripted reality show spoof. يقوم كيفن هارت وأهم النجوم الأزواج في هوليوود بتمثيل بعض المشاهد الخيالية في هذه المحاكاة الساخرة الشبه مكتوبة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919161000" stop="20200919163500" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Real Husbands Of Hollywood</title>
    <title lang="ar">ريل هازبندز اوف هوليوود</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kevin Hart and all-star cast of Hollywood husbands play fictionalised versions of themselves in this semi-scripted reality show spoof. يقوم كيفن هارت وأهم النجوم الأزواج في هوليوود بتمثيل بعض المشاهد الخيالية في هذه المحاكاة الساخرة الشبه مكتوبة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919163500" stop="20200919170000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Real Husbands Of Hollywood</title>
    <title lang="ar">ريل هازبندز اوف هوليوود</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kevin Hart and all-star cast of Hollywood husbands play fictionalised versions of themselves in this semi-scripted reality show spoof. يقوم كيفن هارت وأهم النجوم الأزواج في هوليوود بتمثيل بعض المشاهد الخيالية في هذه المحاكاة الساخرة الشبه مكتوبة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919170000" stop="20200919173000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Friends</title>
    <title lang="ar">فريندز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Joey attempts ballroom dancing in order to help Monica and Rachel keep their illegal sublet. Phoebe is attracted to one of her massage clients and Chandler has trouble attempting to quit a gym. يقوم جوي بممارسة الرقص من أجل مساعدة مونيكا وراشيل في الحفاظ على أجرهما غير الشرعي. تنجذب فيبي لأحد زبائن التدليك ويجد تشاندلر صعوبة في الامتناع عن الذهاب إلى قاعة الرياضة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919173000" stop="20200919180000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Friends</title>
    <title lang="ar">فريندز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Chandler hits on a woman at Central Perk, not realising she's Joey's new girlfriend. Ross and Rachel play the jealousy game in their relationships &amp; Phoebe tries to catch a cold to make her voice and singing more sexy. يغازل تشاندلر امرأة في الحديقة العامة دون أن يدرك انها صديقة جوي الجديدة. يمارس روس وراشيل لعبة الغيرة في علاقتهما وتحاول فيبي المستحيل كي تصاب بالزكام لجعل صوتها يبدو مثيراً.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919180000" stop="20200919183000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Friends</title>
    <title lang="ar">فريندز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ross's new girlfriend seems nearly perfect, until he discovers her apartment is incredibly dirty. Chandler helps Joey pick out a thoughtful present for Kathy's birthday whilst Phoebe helps Monica cater a funeral. تبدو صديقة روس الجديدة كاملة، إلى أن يكتشف أن شقتها متسخة بشكل كبير. يساعد تشاندلر جوي في انتقاء هدية لعيد ميلاد كاثي، بينما تساعد فيبي مونيكا في تلبية حاجات إحدى الجنازات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919183000" stop="20200919190000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Friends</title>
    <title lang="ar">فريندز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Chandler must decide between the girl of his dreams and his best friend when he and Kathy share a kiss. Needless to say Joey is not happy to find out and nobody wants to tell Ross how awful his keyboard playing is. على تشاندلر الاختيار ما بين فتاة أحلامه وصديقه المفضل عندما يتشارك بقبلة مع كاثي. جوي غير مسرور لاكتشاف ذلك ولا أحد يريد مصارحة روس بأن عزفه سيئ جداً.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919190000" stop="20200919193000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Friends</title>
    <title lang="ar">فريندز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Chandler agrees to spend Thanksgiving in a shipping crate as penance for kissing Kathy and the gang decide on Secret Santa gifts. Monica injures her eye preparing dinner &amp; gets a shock when she goes to the eye-doctor. يوافق شاندلر على قضاء عيد الشكر في صندوق شحن كنوع من معاقبة لنفسه على تقبيله لكاتي، وتقرر المجموعة على هدايا بابا نويل السرّي. تؤذي مونيكا عينها بينما تحضر العشاء، وتصاب بصدمة عند ذهابها لطبيب العيون.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919193000" stop="20200919200000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Broad City</title>
    <title lang="ar">برود سيتي</title>
    <desc lang="en">On a spring day in 2011, Abbi and Ilana meet for the first time. في يوم ربيعي من العام 2011 ، يلتقي آبي وإلانا للمرة الأولى.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919200000" stop="20200919210000" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Bridget Everett: Gynecological Wonder</title>
    <title lang="ar">بردجيت افريت جينوكوليجكال وندر</title>
    <desc lang="en">Bridget Everett takes everyone by the balls in her one-hour special, Gynecological Wonder. Her raucous, raunchy and hilarious show is as heartfelt as it is unpredictable as she belts out beautiful songs that will make you laugh, cry and sometimes cringe. تأخذ بريدجيت إيفريت الجميع في جولة في فيلمها الخاص لمدة ساعة واحدة ، المعجزة النسائية. إن عرضها الصاخب والمليء بالمرح هو أمر صادق بقدر ما لا يمكن التنبؤ به لأنها تقوم بإخراج الأغاني الجميلة التي ستجعلك تضحك وتبكي وتتأرجح أحيانًا.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919210000" stop="20200919214500" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">The Daily Show With Trevor Noah</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا ديلي شو ويذ تريفر نوا</title>
    <desc lang="en">Trevor Noah and The Daily Show correspondents tackle the biggest stories in news, politics and pop culture. يعالج مراسلو تريفور نوح وذا ديلي شو اهم القصص الاخبارية والسياسية فضلاً عن ثقافة البوب.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919214500" stop="20200919223500" channel="Comedy Central">
    <title lang="en">Jeff Ross Roast The Border Live From Brownsville</title>
    <title lang="ar">جيف روس روست ذا بوردر لايف فرم براونسفل</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jeff Ross travels to the U.S.-Mexico border to put on a stand-up show next to the wall and talk to the people being affected by American immigration policies. يسافر جيف روس إلى الحدود بين الولايات المتحدة والمكسيك لوضع عرض تقديمي بجانب الجدار والتحدث إلى الأشخاص الذين يتأثرون بسياسات الهجرة الأمريكية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919020000" stop="20200919030000" channel="Star World HD">
    <title lang="en">Say Yes To The Dress: Atlanta</title>
    <title lang="ar">سي ياس تو ذا دراس: اطلنطا</title>
    <desc lang="en">After putting a life-threatening disease behind her, Alyssa is looking forward to a bright future. Shornell is not so sure about what she wants. تأتي النساء المخطوبات حديثاً من جميع أنحاء العالم إلى متجر فساتين الزفاف هذا لإيجاد الثوب المثالي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919030000" stop="20200919040000" channel="Star World HD">
    <title lang="en">Filthy Rich</title>
    <title lang="ar">فيلثي ريتش</title>
    <desc lang="en">After Fisher's plan works, Brady needs to get back to her family and deal with the old and new.  Joe's family connections are troublesome. بعد نجاح خطة فيشر  تحتاج برادي للعودة إلى عائلتها والتعامل مع القديم والجديد وتكون الروابط العائلية بالنسبة لجو مرهقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919040000" stop="20200919050000" channel="Star World HD">
    <title lang="en">Project Runway All Stars</title>
    <title lang="ar">بروجيكت رانواي اول ستارز</title>
    <desc lang="en">The contestants are asked to incorporate a corset into high end fashion look, to celebrate the elegance of a woman's figure. يعود المصممون السابقون للمنافسة للحصول على فرصة أخرى ليكونوا فائزين في بروجكت رانواي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919050000" stop="20200919060000" channel="Star World HD">
    <title lang="en">Battle Of The Fittest Couples</title>
    <title lang="ar">باتل أوف ذا فايتيست كوبلس</title>
    <desc lang="en">An exhausting Main Event challenge is taking the rivalry to the next level, sending one pair to the ER and others looking for vengeance. Eleven couples remain in the chase. تحد رئيسي ومرهق ينقل المنافسة الى المستوى التالي و إرسال أحد الأزواج الى غرفة الطوارئ و متسابقون آخرون يسعوون للانتقام ويبقى إحدى عشرة زوجا" في المسابقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919060000" stop="20200919063000" channel="Star World HD">
    <title lang="en">Cuckoo</title>
    <title lang="ar">كوكو</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rachel and Lorna are occupied elsewhere. Dale recounts stories of his past. Ken want a quiet family evening on his birthday. راشيل ولورنا مشغولان في مكان آخر و يروي ديل قصصا عن ماضيه و يريد كين أمسية عائلية هادئة في عيد ميلاده.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919063000" stop="20200919070000" channel="Star World HD">
    <title lang="en">Cuckoo</title>
    <title lang="ar">كوكو</title>
    <desc lang="en">Rachel gets a visit from Ben, who wants to resume their relationship. Dylan wants to drop out from university after a month after being dumped by girlfriend Zoe. Ken and Dale try to stop Dylan from doing so. تتلقى راشيل زيارة من بن والذي يريد إعادة العلاقة بينهما ويريد ديلان ترك الجامعة بعد شهر من هجر صديقته زوي له و يحاول كين وديل منع ديلان من القيام بذلك.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919070000" stop="20200919080000" channel="Star World HD">
    <title lang="en">Say Yes To The Dress: Atlanta</title>
    <title lang="ar">سي ياس تو ذا دراس: اطلنطا</title>
    <desc lang="en">Britt needs a dress fast while Shelby needs to find a dress that she likes in her size. Will they get what they want? تأتي النساء المخطوبات حديثاً من جميع أنحاء العالم إلى متجر فساتين الزفاف هذا لإيجاد الثوب المثالي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919080000" stop="20200919090000" channel="Star World HD">
    <title lang="en">Filthy Rich</title>
    <title lang="ar">فيلثي ريتش</title>
    <desc lang="en">After a terrible tragedy everyone longs for justice. While Vader is there for a damsel in distress, Savannah swears to murder the killer. بعد مأساة رهيبة يتوق الجميع إلى العدالة وبينما يقوم فادر بمساندة  فتاة في محنة تقسم سافانا على قتل الجاني.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919090000" stop="20200919100000" channel="Star World HD">
    <title lang="en">Project Runway All Stars</title>
    <title lang="ar">بروجيكت رانواي اول ستارز</title>
    <desc lang="en">The fashion in this episode is inspired by the zoo animals for a wild night. The judges are Joan Smalls and Peyton List. يعود المصممون السابقون للمنافسة للحصول على فرصة أخرى ليكونوا فائزين في بروجكت رانواي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919100000" stop="20200919110000" channel="Star World HD">
    <title lang="en">Battle Of The Fittest Couples</title>
    <title lang="ar">باتل أوف ذا فايتيست كوبلس</title>
    <desc lang="en">The demanding Main Event shakes things up for the remaining ten couples. A "Super Secret Alliance" is trying to change the power balance. Emotions run high when one pair feels unfairly targeted. الحدث الرئيسي المفروض يقوم بتغيير شامل لأوضاع الأزواج العشرة المتبقيين وتحالف سري للغاية يغير توازن الفرق وتحتدم المشاعر عندما  تشعر إحدى الفرق بأنها مستهدفة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919110000" stop="20200919113000" channel="Star World HD">
    <title lang="en">Cuckoo</title>
    <title lang="ar">كوكو</title>
    <desc lang="en">On the naming ceremony of Lorna and Ken's baby Sid not only does Zoe brings her new boyfriend which irritates Dylan but Ken's annoying mother also shows up. خلال حفل تسمية طفل لورنا وكين لم يكن إحضار زوي لصديقها الجديد و الذي يسبب الإزعاج لديلان كافيا ولكن تظهر والدة كين المزعجة أيضًا.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919113000" stop="20200919120000" channel="Star World HD">
    <title lang="en">Cuckoo</title>
    <title lang="ar">كوكو</title>
    <desc lang="en">The family goes on a holiday to Cumbria, leaving Sid with Belinda. Meanwhile Ken and Lorna try to find the man Belinda told Ken was his real father. Mr. XI lands up from China to make Dale an offer he can't refuse. تذهب العائلة في إجازة إلى كمبريا تاركة سيد مع بليندا و في هذه الأثناء يحاول كين ولورنا العثور على الرجل الذي أخبرت بليندا عنه لكين أنه والده الحقيقي و يصل السيد إكسل من الصين ليقدم عرضا لدايل لا يمكنه.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919120000" stop="20200919130000" channel="Star World HD">
    <title lang="en">Say Yes To The Dress: Atlanta</title>
    <title lang="ar">سي ياس تو ذا دراس: اطلنطا</title>
    <desc lang="en">Britt needs a dress fast while Shelby needs to find a dress that she likes in her size. Will they get what they want? تأتي النساء المخطوبات حديثاً من جميع أنحاء العالم إلى متجر فساتين الزفاف هذا لإيجاد الثوب المثالي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919130000" stop="20200919140000" channel="Star World HD">
    <title lang="en">The Resident</title>
    <title lang="ar">Star World HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dr Devon Pravesh meets the harsh truths of medical care on his first day as an intern; Conrad Hawkins trains him with unusual techniques of treating patients. في يومه الأول كمتدرب ، يواجه الدّكتور المثالي ديفون برافيش الواقع القاسي للرعاية الطبية ، حيث يضعه الطبيب المتمرس كونراد هوكينز تحت جناحه ويعلّمه طرقه غير التقليدية في علاج المرضى.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919140000" stop="20200919150000" channel="Star World HD">
    <title lang="en">The Greatest Dancer</title>
    <title lang="ar">Star World HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">The auditions featured in this episode include a troupe of contemporary performers dancing in blindfolds, Irish dancing with a twist, and a latin and ballroom real-life couple who leave the judges speechless. تضع أمام مشاهديها مجموعة متنوعة من البرامج العالمية والأفلام والمسلسلات الكوميدية الغربية. منها مجموعة من المسلسلات الشهيرة الحائزة على جوائز عالمية،.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919150000" stop="20200919160000" channel="Star World HD">
    <title lang="en">Battle Of The Fittest Couples</title>
    <title lang="ar">باتل أوف ذا فايتيست كوبلس</title>
    <desc lang="en">The competition heats up for the competitors. There is flow of shockwaves throughout the house which provokes the rivals as a new ally has been betrayed by one of the couples. تزداد حدة المنافسة على المتنافسين وتحدث اضطرابات كثيرة داخل المنزل عندما يقوم أحد الأزواج بخيانة حليف جيد له.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919160000" stop="20200919170000" channel="Star World HD">
    <title lang="en">Grey's Anatomy</title>
    <title lang="ar">غريز أناتومي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Meredith manipulates huge secrets that change her relations with Alex and Maggie. While Richard helps Jo with a decision, April and Catherine argue regarding the baby. عندما يصبح أحد أتباع غراي سلون مريضاً في المستشفى، يحاول بايلي معرفة الذي حدث. تعاني ميريديث من أسرار تؤثر على علاقتها مع أليكس وماغي، بينما يختلف كل من ابريل وكاثرين حول الطفل الجديد.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919170000" stop="20200919180000" channel="Star World HD">
    <title lang="en">Say Yes To The Dress: Atlanta</title>
    <title lang="ar">سي ياس تو ذا دراس: اطلنطا</title>
    <desc lang="en">A dramatic surprise may delay Kisha's walk to the altar; Consultant Becca tries to beat the clock and find a dress for Lindsey against all odds. تأتي النساء المخطوبات حديثاً من جميع أنحاء العالم إلى متجر فساتين الزفاف هذا لإيجاد الثوب المثالي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919180000" stop="20200919190000" channel="Star World HD">
    <title lang="en">Filthy Rich</title>
    <title lang="ar">فيلثي ريتش</title>
    <desc lang="en">Some fresh news lands Joe in quite a pickle, Savannah knows she can count on her supporters but wonders if she can be with her loved ones. تضع بعض الأخبار الجديدة جو في مأزق كبير  وتعلم سافانا أن بإمكانها الاعتماد على مؤيديها ولكنها تتساءل عما إذا كان بإمكانها أن تكون مع أحبائها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919190000" stop="20200919200000" channel="Star World HD">
    <title lang="en">Project Runway All Stars</title>
    <title lang="ar">بروجيكت رانواي اول ستارز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Using two colors, the contestants are asked to create elegant and sophisticated graduation party. يعود المصممون السابقون للمنافسة للحصول على فرصة أخرى ليكونوا فائزين في بروجكت رانواي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919200000" stop="20200919220000" channel="Star World HD">
    <title lang="en">Britain's Got Talent - The Champions</title>
    <title lang="ar">بريتنز غوت تالنت- ذا تشامبينز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Series 8 winners, singing group Collabro, take on sword swallower Alex Magala, the most dangerous act ever on the Got Talent franchise, and more. الفائزون بالسلسلة الثامنة، فرقة الغناء كولابرو في مواجهة مبتلع السيوف أليكس ماغالا وهو أخطر عرض في البرنامج بامتياز، وغيرها الكثير.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919020000" stop="20200919023000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Baking Good Baking Bad</title>
    <title lang="ar">بيكينغ غود بيكينغ باد</title>
    <desc lang="en">Paris, the city of light, love and food is the adopted home of British writer and cook Harry Eastwood. In this series, Harry takes us on a journey through her home city, showing us how to create the mouthwatering delights that find their home in the city's patisseries. تعتبر باريس مدينة النور والحب والطعام هي مصدر إلهام الكاتبة البريطانية والطاهية هاري إيستوود. تأخذنا هاري في رحلة عبر المدينة التي تقطنها لتعلمنا كيفية صنع ألذ المأكولات التي تجد طريقها إلى مخابز المدينة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919023000" stop="20200919030000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Sugar Showdown</title>
    <title lang="ar">شوغار شوداون</title>
    <desc lang="en">All things sweet and delicious are the centrepiece of this cooking competition series that awards one baker $10,000 every episode. تدور هذه المسابقة حول الحلويات والأطباق اللذيذة، حيث سيفوز أحد الخبّازين بـ 10000 دولار في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919030000" stop="20200919040000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Living On The Veg</title>
    <title lang="ar">ليفينغ أون ذا فيج</title>
    <desc lang="en">Vegan chefs Henry Firth and Ian Theasby cook up their favourite recipes showing just how accessible and tasty vegan cuisine can be. يقوم الطاهيان النباتيان هنري فيرث وأيان ثيسبي بطهو وصفاتهم المفضلة التي تظهر للمشاهدين كيف يمكن للخضروات فقط أن تصنع ألذ الأطباق على الإطلاق.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919040000" stop="20200919050000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Nadia's Family Feasts</title>
    <title lang="ar">نادياز فايميلي فيستس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Nadia Sawalha is taking inspiration from busy households around the world as she seeks new ideas for recipes that will fit into hectic schedules. Each week, Nadia is joined by a guest chef with a passion or expertise in that cuisine. تزور ناديا صوالحة الأسرالمزدحمة حول العالم لتستلهم الأفكار الجديدة للوصفات التي تتناسب مع الجداول الاجتماعية المزدحمة، كما وفي كل أسبوع ينضم إلى ناديا أحد الطهاة الخبراء.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919050000" stop="20200919053000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Step Up To The Plate</title>
    <title lang="ar">ستيب أب تو ذا بليت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Culinary Queen Allegra McEvedy and suave service star Fred Sirieix test eight contestants to discover if they have the skills to run their own restaurant. تابعوا ملكة المطبخ أليغرا مكفيدي والنجم فريد سيريكس وهما يختبران مهارات ثمانية متسابقين لاكتشاف قدرتهم على إدارة مطعمهم الخاص.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919053000" stop="20200919060000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Step Up To The Plate</title>
    <title lang="ar">ستيب أب تو ذا بليت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Culinary Queen Allegra McEvedy and suave service star Fred Sirieix test eight contestants to discover if they have the skills to run their own restaurant. تابعوا ملكة المطبخ أليغرا مكفيدي والنجم فريد سيريكس وهما يختبران مهارات ثمانية متسابقين لاكتشاف قدرتهم على إدارة مطعمهم الخاص.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919060000" stop="20200919070000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Fearless Chef</title>
    <title lang="ar">فيرلس تشيف</title>
    <desc lang="en">In a world where food is ever more processed and convenient, Kiran's mission is to discover fascinating natural ingredients and extreme methods of harvesting around the world. في عالم حيث يتوفر الغذاء بكميات أكثر من أي وقت مضى، تتمثل مهمة كيران في اكتشاف المكونات الطبيعية الرائعة والأساليب الفريدة من نوعها في الحصاد في جميع أنحاء العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919070000" stop="20200919073000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">DNA Dinners</title>
    <title lang="ar">دي إن ايه دينرز</title>
    <desc lang="en">DNA Dinners is a new series that explores the diverse heritages of 16 individuals as they discover their roots through DNA analysis and celebrate them through cooking. يكتشف برنامج دي إن ايه دينرز تراث وجذور المشاركين الستة عشر المتنوع  عند تحليل أحماضهم النووية، ويحتفل البرنامج بتراثهم من خلال طهي مأكولات الثقافات الجديدة التي ينتموا إليها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919073000" stop="20200919080000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">DNA Dinners</title>
    <title lang="ar">دي إن ايه دينرز</title>
    <desc lang="en">DNA Dinners is a new series that explores the diverse heritages of 16 individuals as they discover their roots through DNA analysis and celebrate them through cooking. يكتشف برنامج دي إن ايه دينرز تراث وجذور المشاركين الستة عشر المتنوع  عند تحليل أحماضهم النووية، ويحتفل البرنامج بتراثهم من خلال طهي مأكولات الثقافات الجديدة التي ينتموا إليها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919080000" stop="20200919083000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Broken Bread</title>
    <title lang="ar">بروكن بريد</title>
    <desc lang="en">Restaurant entrepreneur, social activist and acclaimed chef Roy Choi takes viewers on a journey through his hometown, the city of Los Angeles. This show is about inspiring people who are making a difference in their communities through food. نشاهد في هذا البرنامج الأشخاص الملهمين والذين يقومون بإحداث فرق إيجابي في مجتمعاتهم في مجال الطعام، حيث سيأخذنا متعهد المطاعم والناشط الإجتماعي روي تشوي في رحلة إلى مسقط رأسه، مدينة لوس أنجلوس.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919083000" stop="20200919090000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Sourced</title>
    <title lang="ar">سورسد</title>
    <desc lang="en">Green markets, fish markets, all the markets! Guy heads to Italy, Japan, and the California's Central Coast and discovers where some of the oldest, most sacred and freshest ingredients come from. السوق الأخضر، أسواق السمك وجميع الأسواق، يتجه غاي إلى إيطاليا واليابان وساحل كاليفورنيا المركزي ليكتشف من أين تأتي أكثر المنتجات الطازجة في العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919090000" stop="20200919093000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Baking Good Baking Bad</title>
    <title lang="ar">بيكينغ غود بيكينغ باد</title>
    <desc lang="en">Paris, the city of light, love and food is the adopted home of British writer and cook Harry Eastwood. In this series, Harry takes us on a journey through her home city, showing us how to create the mouthwatering delights that find their home in the city's patisseries. تعتبر باريس مدينة النور والحب والطعام هي مصدر إلهام الكاتبة البريطانية والطاهية هاري إيستوود. تأخذنا هاري في رحلة عبر المدينة التي تقطنها لتعلمنا كيفية صنع ألذ المأكولات التي تجد طريقها إلى مخابز المدينة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919093000" stop="20200919100000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Sugar Showdown</title>
    <title lang="ar">شوغار شوداون</title>
    <desc lang="en">All things sweet and delicious are the centrepiece of this cooking competition series that awards one baker $10,000 every episode. تدور هذه المسابقة حول الحلويات والأطباق اللذيذة، حيث سيفوز أحد الخبّازين بـ 10000 دولار في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919100000" stop="20200919103000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">The Travelling Chef</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا ترافيلينغ تشيف</title>
    <desc lang="en">Get ready to tuck in as Masterchef New Zealand winner, Chef Brett McGregor, travels the world in search of new flavours and experiences. Each location brings us people to meet, treasured recipes to learn and exciting ingredients to taste. استعد للوليمة الكبيرة بينما نسافر مع الشيف بريت ماكغروغر الفائز بمسابقة ماستر شيف نيوزيلاندا، للبحث عن النكهات الجديدة حول العالم. حيث يلتقي في كل بلدة  أشخاصاً جدد ويتعلم وصفات ذهبية و يتذوق مكونات شهية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919103000" stop="20200919110000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Rustic Adventures: Italy</title>
    <title lang="ar">راستيك أدفينشر: إيطاليا</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this hybrid food, travel and adventure show, two young chefs who have fulfilled their lifelong dream of owning successful restaurants, decide to take a much-needed break and seek out inspiration for new endeavours while on a rustic food tour across Italy. تابعوا في هذا البرنامج الغني بالطعام والسفر والمغامرة، رحلة الطاهيين الشابين اللذين استطاعا تحقيق حلمهما في إنشاء مطاعم ناجحة، وبينما هما على مشارف إجازتهما المنتظرة، يبحثان عن آفاق جديدة لاستكشاف الطعام الريفي في إيطاليا.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919110000" stop="20200919120000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Living On The Veg</title>
    <title lang="ar">ليفينغ أون ذا فيج</title>
    <desc lang="en">Vegan chefs Henry Firth and Ian Theasby cook up their favourite recipes showing just how accessible and tasty vegan cuisine can be. يقوم الطاهيان النباتيان هنري فيرث وأيان ثيسبي بطهو وصفاتهم المفضلة التي تظهر للمشاهدين كيف يمكن للخضروات فقط أن تصنع ألذ الأطباق على الإطلاق.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919120000" stop="20200919123000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Broken Bread</title>
    <title lang="ar">بروكن بريد</title>
    <desc lang="en">Restaurant entrepreneur, social activist and acclaimed chef Roy Choi takes viewers on a journey through his hometown, the city of Los Angeles. This show is about inspiring people who are making a difference in their communities through food. نشاهد في هذا البرنامج الأشخاص الملهمين والذين يقومون بإحداث فرق إيجابي في مجتمعاتهم في مجال الطعام، حيث سيأخذنا متعهد المطاعم والناشط الإجتماعي روي تشوي في رحلة إلى مسقط رأسه، مدينة لوس أنجلوس.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919123000" stop="20200919130000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Sourced</title>
    <title lang="ar">سورسد</title>
    <desc lang="en">Green markets, fish markets, all the markets! Guy heads to Italy, Japan, and the California's Central Coast and discovers where some of the oldest, most sacred and freshest ingredients come from. السوق الأخضر، أسواق السمك وجميع الأسواق، يتجه غاي إلى إيطاليا واليابان وساحل كاليفورنيا المركزي ليكتشف من أين تأتي أكثر المنتجات الطازجة في العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919130000" stop="20200919140000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Nadia's Family Feasts</title>
    <title lang="ar">نادياز فايميلي فيستس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Nadia Sawalha is taking inspiration from busy households around the world as she seeks new ideas for recipes that will fit into hectic schedules. Each week, Nadia is joined by a guest chef with a passion or expertise in that cuisine. تزور ناديا صوالحة الأسرالمزدحمة حول العالم لتستلهم الأفكار الجديدة للوصفات التي تتناسب مع الجداول الاجتماعية المزدحمة، كما وفي كل أسبوع ينضم إلى ناديا أحد الطهاة الخبراء.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919140000" stop="20200919143000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Step Up To The Plate</title>
    <title lang="ar">ستيب أب تو ذا بليت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Culinary Queen Allegra McEvedy and suave service star Fred Sirieix test eight contestants to discover if they have the skills to run their own restaurant. تابعوا ملكة المطبخ أليغرا مكفيدي والنجم فريد سيريكس وهما يختبران مهارات ثمانية متسابقين لاكتشاف قدرتهم على إدارة مطعمهم الخاص.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919143000" stop="20200919150000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Step Up To The Plate</title>
    <title lang="ar">ستيب أب تو ذا بليت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Culinary Queen Allegra McEvedy and suave service star Fred Sirieix test eight contestants to discover if they have the skills to run their own restaurant. تابعوا ملكة المطبخ أليغرا مكفيدي والنجم فريد سيريكس وهما يختبران مهارات ثمانية متسابقين لاكتشاف قدرتهم على إدارة مطعمهم الخاص.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919150000" stop="20200919153000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">The Travelling Chef</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا ترافيلينغ تشيف</title>
    <desc lang="en">Get ready to tuck in as Masterchef New Zealand winner, Chef Brett McGregor, travels the world in search of new flavours and experiences. Each location brings us people to meet, treasured recipes to learn and exciting ingredients to taste. استعد للوليمة الكبيرة بينما نسافر مع الشيف بريت ماكغروغر الفائز بمسابقة ماستر شيف نيوزيلاندا، للبحث عن النكهات الجديدة حول العالم. حيث يلتقي في كل بلدة  أشخاصاً جدد ويتعلم وصفات ذهبية و يتذوق مكونات شهية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919153000" stop="20200919160000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Rustic Adventures: Italy</title>
    <title lang="ar">راستيك أدفينشر: إيطاليا</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this hybrid food, travel and adventure show, two young chefs who have fulfilled their lifelong dream of owning successful restaurants, decide to take a much-needed break and seek out inspiration for new endeavours while on a rustic food tour across Italy. تابعوا في هذا البرنامج الغني بالطعام والسفر والمغامرة، رحلة الطاهيين الشابين اللذين استطاعا تحقيق حلمهما في إنشاء مطاعم ناجحة، وبينما هما على مشارف إجازتهما المنتظرة، يبحثان عن آفاق جديدة لاستكشاف الطعام الريفي في إيطاليا.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919160000" stop="20200919163000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Heritage</title>
    <title lang="ar">هيريتيج</title>
    <desc lang="en">The show introduces viewers to some of the country's most brilliant chefs. Come learn the personal stories behind chefs and what drives them, the flavors that inspire them, and the dreams they continue to work for. يقدم البرنامج بعض أكثر الطهاة تألقًا في البلاد. شاهدوا  قصص هؤلاء الطهاة وما الذي ساهم بنجاحهم وما الحافز الذي يقودهم في رحلة الطهو، والنكهات التي تلهمهم، والأحلام التي يواصلون العمل من أجلها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919163000" stop="20200919170000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Sara's Istanbul Delights</title>
    <title lang="ar">ساراز اسطنبول ديلايتس</title>
    <desc lang="en">World-renowned chef, food writer and designer Sara La Fountain goes on a gastronomic and cultural journey to discover Istanbul's rich culture and diverse tastes. تقوم كبيرة الطهاة المشهورة عالمياً، والكاتبة المختصة بالأغذية والمصممة سارة لا فاونتين، برحلة ثقافية ذواقة لاكتشاف ثقافة اسطنبول الغنية بالنكهات المتنوعة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919170000" stop="20200919173000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Broken Bread</title>
    <title lang="ar">بروكن بريد</title>
    <desc lang="en">Restaurant entrepreneur, social activist and acclaimed chef Roy Choi takes viewers on a journey through his hometown, the city of Los Angeles. This show is about inspiring people who are making a difference in their communities through food. نشاهد في هذا البرنامج الأشخاص الملهمين والذين يقومون بإحداث فرق إيجابي في مجتمعاتهم في مجال الطعام، حيث سيأخذنا متعهد المطاعم والناشط الإجتماعي روي تشوي في رحلة إلى مسقط رأسه، مدينة لوس أنجلوس.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919173000" stop="20200919180000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Sourced</title>
    <title lang="ar">سورسد</title>
    <desc lang="en">From Sicilian pistachios grown in the shadow of Mount Etna, to an epic feast under the California Redwoods Guy travels to some of the most visually stunning areas in the world to source and cook with amazing ingredients. من الفستق الصقلي الذي يُزرع في ظل جبل مونت إتنا، إلى الوليمة الملحمية تحت غابات ريدوود الشاهقة في كاليفورنيا، يسافر غاي غلى أكثر المناطق الذهلة في العالم ليجمع ويطهو أبدع وأبهى المكونات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919180000" stop="20200919190000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Nadia's Family Feasts</title>
    <title lang="ar">نادياز فايميلي فيستس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Nadia Sawalha is taking inspiration from busy households around the world as she seeks new ideas for recipes that will fit into hectic schedules. Each week, Nadia is joined by a guest chef with a passion or expertise in that cuisine. تزور ناديا صوالحة الأسرالمزدحمة حول العالم لتستلهم الأفكار الجديدة للوصفات التي تتناسب مع الجداول الاجتماعية المزدحمة، كما وفي كل أسبوع ينضم إلى ناديا أحد الطهاة الخبراء.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919190000" stop="20200919193000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Step Up To The Plate</title>
    <title lang="ar">ستيب أب تو ذا بليت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Culinary Queen Allegra McEvedy and suave service star Fred Sirieix test eight contestants to discover if they have the skills to run their own restaurant. تابعوا ملكة المطبخ أليغرا مكفيدي والنجم فريد سيريكس وهما يختبران مهارات ثمانية متسابقين لاكتشاف قدرتهم على إدارة مطعمهم الخاص.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919193000" stop="20200919200000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Step Up To The Plate</title>
    <title lang="ar">ستيب أب تو ذا بليت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Culinary Queen Allegra McEvedy and suave service star Fred Sirieix test eight contestants to discover if they have the skills to run their own restaurant. تابعوا ملكة المطبخ أليغرا مكفيدي والنجم فريد سيريكس وهما يختبران مهارات ثمانية متسابقين لاكتشاف قدرتهم على إدارة مطعمهم الخاص.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919200000" stop="20200919210000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">Fearless Chef</title>
    <title lang="ar">فيرلس تشيف</title>
    <desc lang="en">In a world where food is ever more processed and convenient, Kiran's mission is to discover fascinating natural ingredients and extreme methods of harvesting around the world. في عالم حيث يتوفر الغذاء بكميات أكثر من أي وقت مضى، تتمثل مهمة كيران في اكتشاف المكونات الطبيعية الرائعة والأساليب الفريدة من نوعها في الحصاد في جميع أنحاء العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919210000" stop="20200919213000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">DNA Dinners</title>
    <title lang="ar">دي إن ايه دينرز</title>
    <desc lang="en">DNA Dinners is a new series that explores the diverse heritages of 16 individuals as they discover their roots through DNA analysis and celebrate them through cooking. يكتشف برنامج دي إن ايه دينرز تراث وجذور المشاركين الستة عشر المتنوع  عند تحليل أحماضهم النووية، ويحتفل البرنامج بتراثهم من خلال طهي مأكولات الثقافات الجديدة التي ينتموا إليها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919213000" stop="20200919220000" channel="OSN Mezze">
    <title lang="en">DNA Dinners</title>
    <title lang="ar">دي إن ايه دينرز</title>
    <desc lang="en">DNA Dinners is a new series that explores the diverse heritages of 16 individuals as they discover their roots through DNA analysis and celebrate them through cooking. يكتشف برنامج دي إن ايه دينرز تراث وجذور المشاركين الستة عشر المتنوع  عند تحليل أحماضهم النووية، ويحتفل البرنامج بتراثهم من خلال طهي مأكولات الثقافات الجديدة التي ينتموا إليها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919022000" stop="20200919030500" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">90 Day Fianc?: The Other Way</title>
    <title lang="ar">90 داي فيانسي: ذا أذر ويه؟</title>
    <desc lang="en">Deavan tries to improve her relationship with Jihoon's mum. Tim has a troubling job interview, while Brittany and Yazan clash over her social media. يسافر رجال ونساء أمريكيون وقد وقعوا في حب أشخاص من الأراضي البعيدة إليهم لبدء حياتهم الزوجية في الخارج.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919030500" stop="20200919035000" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">90 Day Fianc?: The Other Way</title>
    <title lang="ar">90 داي فيانسي: ذا أذر ويه؟</title>
    <desc lang="en">Series favourites give their own juicy takes on previous episodes' drama from the comfort of their own home - and no-one is holding back! يسافر رجال ونساء أمريكيون وقد وقعوا في حب أشخاص من الأراضي البعيدة إليهم لبدء حياتهم الزوجية في الخارج.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919035000" stop="20200919043500" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">90 Day Fianc?: Before The 90 Days</title>
    <title lang="ar">90 ديز فيانسي: بيفور ذا 90 ديز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Fan favourites including "Big Ed. نتابع الأزواج الذين لم يلتقوا إلا عبر الانترنت، حيث نختبر رحلتهم بينما يقومون بالسفر إلى الدول الأجنبية لأول مرة في محاولة لبناء علاقة حقيقية وشخصية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919043500" stop="20200919050000" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">Say Yes To The Dress UK</title>
    <title lang="ar">ساي يس تو ذا دريس يو كاي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Anna's brought her sister to help but that might just be her downfall! She has a lot of opinions and none of them are good... or kind. إنضموا لمصصم فساتين الزفاف الملكية ديفيد إيمانيول في محل (كونفيتي آند ليس) للعرائس في إسيكس، حيث يقوم هو ومالكة المتجر كريستين داندو وفريقها بمساعدة العرائس في اختيار ثوب أحلامهم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919050000" stop="20200919054500" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">Married By Mum And Dad</title>
    <title lang="ar">ميرييد باي مام أند داد</title>
    <desc lang="en">Devin's parents find him a wife - but he has a history with the wedding planner. Tensions rise for Bethany and Marissa's dad takes his date to a gun range. يوافق الرجال والنساء، الذين لم يحالفهم الحظ في الحب، على وضع حياتهم العاطفية ومستقبلهم في أيدي آبائهم وأمهاتهم ليختاروا لهم شريك الحياة المناسب لهم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919054500" stop="20200919063000" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">Welcome To Plathville</title>
    <title lang="ar">ويلكوم تو بلاثفيل</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kim takes Moriah on her first college tour, Micah nearly jeopardises his career as a model before it's started. Plus, Moriah has some big news for the family. يعيش كيم وباري بلاث في جورجيا مع أولادهم التسعة. شاهدوا هذه العائلة المتحفظة التي لاتشاهد التلفاز وتدرّس أولادها في المنزل.. لكن كل هذا على وشك أن يتغير سريعاَ.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919063000" stop="20200919071500" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">Sister Wives</title>
    <title lang="ar">الضرائر</title>
    <desc lang="en">Valentine's Day proves to be awkward for a polygamist. Lastly, at Kody's birthday party, Mariah and her girlfriend show up with a major announcement! سننتقل من متابعة البنية الأسرية غير التقليدية وترتيبات المعيشة إلى التحديات المالية، تعرض كل حلقة الأعمال الداخلية للأسرة متعددة الزوجات، وتكشف عن التماسك الأسري غير المتوقع والمحبة الوطيدة بين زوجات كودي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919071500" stop="20200919074000" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">Cake Boss</title>
    <title lang="ar">كايك بوس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Buddy meets a floral-loving bride who wants bouquets of flower cupcakes. Plus, has romantic plans for his 25th wedding anniversary with Madeline! يشهد مشروع مخبز كارلوز بيكاري في هوبوكن، نيوجيرسي، المملوك لأسرة بادي فالاسترو إزدهاراً كبيراً ومن المؤكد أن يصبح أكثر انشغالًا بعد إلقاء المشاهدين نظرة داخل المخبز حول الطريقة التي يقوم فيها بادي وعائلته بتحضير الآلاف من قوالب الحلوى الخاصة بالزفاف والمعجنات كل أسبوع.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919074000" stop="20200919080000" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">Cake Boss</title>
    <title lang="ar">كايك بوس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Buddy flaunts his dance moves when he designs a flamenco cake. Meanwhile, Mauro and the team make a cake for a nearby summer camp, and it gets messy! طلب من بودي إعداد كعكة تحت إسم "ناسداك"، وكالة تبادل الأوراق المالية الأمريكية، وأخرى لمجلة "أوو" في نفس الأسبوع. ويريد ابن العم أنتوني أن يتخلى عن وظيفته كسائق وتعلم إعداد الكعك ولكن يجب عليه إيجاد بديل له.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919080000" stop="20200919082500" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">Cake Boss</title>
    <title lang="ar">كايك بوس</title>
    <desc lang="en">The team creates a cake to mark an event for the Mayor of Newark providing school supplies for kids. Madeline makes a rainbow cake for a charity run! طلب من بودي صنع كعكة حفلة زفاف لأربعة عشرة ثنائي يتزوجون معا في عيد الحب. كما طلب العم أنتوني من أحد الموظفات في المحل بأن تكون برفقته في عيد الحب.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919082500" stop="20200919095500" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">My 600-Lb Life</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماي 600-إل بي لايف</title>
    <desc lang="en">Seana is 23 and nearly 700-lbs, living at her mum's house, depressed and anxious. Dr. Now can give her the tools she needs to live, but only she can save herself. نتابع حياة مجموعة من الأشخاص والذين يزن كل منهم أكثر من 600 رطل، خلال رحلتهم الطويلة وصراعهم الطويل لخسارة الوزن بشكل جماعي من أجل المحافظة على صحتهم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919095500" stop="20200919104000" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">Counting On</title>
    <title lang="ar">كاونتينغ أون</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jana and Jessa organise a Christmas pageant, and the whole family helps! In LA, Jinger and Jeremy cut down their first live Christmas tree together. تابعوا أبناء عائلة داغيرز بينما يحتفلون بلحظات مميزة في حياتهم. فها هم قد نضجوا واستقروا مع عائلاتهم لينطلقوا في رحلتهم الخاصة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919104000" stop="20200919112500" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">Counting On</title>
    <title lang="ar">كاونتينغ أون</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jinger and Jeremy share devastating news. In Arkansas, Ben has second thoughts as he undergoes eye surgery. Later, Jeremy throws Jinger a surprise party! تابعوا أبناء عائلة داغيرز بينما يحتفلون بلحظات مميزة في حياتهم. فها هم قد نضجوا واستقروا مع عائلاتهم لينطلقوا في رحلتهم الخاصة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919112500" stop="20200919121000" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">Sister Wives</title>
    <title lang="ar">الضرائر</title>
    <desc lang="en">Valentine's Day proves to be awkward for a polygamist. Lastly, at Kody's birthday party, Mariah and her girlfriend show up with a major announcement! سننتقل من متابعة البنية الأسرية غير التقليدية وترتيبات المعيشة إلى التحديات المالية، تعرض كل حلقة الأعمال الداخلية للأسرة متعددة الزوجات، وتكشف عن التماسك الأسري غير المتوقع والمحبة الوطيدة بين زوجات كودي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919121000" stop="20200919125500" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">Darcey &amp; Stacey</title>
    <title lang="ar">دارسي آند ستيسي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Legendary identical twin sisters Darcey and Stacey Silva embark on a new chapter together. The sisters expand their business, follow their hearts and reconnect with family. قناة عن أنماط الحياة تعرض أفضل البرامج الواقعية والترفيه الهادف. بالإضافة إلى أجمل الفقرات من قناة أوبرا وبنفري نيتوورك.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919125500" stop="20200919132000" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">Say Yes To The Dress UK</title>
    <title lang="ar">ساي يس تو ذا دريس يو كاي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Picky wedding planner Becky seeks the ultimate dress - will a shimmering fishtail impress? And perfectionist Denise aims to find her dream gown. إنضموا لمصصم فساتين الزفاف الملكية ديفيد إيمانيول في محل (كونفيتي آند ليس) للعرائس في إسيكس، حيث يقوم هو ومالكة المتجر كريستين داندو وفريقها بمساعدة العرائس في اختيار ثوب أحلامهم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919132000" stop="20200919134500" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">Say Yes To The Dress UK</title>
    <title lang="ar">ساي يس تو ذا دريس يو كاي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Bride Hetty's alopecia affected her confidence and she wants a simple, elegant dress to flatter her figure. And Hannah seeks a tight-fitting fishtail frock. إنضموا لمصصم فساتين الزفاف الملكية ديفيد إيمانيول في محل (كونفيتي آند ليس) للعرائس في إسيكس، حيث يقوم هو ومالكة المتجر كريستين داندو وفريقها بمساعدة العرائس في اختيار ثوب أحلامهم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919134500" stop="20200919141000" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">Say Yes To The Dress UK</title>
    <title lang="ar">ساي يس تو ذا دريس يو كاي</title>
    <desc lang="en">18-year old Isobel wants a gown that is both mature and elegant, but when her choices push the envelope, her entourage has other ideas. إنضموا لمصصم فساتين الزفاف الملكية ديفيد إيمانيول في محل (كونفيتي آند ليس) للعرائس في إسيكس، حيث يقوم هو ومالكة المتجر كريستين داندو وفريقها بمساعدة العرائس في اختيار ثوب أحلامهم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919141000" stop="20200919143500" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">Say Yes To The Dress UK</title>
    <title lang="ar">ساي يس تو ذا دريس يو كاي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jade and Molly do everything together, including shopping for their upcoming weddings! Kimberley wants something elegant and unique for her big day. إنضموا لمصصم فساتين الزفاف الملكية ديفيد إيمانيول في محل (كونفيتي آند ليس) للعرائس في إسيكس، حيث يقوم هو ومالكة المتجر كريستين داندو وفريقها بمساعدة العرائس في اختيار ثوب أحلامهم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919143500" stop="20200919150000" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">Say Yes To The Dress UK</title>
    <title lang="ar">ساي يس تو ذا دريس يو كاي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Helen postponed her wedding after having a baby, now she's ready to find her perfect gown. Rebecca worries about her dress fitting after losing weight. إنضموا لمصصم فساتين الزفاف الملكية ديفيد إيمانيول في محل (كونفيتي آند ليس) للعرائس في إسيكس، حيث يقوم هو ومالكة المتجر كريستين داندو وفريقها بمساعدة العرائس في اختيار ثوب أحلامهم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919150000" stop="20200919155000" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">90 Day Fianc?: The Other Way</title>
    <title lang="ar">90 داي فيانسي: ذا أذر ويه؟</title>
    <desc lang="en">Deavan tries to improve her relationship with Jihoon's mum. Tim has a troubling job interview, while Brittany and Yazan clash over her social media. يسافر رجال ونساء أمريكيون وقد وقعوا في حب أشخاص من الأراضي البعيدة إليهم لبدء حياتهم الزوجية في الخارج.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919155000" stop="20200919164000" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">90 Days To Wed: Before The 90 Days</title>
    <title lang="ar">90 ديز تو ويد: بيفور ذا 90 ديز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Larry fails to contact Jenny on his journey to the Philippines. Cortney hopes Antonio will be at the airport. Sean makes a shocking discovery about Abby's ex. نتابع الأزواج الذين لم يلتقوا إلا عبر الانترنت، حيث نختبر رحلتهم بينما يقومون بالسفر إلى الدول الأجنبية لأول مرة في محاولة لبناء علاقة حقيقية وشخصية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919164000" stop="20200919173000" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">90 Days To Wed: Before The 90 Days</title>
    <title lang="ar">90 ديز تو ويد: بيفور ذا 90 ديز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Whilst Paul worries about Katrine's test results, Courtney questions Antonio's loyalty. Plus, Myriam has some unexpected news that could jeopardise Patrick's trip. نتابع الأزواج الذين لم يلتقوا إلا عبر الانترنت، حيث نختبر رحلتهم بينما يقومون بالسفر إلى الدول الأجنبية لأول مرة في محاولة لبناء علاقة حقيقية وشخصية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919173000" stop="20200919182000" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">90 Days To Wed: Before The 90 Days</title>
    <title lang="ar">90 ديز تو ويد: بيفور ذا 90 ديز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Darcey and Jesse's dispute spirals. Larry questions Jenny's past on his first day in Manila. Patrick must make a big decision in Paris after Myriam's bombshell. نتابع الأزواج الذين لم يلتقوا إلا عبر الانترنت، حيث نختبر رحلتهم بينما يقومون بالسفر إلى الدول الأجنبية لأول مرة في محاولة لبناء علاقة حقيقية وشخصية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919182000" stop="20200919191000" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">90 Days To Wed: Before The 90 Days</title>
    <title lang="ar">90 ديز تو ويد: بيفور ذا 90 ديز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Sean meets Abby's ex in an emotional showdown. Jesse and Darcey hit breaking point. Paul reveals a big secret to Karine, leading to a dangerous encounter in Brazil. نتابع الأزواج الذين لم يلتقوا إلا عبر الانترنت، حيث نختبر رحلتهم بينما يقومون بالسفر إلى الدول الأجنبية لأول مرة في محاولة لبناء علاقة حقيقية وشخصية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919191000" stop="20200919200000" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">90 Days To Wed: Before The 90 Days</title>
    <title lang="ar">90 ديز تو ويد: بيفور ذا 90 ديز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Larry wants to confront Jenny about her recent activity on a dating site, but cultural differences cause bigger problems. And, Patrick and Myriam meet for sightseeing. نتابع الأزواج الذين لم يلتقوا إلا عبر الانترنت، حيث نختبر رحلتهم بينما يقومون بالسفر إلى الدول الأجنبية لأول مرة في محاولة لبناء علاقة حقيقية وشخصية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919200000" stop="20200919205000" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">90 Day Fianc?: The Other Way</title>
    <title lang="ar">90 داي فيانسي: ذا أذر ويه؟</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ari hits breaking point. Elicia doesn't want to leave Korea without Deavan. Armando prepares for Kenny and his family to meet, and Brittany is still lying to Yazan. يسافر رجال ونساء أمريكيون وقد وقعوا في حب أشخاص من الأراضي البعيدة إليهم لبدء حياتهم الزوجية في الخارج.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919205000" stop="20200919214000" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">90 Day Fianc?: The Other Way</title>
    <title lang="ar">90 داي فيانسي: ذا أذر ويه؟</title>
    <desc lang="en">Series favourites give their own juicy takes on previous episodes' drama from the comfort of their own home - and no-one is holding back! يسافر رجال ونساء أمريكيون وقد وقعوا في حب أشخاص من الأراضي البعيدة إليهم لبدء حياتهم الزوجية في الخارج.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919214000" stop="20200919223000" channel="TLC HD">
    <title lang="en">90 Day Fianc?: Before The 90 Days</title>
    <title lang="ar">90 ديز فيانسي: بيفور ذا 90 ديز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Fan favourites from the latest season watch previous episodes, then respond to comments from the Pillow Talk cast, and the internet's most buzzworthy tweets! نتابع الأزواج الذين لم يلتقوا إلا عبر الانترنت، حيث نختبر رحلتهم بينما يقومون بالسفر إلى الدول الأجنبية لأول مرة في محاولة لبناء علاقة حقيقية وشخصية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919020000" stop="20200919030000" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">Very Cavallari</title>
    <title lang="ar">فيري كافالاري</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kristin and Jay have moved into their new home with chickens and goats, and Kristin agrees to babysit her friend's llama. تعود كريستين كافالري في الموسم الثالث، حيث تحاول موازنة عملها كأم وزوجة وسيدة أعمال مع زوجها الذي يقف معها دائماً، تعمل كريستين بلا كلل أو ملل لافتتاح متجرها الثاني في شيكاغو (أنكامن جيمس) ويصبح جاي في ناشفيل مصدر دعم كبير لعائلته.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919030000" stop="20200919040000" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">Very Cavallari</title>
    <title lang="ar">فيري كافالاري</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kristin balances business and pleasure as she heads out of town to Palm Springs for a UJ campaign shoot. تعود كريستين كافالري في الموسم الثالث، حيث تحاول موازنة عملها كأم وزوجة وسيدة أعمال مع زوجها الذي يقف معها دائماً، تعمل كريستين بلا كلل أو ملل لافتتاح متجرها الثاني في شيكاغو (أنكامن جيمس) ويصبح جاي في ناشفيل مصدر دعم كبير لعائلته.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919040000" stop="20200919050000" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">Flip It Like Disick</title>
    <title lang="ar">فليب إت لايك ديسيك</title>
    <desc lang="en">While helping his friend Steve Aoki with a room remodel in his Las Vegas mansion, Scott sets out to find his next major flip investment opportunity. يقوم سكوت ديسيك وفريقه بمشاريع تصميم الديكور للعقارات الفاخرة في لوس أنجلس، كما يقومون بمشاريع تحويل جذري لتصاميم منازل أصدقائهم المشاهير.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919050000" stop="20200919060000" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">Flip It Like Disick</title>
    <title lang="ar">فليب إت لايك ديسيك</title>
    <desc lang="en">With Jed Smith officially purchased and the new layout for the property agreed upon, Scott is eager to get started with demo right away. يقوم سكوت ديسيك وفريقه بمشاريع تصميم الديكور للعقارات الفاخرة في لوس أنجلس، كما يقومون بمشاريع تحويل جذري لتصاميم منازل أصدقائهم المشاهير.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919060000" stop="20200919070000" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">Flip It Like Disick</title>
    <title lang="ar">فليب إت لايك ديسيك</title>
    <desc lang="en">After visiting a mega-flip property being built by Scott's real-estate mentor, Ilan, Scott is inspired to redo the pool at his personal residence. يقوم سكوت ديسيك وفريقه بمشاريع تصميم الديكور للعقارات الفاخرة في لوس أنجلس، كما يقومون بمشاريع تحويل جذري لتصاميم منازل أصدقائهم المشاهير.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919070000" stop="20200919075500" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">Flip It Like Disick</title>
    <title lang="ar">فليب إت لايك ديسيك</title>
    <desc lang="en">With Miki feeling disrespected and a potential HOA shutdown looming, the team now faces major personal and logistical problems. يقوم سكوت ديسيك وفريقه بمشاريع تصميم الديكور للعقارات الفاخرة في لوس أنجلس، كما يقومون بمشاريع تحويل جذري لتصاميم منازل أصدقائهم المشاهير.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919075500" stop="20200919082000" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">E! News: Daily Pop</title>
    <title lang="ar">إي! نيوز: ديلي بوب</title>
    <desc lang="en">Daily Pop is the daytime destination for live entertainment talk - the place for fun conversations about the top pop culture stories of the day. من إي! نيوز، يحتل ديلي بوب الفترة الصباحية ليصبح وجهة لعشاق الترفيه. المزيد من أخبار إي!، المزيد من المتعة، والمزيد من المرح!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919082000" stop="20200919085000" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">E! News: Daily Pop</title>
    <title lang="ar">إي! نيوز: ديلي بوب</title>
    <desc lang="en">Daily Pop is the daytime destination for live entertainment talk - the place for fun conversations about the top pop culture stories of the day. من إي! نيوز، يحتل ديلي بوب الفترة الصباحية ليصبح وجهة لعشاق الترفيه. المزيد من أخبار إي!، المزيد من المتعة، والمزيد من المرح!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919085000" stop="20200919094500" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">Flip It Like Disick</title>
    <title lang="ar">فليب إت لايك ديسيك</title>
    <desc lang="en">The team races to complete Jed Smith in order to get it listed and sold by the end of summer. Scott and his Sofia Richie look to buy a house together. يقوم سكوت ديسيك وفريقه بمشاريع تصميم الديكور للعقارات الفاخرة في لوس أنجلس، كما يقومون بمشاريع تحويل جذري لتصاميم منازل أصدقائهم المشاهير.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919094500" stop="20200919104000" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">Keeping Up With The Kardashians</title>
    <title lang="ar">كيبينغ أب ويذ ذا كارديشيانز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kris has had it with Scott when he brokers a Vegas nightclub appearance for her birthday, then shows up to it wasted and belligerent. ينفذ صبر كريس تجاه سكوت عندما يقوم بالترتيب للظهور في أحد نوادي لاس فيغاس بمناسبة عيد ميلادها، ثم يحضر وهو في حالة ثمالة وعدائية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919104000" stop="20200919113500" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">Keeping Up With The Kardashians</title>
    <title lang="ar">كيبينغ أب ويذ ذا كارديشيانز</title>
    <desc lang="en">A security breach motivates Kris to step up security. Scott goes to a Lord Disick party in Vegas while Kourtney finds out the baby could come early. اختراق أمني يحفز كريس على تحديث نظام الحراسة الأمني. ينطلق سكوت لحضور حفلة لورد ديسيك في لاس فيغاس بينما تكتشف كورتني أن موعد الولادة قد يأتي مبكراً.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919113500" stop="20200919123000" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">Keeping Up With The Kardashians</title>
    <title lang="ar">كيبينغ أب ويذ ذا كارديشيانز</title>
    <desc lang="en">The birth of his third child sends Scott spiraling, and Khloe enlists Bruce to help bring Scott back down to earth. Kanye shoots a video with North. ولادة طفله الثالث يصيب سكوت بحالة من الكآبة، وهو ما يدفع كلوي لطلب المساعدة من بروس. يقوم كانييه بتصوير مقطع فيديو برفقته طفلته نورث.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919123000" stop="20200919132500" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">Keeping Up With The Kardashians</title>
    <title lang="ar">كيبينغ أب ويذ ذا كارديشيانز</title>
    <desc lang="en">The media starts prying into Kylie's beauty secrets and she realizes she must address her new look. Scott hires Kourtney as an interior designer. تبدأ وسائل الإعلام بتناول أسرار جمال كيلي مما يدفعها لإدراك أهمية الافصاح عن سر مظهرها الجديد. تعمل كيرتني كمصممة ديكور داخلي لصالح سكوت.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919132500" stop="20200919135000" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">E! News: Daily Pop</title>
    <title lang="ar">إي! نيوز: ديلي بوب</title>
    <desc lang="en">Daily Pop is the daytime destination for live entertainment talk - the place for fun conversations about the top pop culture stories of the day. من إي! نيوز، يحتل ديلي بوب الفترة الصباحية ليصبح وجهة لعشاق الترفيه. المزيد من أخبار إي!، المزيد من المتعة، والمزيد من المرح!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919135000" stop="20200919142000" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">E! News: Daily Pop</title>
    <title lang="ar">إي! نيوز: ديلي بوب</title>
    <desc lang="en">Daily Pop is the daytime destination for live entertainment talk - the place for fun conversations about the top pop culture stories of the day. من إي! نيوز، يحتل ديلي بوب الفترة الصباحية ليصبح وجهة لعشاق الترفيه. المزيد من أخبار إي!، المزيد من المتعة، والمزيد من المرح!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919142000" stop="20200919151500" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">Keeping Up With The Kardashians</title>
    <title lang="ar">كيبينغ أب ويذ ذا كارديشيانز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kim needs to deliver earlier than planned, Kris prepares the house for her granddaughter's arrival, and Khloe tries to make peace with what's happening in her life. يتعين على كيم الدخول في المخاض قبل الموعد المقرر، تقوم كريس بتجهيز المنزل بانتظار حفيدتها المرتقبة، بينما تحاول كلوي التأقلم مع مجريات حياتها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919151500" stop="20200919154000" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">10 Things You Don't Know</title>
    <title lang="ar">10 ثينغز يو دونت نو</title>
    <desc lang="en">The most unbelievable, surprising, and OMG things about Brad Pitt, from his steamiest movie scenes to his shocking pre-fame jobs. عرض سريع الخطى يكشف عن التفاصيل والقصص والأسرار الأكثر جنونًا وغموضًا حول المشاهير المفضلين لديك.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919154000" stop="20200919161000" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">10 Things You Don't Know</title>
    <title lang="ar">10 ثينغز يو دونت نو</title>
    <desc lang="en">The most unbelievable, surprising, and OMG things about J. Lo, from how she prepared for 'Hustlers' to how she changed the internet forever. عرض سريع الخطى يكشف عن التفاصيل والقصص والأسرار الأكثر جنونًا وغموضًا حول المشاهير المفضلين لديك.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919161000" stop="20200919163500" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">10 Things You Don't Know</title>
    <title lang="ar">10 ثينغز يو دونت نو</title>
    <desc lang="en">The most unbelievable, surprising, and OMG things about Tiffany Haddish, from the celebrity that changed her life to a crazy job she had pre-fame. عرض سريع الخطى يكشف عن التفاصيل والقصص والأسرار الأكثر جنونًا وغموضًا حول المشاهير المفضلين لديك.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919163500" stop="20200919170500" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">10 Things You Don't Know</title>
    <title lang="ar">10 ثينغز يو دونت نو</title>
    <desc lang="en">The most unbelievable, surprising, and OMG things about Keanu Reeves, from the story behind his famous name to where all of his 'Matrix' money went. عرض سريع الخطى يكشف عن التفاصيل والقصص والأسرار الأكثر جنونًا وغموضًا حول المشاهير المفضلين لديك.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919170500" stop="20200919180000" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">Hollywood Medium With Tyler Henry</title>
    <title lang="ar">هوليوود ميديوم ويذ تايلر هنري</title>
    <desc lang="en">In NYC, with Tyler's help, a famous friend reaches out from beyond the grave to Carole Radziwill, giving Carole the closure she has longed for. في نيويورك سيتي، وبمساعدة من تيلور، يتواصل صديق سابق وهو من المشاهير مع كارول رادزويل، وهو ما يمنحها خاتمة ملائمة لطالما سعت خلفها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919180000" stop="20200919190000" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">Hollywood Medium With Tyler Henry</title>
    <title lang="ar">هوليوود ميديوم ويذ تايلر هنري</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tyler uncovers a family mystery with Audrina Patridge, while Moby is shocked when Tyler offers him very specific details from his deceased mother. تايلر هو منجم عمره 19 عاماً، لا تقتصر قدراته على التواصل مع الأرواح وقراءة المستقبل فقط، بل يستطيع تشخيص الحالة الصحية للأفراد.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919190000" stop="20200919200000" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">Very Cavallari</title>
    <title lang="ar">فيري كافالاري</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kristin embarks on another glamorous trip to Los Angeles for the Emmys, bringing Jay along as her LaLa Land sidekick. تعود كريستين كافالري في الموسم الثالث، حيث تحاول موازنة عملها كأم وزوجة وسيدة أعمال مع زوجها الذي يقف معها دائماً، تعمل كريستين بلا كلل أو ملل لافتتاح متجرها الثاني في شيكاغو (أنكامن جيمس) ويصبح جاي في ناشفيل مصدر دعم كبير لعائلته.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919200000" stop="20200919210000" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">Very Cavallari</title>
    <title lang="ar">فيري كافالاري</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kristin and Jay take their friends on a wild camping trip. Jay is at home in the wilderness, while everyone else feels like a fish out of water. تعود كريستين كافالري في الموسم الثالث، حيث تحاول موازنة عملها كأم وزوجة وسيدة أعمال مع زوجها الذي يقف معها دائماً، تعمل كريستين بلا كلل أو ملل لافتتاح متجرها الثاني في شيكاغو (أنكامن جيمس) ويصبح جاي في ناشفيل مصدر دعم كبير لعائلته.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919210000" stop="20200919213000" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">The Soup</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا سوب</title>
    <desc lang="en">The evolved and supercharged series will feature Jade Catta-Preta's irreverent sense of humour and sharp point-of-view of the entertainment world. نظرة على أهم أخبار المشاهير وأروع مقاطع الفيديو لهذا الأسبوع.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919213000" stop="20200919220000" channel="E! Entertainment HD">
    <title lang="en">Celebrity Call Centre</title>
    <title lang="ar">سيليبريتي كول سنتر</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Bella Twins, Reza Farahan, Lauren Ash and Trixie Mattel field phone calls and speak to real people seeking their advice. آخر ما قيل ويقال من أخبار النجوم وتقليعات الوسط الفني مباشرة من هوليوود، عاصمة الترفيه في العالم أجمع.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919020000" stop="20200919030000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">Undiscovered Vistas</title>
    <title lang="ar">أنديسكوفرد فيستاس</title>
    <desc lang="en">An awe-inspiring journey to some of the most beautiful places in the world. Across the globe lie a number of little-known, breathtaking natural settings. Get acquainted with these areas of outstanding natural beauty, their wildlife, and the forces that shape them. نتابع في هذا البرنامج الرحلة المذهلة إلى أحد أجمل المناطق في العالم. حيث تكمن العديد من الأماكن غير المعروفة والتي تخطف الأنفاس.، تعرف على هذه الطبيعة الخلابة، حياتها البرية والقوى الطبيعية التي أدت إلى تشكل تلك التضاريس.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919030000" stop="20200919040000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">Trading Spaces</title>
    <title lang="ar">تريدينغ سبيسيز</title>
    <desc lang="en">This show pits neighbor against neighbor in a race to redecorate a room in each-other's homes. Can a friendship survive this weekend? يتبارى في هذا البرنامج الجار ضد جاره للقيام بتصميم وترتيب غرفةً واحدة في منزل الآخر. هل ستصمد الصداقة بعد ذلك السباق؟.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919040000" stop="20200919050000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">Brilliant Corners</title>
    <title lang="ar">بريليانت كورنرز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brilliant Corners is a dynamic new adventure series presented by travel writer, explorer and former European Longboard surfing champion, Sam Bleakley. شاهدوا مسلسل المغامرات الجديد الذي يقدمه لنا كاتب السفريات والمستكشف والبطل السابق للتزلج على الأمواج ، سام بليكلي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919050000" stop="20200919060000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <title lang="ar">أنثوني بوردين : بارتس أناون</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join world-renowned chef, bestselling author and multiple Emmy-winning television personality Anthony Bourdain as he travels across the globe to uncover little-known destinations and diverse cultures. انضموا إلى الشيف الأكثر شهرة في العالم والمؤلف صاحب الكتب الأكثر مبيعاً والحائز على جائزة إيمي أنتوني بوردين بينما يسافر حول العالم للكشف عن الوجهات غير المعروفة والثقافات المتنوعة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919060000" stop="20200919070000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">Undiscovered Vistas</title>
    <title lang="ar">أنديسكوفرد فيستاس</title>
    <desc lang="en">An awe-inspiring journey to some of the most beautiful places in the world. Across the globe lie a number of little-known, breathtaking natural settings. Get acquainted with these areas of outstanding natural beauty, their wildlife, and the forces that shape them. نتابع في هذا البرنامج الرحلة المذهلة إلى أحد أجمل المناطق في العالم. حيث تكمن العديد من الأماكن غير المعروفة والتي تخطف الأنفاس.، تعرف على هذه الطبيعة الخلابة، حياتها البرية والقوى الطبيعية التي أدت إلى تشكل تلك التضاريس.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919070000" stop="20200919073000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">Top Million Dollar Agent</title>
    <title lang="ar">توب ميليون دولار أيجنت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Reality show focusing on luxury real estate around the world. Each episode features a couple looking for a knockout property, aided by top real estate agents. After touring four multi-million dollar properties, the couple has to choose which home is the perfect fit. يتمحور هذا البرنامج الواقعي حول العقارات الفاخرة وحياة الرفاهية حول العالم. ففي كل حلقة نتابع زوجين وهما يبحثان عن عقار لامثيل له، بمساعدة أكبر وكلاء العقارات. وبعد إلقائهم نظرة على أربع عقارات تساوي ملايين الدولارات، على الزوجين اختيار الأنسب لهما للعيش فيه.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919073000" stop="20200919080000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">Top Million Dollar Agent</title>
    <title lang="ar">توب ميليون دولار أيجنت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Reality show focusing on luxury real estate around the world. Each episode features a couple looking for a knockout property, aided by top real estate agents. After touring four multi-million dollar properties, the couple has to choose which home is the perfect fit. يتمحور هذا البرنامج الواقعي حول العقارات الفاخرة وحياة الرفاهية حول العالم. ففي كل حلقة نتابع زوجين وهما يبحثان عن عقار لامثيل له، بمساعدة أكبر وكلاء العقارات. وبعد إلقائهم نظرة على أربع عقارات تساوي ملايين الدولارات، على الزوجين اختيار الأنسب لهما للعيش فيه.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919080000" stop="20200919090000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">Brilliant Corners</title>
    <title lang="ar">بريليانت كورنرز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brilliant Corners is a dynamic new adventure series presented by travel writer, explorer and former European Longboard surfing champion, Sam Bleakley. شاهدوا مسلسل المغامرات الجديد الذي يقدمه لنا كاتب السفريات والمستكشف والبطل السابق للتزلج على الأمواج ، سام بليكلي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919090000" stop="20200919100000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <title lang="ar">أنثوني بوردين : بارتس أناون</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join world-renowned chef, bestselling author and multiple Emmy-winning television personality Anthony Bourdain as he travels across the globe to uncover little-known destinations and diverse cultures. انضموا إلى الشيف الأكثر شهرة في العالم والمؤلف صاحب الكتب الأكثر مبيعاً والحائز على جائزة إيمي أنتوني بوردين بينما يسافر حول العالم للكشف عن الوجهات غير المعروفة والثقافات المتنوعة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919100000" stop="20200919110000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">Trading Spaces</title>
    <title lang="ar">تريدينغ سبيسيز</title>
    <desc lang="en">This show pits neighbor against neighbor in a race to redecorate a room in each-other's homes. Can a friendship survive this weekend? يتبارى في هذا البرنامج الجار ضد جاره للقيام بتصميم وترتيب غرفةً واحدة في منزل الآخر. هل ستصمد الصداقة بعد ذلك السباق؟.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919110000" stop="20200919120000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">Undiscovered Vistas</title>
    <title lang="ar">أنديسكوفرد فيستاس</title>
    <desc lang="en">An awe-inspiring journey to some of the most beautiful places in the world. Across the globe lie a number of little-known, breathtaking natural settings. Get acquainted with these areas of outstanding natural beauty, their wildlife, and the forces that shape them. نتابع في هذا البرنامج الرحلة المذهلة إلى أحد أجمل المناطق في العالم. حيث تكمن العديد من الأماكن غير المعروفة والتي تخطف الأنفاس.، تعرف على هذه الطبيعة الخلابة، حياتها البرية والقوى الطبيعية التي أدت إلى تشكل تلك التضاريس.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919120000" stop="20200919123000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">Top Million Dollar Agent</title>
    <title lang="ar">توب ميليون دولار أيجنت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Reality show focusing on luxury real estate around the world. Each episode features a couple looking for a knockout property, aided by top real estate agents. After touring four multi-million dollar properties, the couple has to choose which home is the perfect fit. يتمحور هذا البرنامج الواقعي حول العقارات الفاخرة وحياة الرفاهية حول العالم. ففي كل حلقة نتابع زوجين وهما يبحثان عن عقار لامثيل له، بمساعدة أكبر وكلاء العقارات. وبعد إلقائهم نظرة على أربع عقارات تساوي ملايين الدولارات، على الزوجين اختيار الأنسب لهما للعيش فيه.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919123000" stop="20200919130000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">Top Million Dollar Agent</title>
    <title lang="ar">توب ميليون دولار أيجنت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Reality show focusing on luxury real estate around the world. Each episode features a couple looking for a knockout property, aided by top real estate agents. After touring four multi-million dollar properties, the couple has to choose which home is the perfect fit. يتمحور هذا البرنامج الواقعي حول العقارات الفاخرة وحياة الرفاهية حول العالم. ففي كل حلقة نتابع زوجين وهما يبحثان عن عقار لامثيل له، بمساعدة أكبر وكلاء العقارات. وبعد إلقائهم نظرة على أربع عقارات تساوي ملايين الدولارات، على الزوجين اختيار الأنسب لهما للعيش فيه.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919130000" stop="20200919140000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">The Apartment</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا أبارتمنت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Under the watchful eyes of international design superstar Laurence Llewelyn-Bowen, dozens of passionate amateurs brave tight budgets and exacting time frames as they attempt to create stunning rooms in one-of-a-kind developments in Asia's biggest design reality show. سيقوم المُصمم المشهور لورانس ليفلن- بوين بتقديم أكبر معرض تصميم واقعيّ في العالم و الذي يحاول من خلاله عشرات من الهواة الشجعان تصميم و إبتكارغرف مذهلة في مشاريع فريدة من نوعها بميزانيات مالية ضئيلة وفترات زمنية قليلة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919140000" stop="20200919150000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">Brilliant Corners</title>
    <title lang="ar">بريليانت كورنرز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brilliant Corners is a dynamic new adventure series presented by travel writer, explorer and former European Longboard surfing champion, Sam Bleakley. شاهدوا مسلسل المغامرات الجديد الذي يقدمه لنا كاتب السفريات والمستكشف والبطل السابق للتزلج على الأمواج ، سام بليكلي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919150000" stop="20200919160000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <title lang="ar">أنثوني بوردين : بارتس أناون</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join world-renowned chef, bestselling author and multiple Emmy-winning television personality Anthony Bourdain as he travels across the globe to uncover little-known destinations and diverse cultures. انضموا إلى الشيف الأكثر شهرة في العالم والمؤلف صاحب الكتب الأكثر مبيعاً والحائز على جائزة إيمي أنتوني بوردين بينما يسافر حول العالم للكشف عن الوجهات غير المعروفة والثقافات المتنوعة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919160000" stop="20200919170000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">The Apartment</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا أبارتمنت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Under the watchful eyes of international design superstar Laurence Llewelyn-Bowen, dozens of passionate amateurs brave tight budgets and exacting time frames as they attempt to create stunning rooms in one-of-a-kind developments in Asia's biggest design reality show. سيقوم المُصمم المشهور لورانس ليفلن- بوين بتقديم أكبر معرض تصميم واقعيّ في العالم و الذي يحاول من خلاله عشرات من الهواة الشجعان تصميم و إبتكارغرف مذهلة في مشاريع فريدة من نوعها بميزانيات مالية ضئيلة وفترات زمنية قليلة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919170000" stop="20200919180000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">Trading Spaces</title>
    <title lang="ar">تريدينغ سبيسيز</title>
    <desc lang="en">This show pits neighbor against neighbor in a race to redecorate a room in each-other's homes. Can a friendship survive this weekend? يتبارى في هذا البرنامج الجار ضد جاره للقيام بتصميم وترتيب غرفةً واحدة في منزل الآخر. هل ستصمد الصداقة بعد ذلك السباق؟.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919180000" stop="20200919190000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">Brilliant Corners</title>
    <title lang="ar">بريليانت كورنرز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brilliant Corners is a dynamic new adventure series presented by travel writer, explorer and former European Longboard surfing champion, Sam Bleakley. شاهدوا مسلسل المغامرات الجديد الذي يقدمه لنا كاتب السفريات والمستكشف والبطل السابق للتزلج على الأمواج ، سام بليكلي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919190000" stop="20200919200000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <title lang="ar">أنثوني بوردين : بارتس أناون</title>
    <desc lang="en">Join world-renowned chef, bestselling author and multiple Emmy-winning television personality Anthony Bourdain as he travels across the globe to uncover little-known destinations and diverse cultures. انضموا إلى الشيف الأكثر شهرة في العالم والمؤلف صاحب الكتب الأكثر مبيعاً والحائز على جائزة إيمي أنتوني بوردين بينما يسافر حول العالم للكشف عن الوجهات غير المعروفة والثقافات المتنوعة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919200000" stop="20200919213000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">The Bachelor</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا باتشيلور</title>
    <desc lang="en">Peter will need to concentrate on his developing relationships in Santiago, the vibrant capital of Chile. His first date raises serious concerns when she reveals she has never been in love before. Another woman is getting a second one-on-one date causing a furore. يجب على بيتر التركيز على تطوير علاقاته في سانتياغو عاصمة تشيلي النابضة بالحياة. يبدأ موعده الأول بإثارة الأسئلة عندما تكشف الفتاة بأنها لم تقع في الحب من قبل. وتحصل إحدى الفتيات على موعد ثاني مما يثير الأمر الغضب لدى الأخريات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20200919213000" stop="20200919223000" channel="OSN Living HD">
    <title lang="en">Trading Spaces</title>
    <title lang="ar">تريدينغ سبيسيز</title>
    <desc lang="en">This show pits neighbor against neighbor in a race to redecorate a room in each-other's homes. Can a friendship survive this weekend? يتبارى في هذا البرنامج الجار ضد جاره للقيام بتصميم وترتيب غرفةً واحدة في منزل الآخر. هل ستصمد الصداقة بعد ذلك السباق؟.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>