<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB &amp; REX Postprocess -- version  V3.1.0.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
  <channel id="Discovery HD">
    <display-name lang="en">Discovery HD</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/DSC.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Discovery Science HD">
    <display-name lang="en">Discovery Science HD</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/SCI.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Discovery ID">
    <display-name lang="en">Discovery ID</display-name>
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="History HD">
    <display-name lang="en">History HD</display-name>
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="H2 HD">
    <display-name lang="en">H2 HD</display-name>
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Crime Investigation Network">
    <display-name lang="en">Crime Investigation Network</display-name>
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Nat Geo HD">
    <display-name lang="en">Nat Geo HD</display-name>
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Nat Geo Wild HD">
    <display-name lang="en">Nat Geo Wild HD</display-name>
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Nat Geo People HD">
    <display-name lang="en">Nat Geo People HD</display-name>
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20210117002000 +0000" stop="20210117010500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Misfit Garage</title>
    <title lang="ar">ميسفيت غاراج</title>
    <desc lang="en">Thomas and Tom pick up a rusted '67 Chevelle to flip for money towards Sue Yu-Lan's Martin's '56 Ford truck. Sue brings Richard Rawlings into the fold. يحصل توماس وتوم على سيارة شيفيل 67 الصدئة لاستبدالها بشاحنة سو يو لان مارتن فورد 56. يصطحب سو ريتشارد رولينغز إلى الحظيرة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117010500 +0000" stop="20210117015000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Marooned With Ed Stafford</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماروند ويذ إد ستافورد</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ed is stranded in the Carpathian Mountains. He's completely on his own with nothing - no food, no water, not even a knife. How will he cope in this environment for 10 days? تقطَعت السبل بإيد ستافورد في جبال كارباثيان. إنه معزول تماما عن العالم دون طعام أو ماء، ولا حتى سكين. فكيف سيتعامل مع هذا الوضع لمدة عشرة أيام؟.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117015000 +0000" stop="20210117021500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they make pistachios, what is the Forbidden City, and how do they produce radars? Find out as more items are put under the microscope. سنتعرف على أسرار الإنتاج من خلال اكتشاف طريقة صنع الأشياء حول العالم، انطلاقا من مكوك الفضاء إلى القهوة الفورية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117021500 +0000" stop="20210117023500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they build wrecker trucks, how do they produce Roquefort, and how are trees transported? Find out as more items are examined. سنتعرف على أسرار الإنتاج من خلال اكتشاف طريقة صنع الأشياء حول العالم، انطلاقا من مكوك الفضاء إلى القهوة الفورية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117023500 +0000" stop="20210117030000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they produce marble, how do they make mahjong pieces, and how do they build escape slides? Finds out as more items are put under the microscope. يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117030000 +0000" stop="20210117032500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at how products are manufactured. Featuring ball-bearings, what goes into cartoonist's ink and discover how false eyes are made. نتابع أسرا تصنيع العديد من الأدوات من مختلف أرجاء العالم، وفي هذه الحلقة طريقة تصنيع: المدحرجات الميكانيكية، حبر رسام الكاريكانور والعيون الصناعية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117032500 +0000" stop="20210117034500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at how products are manufactured around the world. How are Russian dolls manufactured, how is aloe vera produced and how are flags made? سنتعرف على كيفية صنع المنتجات في جميع أنحاء العالم. كيف يتم صنع الدمى الروسية المصنعة، مادة ألوي فيرا، والأعلام.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117034500 +0000" stop="20210117041000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at how products are manufactured around the world. How is vodka produced, how are Chinamax ships manufactured and how is abalone made? إكتشف أسرار تصنيع العديد من المنتجات من مختلف أرجاء العالم، نتابع في هذه الحلقة: فودكا ستاندرد الروسية، سفن شاينامكس العملاقة وأذن البحر.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117041000 +0000" stop="20210117043500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at how products are made around the world. Featuring the St Petersburg metro, the world's most expensive coffee and chip makers. نتابع أسرا تصنيع العديد من الأدوات من مختلف أرجاء العالم، وفي هذه الحلقة نتعرف على طريقة تصنيع: مترو سانت بطرسبيرغ، أغلى قهوة في العالم والرقائق.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117043500 +0000" stop="20210117052000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Deadliest Catch</title>
    <title lang="ar">دادلياست كاتش</title>
    <desc lang="en">A US Coastguard chopper attempts a dangerous rescue as Sean and Josh seek help from above. Edgar takes a major gamble and rejects advice from brother Sig. برنامج وثائقي يُسلط الضوء على الحياة الحقيقية لصيادي السلطعون  ومغامراتهم في ألاسكا. إنها المهنة الأكثر فتكا في العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117052000 +0000" stop="20210117061000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Gold Rush</title>
    <title lang="ar">غولد راش</title>
    <desc lang="en">Parker Schnabel is halfway through the season, but nowhere near halfway his goal. Plus, Tony Beets is ready to barge the bucket line down the Yukon River. قبل ست سنوات نجا عامل الذهب تود هوفمان من الانكماش الاقتصادي وتمكن من بناء مستقبل أفضل في حقول الذهب في الشمال المُجمد. هذه هي قصته الملهمة التي لا توصف.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117061000 +0000" stop="20210117063500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Building Alaska</title>
    <title lang="ar">بيلدنغ ألاسكا</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hunting and fishing guide Bob May builds a cabin on a remote island in southern Alaska. But, before he starts, he must tear down the old, abandoned one. سنتابع مجموعة من الشخصيات التي انطلقت لبناء ثلاثة كابينات لا تصدق في برية ألاسكا الغامضة. مع انعدام الطرق ومراكز تزويد المباني، سيتعين عليهم الإبداع في الموسم الجديد من برنامج "بيلدنغ ألاسكا".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117063500 +0000" stop="20210117065500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Building Alaska</title>
    <title lang="ar">بيلدنغ ألاسكا</title>
    <desc lang="en">On a nearly-deserted island Bob must adapt as inferior lumber, changing weather conditions and an 11-foot brown bear cause havoc on the build site. سنتابع مجموعة من الشخصيات التي انطلقت لبناء ثلاثة كابينات لا تصدق في برية ألاسكا الغامضة. مع انعدام الطرق ومراكز تزويد المباني، سيتعين عليهم الإبداع في الموسم الجديد من برنامج "بيلدنغ ألاسكا".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117065500 +0000" stop="20210117074500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Salvage Hunters</title>
    <title lang="ar">سالفدج هانترز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Drew haggles with a dealer at an Elizabethan manor house. He spots a jet engine in a Welsh museum, and meets an old friend in Sheffield - finding a modern treasure. سواء كانت مدخنة تعود لمنزل قديم متهالك أو قبة زجاجية تم تصميمها على النمط الفيكتوري، يبحث درو بيتشارد عن مقتنيات جميلة سواء كانت كهربائية أو معمارية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117074500 +0000" stop="20210117081000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they make steel cables strong enough to hold up a 50,000 tonne bridge? Why do modern hunters use medieval weapons? يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117081000 +0000" stop="20210117083000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they make Tennessee whiskey the traditional Lincoln County way? How do night goggles work? How do the Finnish relax in 160-degree saunas? يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117083000 +0000" stop="20210117092000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Misfit Garage</title>
    <title lang="ar">ميسفيت غاراج</title>
    <desc lang="en">Thomas and Tom acquire a rare first generation 1959 Chevy El Camino, but excitement turns to despair when the cars condition gives John Klump second thoughts. يحصل توماس وتوم على سيارة شيفي إل كامينو طراز عام 1959 نادرة ومن الجيل الأول، لكن الحماس يتحول إلى يأس عندما تجبر حالة السيارة جون كلامب على التفكير مرة أخرى.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117092000 +0000" stop="20210117100500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Alaska: The Last Frontier</title>
    <title lang="ar">آلاسكا: الحدود الأخيرة</title>
    <desc lang="en">Always pushed to their limits by the elements, circumstances and each other, the Kilchers continue to work together as a family to sustain the rich heritage of homesteading. تابع آل كليتشر ومجتمعهم المنعزل قرب هومر-آلاسكا. حيث عاشت هذه العائلة في منزلها وأكلت من حصاد زراعتها على مدى أربعة أجيال.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117100500 +0000" stop="20210117105500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Salvage Hunters</title>
    <title lang="ar">سالفدج هانترز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Drew is thrilled to look through an oddball collection of military antiques in Nantes, France. Plus, he takes an interest in a de Sede sofa bed in the Netherlands. سواء كانت مدخنة تعود لمنزل قديم متهالك أو قبة زجاجية تم تصميمها على النمط الفيكتوري، يبحث درو بيتشارد عن مقتنيات جميلة سواء كانت كهربائية أو معمارية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117105500 +0000" stop="20210117114000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Street Outlaws: Race Night In America</title>
    <title lang="ar">Discovery Channel HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">All across America street racers take on their rivals for cash prizes. In Missouri, there's an elimination tournament and in Michigan rivals hold a grudge match. توسيع للمدارك وإثراء لدائرة المعارف عبر قناة تعرض أهم البرامج الوثائقية الحائزة على جوائز عالمية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117114000 +0000" stop="20210117123000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Expedition To The Edge</title>
    <title lang="ar">Discovery Channel HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">A crew of modern explorers, Captain Clemens Gabriel and his family embarked on an 11-month journey into the Northwest Passage. What happened on their adventure? توسيع للمدارك وإثراء لدائرة المعارف عبر قناة تعرض أهم البرامج الوثائقية الحائزة على جوائز عالمية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117123000 +0000" stop="20210117131500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Alaska: The Last Frontier</title>
    <title lang="ar">آلاسكا: الحدود الأخيرة</title>
    <desc lang="en">Things get explosive when the Kilchers expand a road with the help of a detonation expert. Atz Sr and Bonnie brave the backcountry to salvage vital resources. تابع آل كليتشر ومجتمعهم المنعزل قرب هومر-آلاسكا. حيث عاشت هذه العائلة في منزلها وأكلت من حصاد زراعتها على مدى أربعة أجيال.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117131500 +0000" stop="20210117140500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Legends Of The Wild</title>
    <title lang="ar">Discovery Channel HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kangaroos are mysteriously being mauled in Victoria, Australia. With no big cats in this part of the world, has a long-extinct predator returned? توسيع للمدارك وإثراء لدائرة المعارف عبر قناة تعرض أهم البرامج الوثائقية الحائزة على جوائز عالمية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117140500 +0000" stop="20210117145000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Gold Rush</title>
    <title lang="ar">غولد راش</title>
    <desc lang="en">Parker running behind on his goal of 5,000 ounces - but his family has a birthday gift that might help. And, the Hoffmans play catch-up after a safety violation. قبل ست سنوات نجا عامل الذهب تود هوفمان من الانكماش الاقتصادي وتمكن من بناء مستقبل أفضل في حقول الذهب في الشمال المُجمد. هذه هي قصته الملهمة التي لا توصف.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117145000 +0000" stop="20210117154000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Expedition To The Edge</title>
    <title lang="ar">Discovery Channel HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">A crew of modern explorers, Captain Clemens Gabriel and his family embarked on an 11-month journey into the Northwest Passage. What happened on their adventure? توسيع للمدارك وإثراء لدائرة المعارف عبر قناة تعرض أهم البرامج الوثائقية الحائزة على جوائز عالمية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117154000 +0000" stop="20210117160500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they produce marble, how do they make mahjong pieces, and how do they build escape slides? Finds out as more items are put under the microscope. يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117160500 +0000" stop="20210117162500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at how products are manufactured around the world. Featuring Kamaz trucks, products for hair and the Canton Tower. نتابع في هذه الحلقة أسرار وطرق تصنيع ما يلي: شاحنات كاماز، منتجات العناية بالشعر وبرج كانتون.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117162500 +0000" stop="20210117171500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Misfit Garage</title>
    <title lang="ar">ميسفيت غاراج</title>
    <desc lang="en">Thomas surprises Klump with an offer. Thomas goes on a spending spree, adding two extra cars to the garage's inventory. Meanwhile, problems arise on the El Camino build. يفاجئ توماس كلامب بعرض. يذهب توماس في جولة إنفاق، ويحضر سيارتين إضافيتين إلى المرآب. وفي هذه الأثناء، تظهر بعض المشاكل أثناء العمل على سيارة إل كامينو.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117171500 +0000" stop="20210117180000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Misfit Garage</title>
    <title lang="ar">ميسفيت غاراج</title>
    <desc lang="en">The guys buy back a 1952 Willys Jeep to build an off-road machine! With no buyer, they showcase it at off-road event "Rednecks With Paychecks.". يعود توماس ويكس وفريقه من الميكانيكين لإعادة إصلاح المزيد من السيارات بطريقة إبداعية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117180000 +0000" stop="20210117185000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Kindig Customs</title>
    <title lang="ar">كندينغ كاستومس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dave has decided that the time is right to design his own concept car from scratch. It's a huge job that involves all the different departments in the shop. يُعيد ديف كينديغ، مالك ومشغِّل متجر كينديغ إت، تصميم سيارات فريدة من نوعها لزبائنه المتطلبين والمشهورين. سنرى السيارات المُصممة وقد كسبت شكلا آخر قبل أن يتم كشفها للمالك.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117185000 +0000" stop="20210117191500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Chasing Classic Cars</title>
    <title lang="ar">تشيزينغ كلاسيك كارز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Wayne finds a late '50s Stanguellini Monoposto Formula Junior race car for sale. Plus, he hopes to sell two cars to make room for a 1953 Bandini. يأخذ واين كاريني المشاهدين إلى عالم جمع السيارات الراقية. سنشاهد مهاراته في الكشف عن الجواهر الخفية التي تعتبر تقريبا منقرضة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117191500 +0000" stop="20210117194000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Chasing Classic Cars</title>
    <title lang="ar">تشيزينغ كلاسيك كارز</title>
    <desc lang="en">A pair of early '60s Volkswagen Karmann Ghias has Wayne grabbing his chequebook. Plus, Roger bets he can get one car running in eight minutes or less. يأخذ واين كاريني المشاهدين إلى عالم جمع السيارات الراقية. سنشاهد مهاراته في الكشف عن الجواهر الخفية التي تعتبر تقريبا منقرضة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117194000 +0000" stop="20210117203000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Fast N' Loud</title>
    <title lang="ar">سريع ومزعج</title>
    <desc lang="en">The guys team up with the Gary Sinise Foundation to build a custom '81 Jeep CJ7 as a tribute for Veteran's Day. Later, an original '68 Chevelle tempts Richard. قوم مالكو مرآب غاس مونكي في دالاس بشراء، ترميم، وإعادة بيع السيارات الأمريكية المتروكة، كل شيء بدءا من نماذج سنة 1931 إلى السيارات الكلاسيكية الرياضية والتي تعود إلى سنة 1973.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117203000 +0000" stop="20210117203000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Deadliest Catch</title>
    <title lang="ar">دادلياست كاتش</title>
    <desc lang="en">A serious illness forces Keith to hand over the Wizard. Josh fights for the helm despite a bad showing. Meanwhile, major engine trouble threatens Wild Bill's season. برنامج وثائقي يُسلط الضوء على الحياة الحقيقية لصيادي السلطعون  ومغامراتهم في ألاسكا. إنها المهنة الأكثر فتكا في العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117203000 +0000" stop="20210117211500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Deadliest Catch</title>
    <title lang="ar">دادلياست كاتش</title>
    <desc lang="en">A serious illness forces Keith to hand over the Wizard. Josh fights for the helm despite a bad showing. Meanwhile, major engine trouble threatens Wild Bill's season. برنامج وثائقي يُسلط الضوء على الحياة الحقيقية لصيادي السلطعون  ومغامراتهم في ألاسكا. إنها المهنة الأكثر فتكا في العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117211500 +0000" stop="20210117220500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Marooned With Ed Stafford</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماروند ويذ إد ستافورد</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ed is marooned on the unforgiving coast of Western Australia. He's completely on his own with nothing - No food, no water, not even a knife. How will he cope for 10 days? تقطَعت السبل بإيد ستافورد في ساحل غرب أستراليا الذي لا يرحم. إنه معزول تماما عن العالم دون طعام أو ماء، ولا حتى سكين. فكيف سيتعامل مع هذا الوضع لمدة عشرة أيام؟.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117220500 +0000" stop="20210117225000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Kindig Customs</title>
    <title lang="ar">كندينغ كاستومس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dave has decided that the time is right to design his own concept car from scratch. It's a huge job that involves all the different departments in the shop. يُعيد ديف كينديغ، مالك ومشغِّل متجر كينديغ إت، تصميم سيارات فريدة من نوعها لزبائنه المتطلبين والمشهورين. سنرى السيارات المُصممة وقد كسبت شكلا آخر قبل أن يتم كشفها للمالك.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117225000 +0000" stop="20210117231500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Chasing Classic Cars</title>
    <title lang="ar">تشيزينغ كلاسيك كارز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Wayne finds a late '50s Stanguellini Monoposto Formula Junior race car for sale. Plus, he hopes to sell two cars to make room for a 1953 Bandini. يأخذ واين كاريني المشاهدين إلى عالم جمع السيارات الراقية. سنشاهد مهاراته في الكشف عن الجواهر الخفية التي تعتبر تقريبا منقرضة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117231500 +0000" stop="20210117233500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Chasing Classic Cars</title>
    <title lang="ar">تشيزينغ كلاسيك كارز</title>
    <desc lang="en">A pair of early '60s Volkswagen Karmann Ghias has Wayne grabbing his chequebook. Plus, Roger bets he can get one car running in eight minutes or less. يأخذ واين كاريني المشاهدين إلى عالم جمع السيارات الراقية. سنشاهد مهاراته في الكشف عن الجواهر الخفية التي تعتبر تقريبا منقرضة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117233500 +0000" stop="20210118002000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Fast N' Loud</title>
    <title lang="ar">سريع ومزعج</title>
    <desc lang="en">The guys team up with the Gary Sinise Foundation to build a custom '81 Jeep CJ7 as a tribute for Veteran's Day. Later, an original '68 Chevelle tempts Richard. قوم مالكو مرآب غاس مونكي في دالاس بشراء، ترميم، وإعادة بيع السيارات الأمريكية المتروكة، كل شيء بدءا من نماذج سنة 1931 إلى السيارات الكلاسيكية الرياضية والتي تعود إلى سنة 1973.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118002000 +0000" stop="20210118010500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Misfit Garage</title>
    <title lang="ar">ميسفيت غاراج</title>
    <desc lang="en">Thomas surprises Klump with an offer. Thomas goes on a spending spree, adding two extra cars to the garage's inventory. Meanwhile, problems arise on the El Camino build. يفاجئ توماس كلامب بعرض. يذهب توماس في جولة إنفاق، ويحضر سيارتين إضافيتين إلى المرآب. وفي هذه الأثناء، تظهر بعض المشاكل أثناء العمل على سيارة إل كامينو.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118010500 +0000" stop="20210118015000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Marooned With Ed Stafford</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماروند ويذ إد ستافورد</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ed is marooned on the unforgiving coast of Western Australia. He's completely on his own with nothing - No food, no water, not even a knife. How will he cope for 10 days? تقطَعت السبل بإيد ستافورد في ساحل غرب أستراليا الذي لا يرحم. إنه معزول تماما عن العالم دون طعام أو ماء، ولا حتى سكين. فكيف سيتعامل مع هذا الوضع لمدة عشرة أيام؟.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118015000 +0000" stop="20210118021500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at how products are manufactured. Featuring ball-bearings, what goes into cartoonist's ink and discover how false eyes are made. نتابع أسرا تصنيع العديد من الأدوات من مختلف أرجاء العالم، وفي هذه الحلقة طريقة تصنيع: المدحرجات الميكانيكية، حبر رسام الكاريكانور والعيون الصناعية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118021500 +0000" stop="20210118023500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at how products are manufactured around the world. How are Russian dolls manufactured, how is aloe vera produced and how are flags made? سنتعرف على كيفية صنع المنتجات في جميع أنحاء العالم. كيف يتم صنع الدمى الروسية المصنعة، مادة ألوي فيرا، والأعلام.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118023500 +0000" stop="20210118030000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at how products are manufactured around the world. How is vodka produced, how are Chinamax ships manufactured and how is abalone made? إكتشف أسرار تصنيع العديد من المنتجات من مختلف أرجاء العالم، نتابع في هذه الحلقة: فودكا ستاندرد الروسية، سفن شاينامكس العملاقة وأذن البحر.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118030000 +0000" stop="20210118032500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at how products are made. Featuring how leather is produced, how goods are moved down the Grand Canal and how Flyboard is created. نتابع أسرا تصنيع العديد من الأدوات من مختلف أرجاء العالم، وفي هذه الحلقة نتعرف على طريقة تصنيع: الجلود، محطة قطارات غرند سنترال والألواح المائية النفاثة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118032500 +0000" stop="20210118034500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do Japanese master chefs prepare the extremely poisonous puffer fish and avoid killing their customers? And how do Scots weave over 700 types of tartan for kilts? نتعامل مع العديد من الأشياء في هذا العالم بمنطق: تحصيل حاصل، ولكن بعضا منها، بسيطة وصغيرة، يقف خلفها كما هائلا من الإجراءات والعمليات الهندسية المعقدة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118034500 +0000" stop="20210118041000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they design and produce the ultimate kingpin bowling ball? How do they raise and lower Tower Bridge? And how do they produce millions of gummy bears a day? Find out. نتعامل مع العديد من الأشياء في هذا العالم بمنطق: تحصيل حاصل، ولكن بعضا منها، بسيطة وصغيرة، يقف خلفها كما هائلا من الإجراءات والعمليات الهندسية المعقدة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118041000 +0000" stop="20210118043500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they run Ryker's Island, one of the biggest jails in the world? How do they make the famous Royal Mail post box? And how do they turn fruit into jam? Find out. نتعامل مع العديد من الأشياء في هذا العالم بمنطق: تحصيل حاصل، ولكن بعضا منها، بسيطة وصغيرة، يقف خلفها كما هائلا من الإجراءات والعمليات الهندسية المعقدة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118043500 +0000" stop="20210118052000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Deadliest Catch</title>
    <title lang="ar">دادلياست كاتش</title>
    <desc lang="en">A serious illness forces Keith to hand over the Wizard. Josh fights for the helm despite a bad showing. Meanwhile, major engine trouble threatens Wild Bill's season. برنامج وثائقي يُسلط الضوء على الحياة الحقيقية لصيادي السلطعون  ومغامراتهم في ألاسكا. إنها المهنة الأكثر فتكا في العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118052000 +0000" stop="20210118061000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Gold Rush</title>
    <title lang="ar">غولد راش</title>
    <desc lang="en">Parker running behind on his goal of 5,000 ounces - but his family has a birthday gift that might help. And, the Hoffmans play catch-up after a safety violation. قبل ست سنوات نجا عامل الذهب تود هوفمان من الانكماش الاقتصادي وتمكن من بناء مستقبل أفضل في حقول الذهب في الشمال المُجمد. هذه هي قصته الملهمة التي لا توصف.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118061000 +0000" stop="20210118063500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Building Alaska</title>
    <title lang="ar">بيلدنغ ألاسكا</title>
    <desc lang="en">Things are built differently in a state that experiences 100 earthquakes a day. Though the framing is completed, the five-month project takes its toll. سنتابع مجموعة من الشخصيات التي انطلقت لبناء ثلاثة كابينات لا تصدق في برية ألاسكا الغامضة. مع انعدام الطرق ومراكز تزويد المباني، سيتعين عليهم الإبداع في الموسم الجديد من برنامج "بيلدنغ ألاسكا".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118063500 +0000" stop="20210118065500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Building Alaska</title>
    <title lang="ar">بيلدنغ ألاسكا</title>
    <desc lang="en">A sub-contractor fails to show up at the jobsite for weeks, pushing Bob behind schedule. And, furry pests have chewed through hoses, cables, and grocery bags. سنتابع مجموعة من الشخصيات التي انطلقت لبناء ثلاثة كابينات لا تصدق في برية ألاسكا الغامضة. مع انعدام الطرق ومراكز تزويد المباني، سيتعين عليهم الإبداع في الموسم الجديد من برنامج "بيلدنغ ألاسكا".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118065500 +0000" stop="20210118074500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Salvage Hunters</title>
    <title lang="ar">سالفدج هانترز</title>
    <desc lang="en">In Tyne and Wear Drew tries to satisfy a customer with a taste for mid-century chic. Plus, he is enchanted by a former friary where a rare mirror catches his eye. سواء كانت مدخنة تعود لمنزل قديم متهالك أو قبة زجاجية تم تصميمها على النمط الفيكتوري، يبحث درو بيتشارد عن مقتنيات جميلة سواء كانت كهربائية أو معمارية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118074500 +0000" stop="20210118081000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How are powerful Scania trucks built? How do they use the world's biggest DNA database to solve crime? How is paraffin used to make Gouda cheese? يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118081000 +0000" stop="20210118083000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they make the finest classical guitars? How do they keep the blades turning on a wind turbine? How do they produce America's ultimate mowing machines? يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118083000 +0000" stop="20210118092000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Misfit Garage</title>
    <title lang="ar">ميسفيت غاراج</title>
    <desc lang="en">With a 48-hour deadline looming, the Fired Up Garage crew rush to complete Sue's '56 Ford truck, only to find their tools have been stolen! انضم أربعة ميكانيكيين إلى ريتشارد رولنغس في مرآب غاس مونكي للعمل على ابتكار سيارتهم الخاصة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118092000 +0000" stop="20210118100500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Railroad Alaska</title>
    <title lang="ar">ريلرود ألاسكا</title>
    <desc lang="en">After an accident, veteran off-gridder Jim James attempts to reach the hospital by train, but obstacles may put him in jeopardy. سنتابع طاقما من نخبة العمال - عمال البناء، آلات ميكانيكية وسائقي القطارات وهم يحاولون الحفاظ على سير عمل السكك الحديدية في ألاسكا التي تبلغ 500 ميلا خلال فصل الشتاء القاسي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118100500 +0000" stop="20210118105500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Salvage Hunters: Classic Cars</title>
    <title lang="ar">سالفج هنترس: كلاسك كارس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Drew and Paul head to the Midlands to look at a Swedish classic: the Volvo Amazon. And, Paul falls for an early Toyota MR2 - but can he convince Drew it will turn a profit? في هذه البرنامج، يقوم خبير التحف درو بريتشارد وبول كاولاند بشراء، إصلاح وبيع السيارات الكلاسيكية والدراجات النارية القديمة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118105500 +0000" stop="20210118114000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Kindig Customs</title>
    <title lang="ar">كندينغ كاستومس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dave has decided that the time is right to design his own concept car from scratch. It's a huge job that involves all the different departments in the shop. يُعيد ديف كينديغ، مالك ومشغِّل متجر كينديغ إت، تصميم سيارات فريدة من نوعها لزبائنه المتطلبين والمشهورين. سنرى السيارات المُصممة وقد كسبت شكلا آخر قبل أن يتم كشفها للمالك.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118114000 +0000" stop="20210118123000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Expedition To The Edge</title>
    <title lang="ar">Discovery Channel HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">A crew of modern explorers, Captain Clemens Gabriel and his family embarked on an 11-month journey into the Northwest Passage. What happened on their adventure? توسيع للمدارك وإثراء لدائرة المعارف عبر قناة تعرض أهم البرامج الوثائقية الحائزة على جوائز عالمية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118123000 +0000" stop="20210118131500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Alaska: The Last Frontier</title>
    <title lang="ar">آلاسكا: الحدود الأخيرة</title>
    <desc lang="en">As Thanksgiving approaches, the Kilchers prepare for a feast. Eivin and Eve rescue a baby seal on the beach and there's a beetle infestation on the homestead. تابع آل كليتشر ومجتمعهم المنعزل قرب هومر-آلاسكا. حيث عاشت هذه العائلة في منزلها وأكلت من حصاد زراعتها على مدى أربعة أجيال.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118131500 +0000" stop="20210118140500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Legends Of The Wild</title>
    <title lang="ar">Discovery Channel HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">In Ecuador, a killer is loose in the wild as livestock are being mutilated and left uneaten. Could it be proof the mythical Andean Mountain Wolf exists? توسيع للمدارك وإثراء لدائرة المعارف عبر قناة تعرض أهم البرامج الوثائقية الحائزة على جوائز عالمية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118140500 +0000" stop="20210118145000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Gold Rush</title>
    <title lang="ar">غولد راش</title>
    <desc lang="en">Todd's Colorado mine is in the path of a rare solar eclipse, but he's in trouble with less than 800 ounces this season. Meanwhile, Rick has bad news for Parker. يعلق حفار جاك هوفمان في وضع حرج مما يتطلب خضوعه لجراحة عاجلة، كما يقوم الطاقم بتعديل محطة الغسيل والتي تضاعف فرصهم في العثور على الذهب.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118145000 +0000" stop="20210118154000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Expedition To The Edge</title>
    <title lang="ar">Discovery Channel HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">A crew of modern explorers, Captain Clemens Gabriel and his family embarked on an 11-month journey into the Northwest Passage. What happened on their adventure? توسيع للمدارك وإثراء لدائرة المعارف عبر قناة تعرض أهم البرامج الوثائقية الحائزة على جوائز عالمية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118154000 +0000" stop="20210118160500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at how products are manufactured around the world. How is vodka produced, how are Chinamax ships manufactured and how is abalone made? إكتشف أسرار تصنيع العديد من المنتجات من مختلف أرجاء العالم، نتابع في هذه الحلقة: فودكا ستاندرد الروسية، سفن شاينامكس العملاقة وأذن البحر.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118160500 +0000" stop="20210118162500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at how products are made around the world. Featuring the St Petersburg metro, the world's most expensive coffee and chip makers. نتابع أسرا تصنيع العديد من الأدوات من مختلف أرجاء العالم، وفي هذه الحلقة نتعرف على طريقة تصنيع: مترو سانت بطرسبيرغ، أغلى قهوة في العالم والرقائق.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118162500 +0000" stop="20210118171500 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Misfit Garage</title>
    <title lang="ar">ميسفيت غاراج</title>
    <desc lang="en">Klump returns with the Willys Jeep painted the wrong colour. Thomas and Tom make a deal on a vintage '64 GTI and tell him they're building it. يعود توماس ويكس وفريقه من الميكانيكين لإعادة إصلاح المزيد من السيارات بطريقة إبداعية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118171500 +0000" stop="20210118180000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Misfit Garage</title>
    <title lang="ar">ميسفيت غاراج</title>
    <desc lang="en">Thomas finds a rare original 1932 Ford Tudor to build into the shop's finest car yet. And he plans to expand the business by sponsoring a red-hot bull rider. يعود توماس ويكس وفريقه من الميكانيكين لإعادة إصلاح المزيد من السيارات بطريقة إبداعية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118180000 +0000" stop="20210118185000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Gold Rush</title>
    <title lang="ar">غولد راش</title>
    <desc lang="en">The gold miners of the Yukon put everything on the line in the hopes of striking it rich. With new miners, new claims and new machines, the stakes are higher than ever! تعوق الحفارة المعطلة سير أعمال آل هوفمان، يجمع باركر شنابل حصيلته لهذا الموسم ويعيد تسليم المنجم لجده، بينما يحاول فتية داكوتا إعادة إفتتاح منجمهم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118185000 +0000" stop="20210118194000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Gold Rush: White Water</title>
    <title lang="ar">غولد راش: وايت ووتر</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dakota Fred and his son Dustin risk their lives to find a fortune in gold nuggets, taking them deep beneath the waters of one of Alaska's wildest creeks. في جبال تشيلكات النائية، يبحث فريد و داستن هرت عن كنز ودائع الذهب الذي لم يُكتشف بعد في ألاسكا. فهل سيعثران على أول رقائق من الذهب في المياه البيضاء؟.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118194000 +0000" stop="20210118203000 +0000" channel="Discovery HD">
    <title lang="en">Gold Rush: Dave Turin's Lost Mine</title>
    <title lang="ar">غولد راش: ديف تورنس لوست ماين</title>
    <desc lang="en">Legendary miner Dave Turin and his crew set out to find a new lost mine in Montana. But disaster strikes on their journey, threatening to end their season. يزور ديف تورينو العديد من مناجم الذهب المهجورة في جميع أنحاء غرب الولايات المتحدة ويقرر أي منها تصلح لإعادة استغلالها وتحويلها إلى منجم فعال ومُربح.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117001000 +0000" stop="20210117010000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">You Have Been Warned</title>
    <title lang="ar">يو هاف بين وورند</title>
    <desc lang="en">The smartest and bravest people use science to take their skills to the next level, from using trees as dominos to cutting through walls with a firehose. عد تنازلي سريع لأكثر الأعمال الفنية المثيرة في العالم. يجمع العلماء المقاطع الأكثر انتشارا من على شبكة الإنترنت لإظهار العلم وراء الحيل.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117010000 +0000" stop="20210117014800 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">The Explosion Show</title>
    <title lang="ar">Discovery Science HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tory Belleci and Streetbike Tommy meet experts using cutting-edge explosives to turn entire mountains into gravel-sized bits essential for construction. إحدى قنوات شبكة ديسكفري، تأتيكم ببرامج وثائقية ممتعة وتثري المعرفة في مجالات الفضاء، التكنولوجيا والطقس.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117014800 +0000" stop="20210117023600 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">The Explosion Show</title>
    <title lang="ar">Discovery Science HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tory Belleci and Streetbike Tommy meet experts from the FBI's bomb squad to reveal the forensics and technology required to investigate deadly bomb threats. إحدى قنوات شبكة ديسكفري، تأتيكم ببرامج وثائقية ممتعة وتثري المعرفة في مجالات الفضاء، التكنولوجيا والطقس.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117023600 +0000" stop="20210117030000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they forge a set of jaws that can chomp through concrete, stitch the historic airman's bomber, and brew the oldest beer in the Western World? يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117030000 +0000" stop="20210117032400 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they turn Sheffield steel into a carpenter's handsaw, make a microphone that can pick up a whisper, and safely steer through a frozen river? يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117032400 +0000" stop="20210117034800 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they brew moonshine in the heart of New York City, make a battery powered bicycle, and grow the rubber for wetsuits in the Arizona desert? يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117034800 +0000" stop="20210117041200 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they mine one of the rarest gemstones in the world, craft the classic cowboy boot, and build a road sweeper that can pick up seven tonnes of trash? يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117041200 +0000" stop="20210117043600 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How It's Made</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو اتس ميد</title>
    <desc lang="en">More everyday items are put under the microscope as we discover how upright pianos are manufactured and flags are produced. إذا تساءلت يوماً: من أين أتى هذا؟ أو كيف قاموا بصنع ذلك؟ فهذا هو البرنامج الذي تبحث عنه، لأنه يختبر إحدى الأدوات المنزلية المألوفة وكيف تمت صناعتها، في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117043600 +0000" stop="20210117050000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How It's Made</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو اتس ميد</title>
    <desc lang="en">More everyday items are put under the microscope as we discover how oil lamps are manufactured and chocolate mints are produced. إذا تساءلت يوماً: من أين أتى هذا؟ أو كيف قاموا بصنع ذلك؟ فهذا هو البرنامج الذي تبحث عنه، لأنه يختبر إحدى الأدوات المنزلية المألوفة وكيف تمت صناعتها، في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117050000 +0000" stop="20210117052400 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How It's Made</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو اتس ميد</title>
    <desc lang="en">More everyday items go under the microscope, revealing their production processes. How are objects including dumplings and brass faucets made? إذا تساءلت يوماً: من أين أتى هذا؟ أو كيف قاموا بصنع ذلك؟ فهذا هو البرنامج الذي تبحث عنه، لأنه يختبر إحدى الأدوات المنزلية المألوفة وكيف تمت صناعتها، في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117052400 +0000" stop="20210117061200 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">The Explosion Show</title>
    <title lang="ar">Discovery Science HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tory Belleci and Streetbike Tommy check out one of the world's largest fireworks companies to reveal the explosive secrets of its pyrotechnics experts. إحدى قنوات شبكة ديسكفري، تأتيكم ببرامج وثائقية ممتعة وتثري المعرفة في مجالات الفضاء، التكنولوجيا والطقس.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117061200 +0000" stop="20210117070000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">The Explosion Show</title>
    <title lang="ar">Discovery Science HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tory Belleci and Streetbike Tommy meet the expert firefighters who use explosive technology to battle dangerous infernos. Is more fire the best antidote? إحدى قنوات شبكة ديسكفري، تأتيكم ببرامج وثائقية ممتعة وتثري المعرفة في مجالات الفضاء، التكنولوجيا والطقس.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117070000 +0000" stop="20210117074800 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">The Explosion Show</title>
    <title lang="ar">Discovery Science HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tory Belleci and Streetbike Tommy check out a Hollywood special effects company to reveal the secrets of the world's greatest movie explosions. إحدى قنوات شبكة ديسكفري، تأتيكم ببرامج وثائقية ممتعة وتثري المعرفة في مجالات الفضاء، التكنولوجيا والطقس.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117074800 +0000" stop="20210117083600 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">The Explosion Show</title>
    <title lang="ar">Discovery Science HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tory Belleci and Streetbike Tommy meet experts of the battlefield who recreate black powder blasts from the Civil War and experiment with this deadly explosive. إحدى قنوات شبكة ديسكفري، تأتيكم ببرامج وثائقية ممتعة وتثري المعرفة في مجالات الفضاء، التكنولوجيا والطقس.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117083600 +0000" stop="20210117092400 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Mythbusters</title>
    <title lang="ar">ميثباسترز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Adam and Jamie ask if drifting is faster than driving -on dirt- then they return to fan favourite 'What Is Bulletproof?' featuring lighters and fish tanks. مع المضيفين جيمي هينيمان وآدم سافيج، يكشف البرنامج الحقيقة وراء أساطير وخرافات شعبية بمزج الأسلوب العلمي مع الفضول المرح والبراعة القديمة السهلة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117092400 +0000" stop="20210117094800 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How It's Made</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو اتس ميد</title>
    <desc lang="en">More everyday items are put under the microscope as we discover how NASCAR car bodies are manufactured and thermal coffee pots are produced. إذا تساءلت يوماً: من أين أتى هذا؟ أو كيف قاموا بصنع ذلك؟ فهذا هو البرنامج الذي تبحث عنه، لأنه يختبر إحدى الأدوات المنزلية المألوفة وكيف تمت صناعتها، في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117094800 +0000" stop="20210117101200 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How It's Made</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو اتس ميد</title>
    <desc lang="en">More everyday items are put under the microscope as we discover how electric vehicle charging stations are made and grappa is produced. إذا تساءلت يوماً: من أين أتى هذا؟ أو كيف قاموا بصنع ذلك؟ فهذا هو البرنامج الذي تبحث عنه، لأنه يختبر إحدى الأدوات المنزلية المألوفة وكيف تمت صناعتها، في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117101200 +0000" stop="20210117103600 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How It's Made</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو اتس ميد</title>
    <desc lang="en">More everyday items are put under the microscope as we discover how slate tiles are produced and hot dog carts are made. إذا تساءلت يوماً: من أين أتى هذا؟ أو كيف قاموا بصنع ذلك؟ فهذا هو البرنامج الذي تبحث عنه، لأنه يختبر إحدى الأدوات المنزلية المألوفة وكيف تمت صناعتها، في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117103600 +0000" stop="20210117110000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How It's Made</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو اتس ميد</title>
    <desc lang="en">More everyday items are put under the microscope as we discover how racing leathers are manufactured and wood rocking chairs are made. إذا تساءلت يوماً: من أين أتى هذا؟ أو كيف قاموا بصنع ذلك؟ فهذا هو البرنامج الذي تبحث عنه، لأنه يختبر إحدى الأدوات المنزلية المألوفة وكيف تمت صناعتها، في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117110000 +0000" stop="20210117112400 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How It's Made</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو اتس ميد</title>
    <desc lang="en">More everyday items are put under the microscope as we discover how mountain bikes are produced and lever action rifles are manufactured. إذا تساءلت يوماً: من أين أتى هذا؟ أو كيف قاموا بصنع ذلك؟ فهذا هو البرنامج الذي تبحث عنه، لأنه يختبر إحدى الأدوات المنزلية المألوفة وكيف تمت صناعتها، في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117112400 +0000" stop="20210117115000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How It's Made</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو اتس ميد</title>
    <desc lang="en">More everyday items are put under the microscope as we discover how saunas are produced and wheelchair lifts are manufactured. إذا تساءلت يوماً: من أين أتى هذا؟ أو كيف قاموا بصنع ذلك؟ فهذا هو البرنامج الذي تبحث عنه، لأنه يختبر إحدى الأدوات المنزلية المألوفة وكيف تمت صناعتها، في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117115000 +0000" stop="20210117121400 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How It's Made</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو اتس ميد</title>
    <desc lang="en">More everyday items are put under the microscope as we discover how upright pianos are manufactured and flags are produced. إذا تساءلت يوماً: من أين أتى هذا؟ أو كيف قاموا بصنع ذلك؟ فهذا هو البرنامج الذي تبحث عنه، لأنه يختبر إحدى الأدوات المنزلية المألوفة وكيف تمت صناعتها، في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117121400 +0000" stop="20210117123800 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How It's Made</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو اتس ميد</title>
    <desc lang="en">More everyday items are put under the microscope as we discover how oil lamps are manufactured and chocolate mints are produced. إذا تساءلت يوماً: من أين أتى هذا؟ أو كيف قاموا بصنع ذلك؟ فهذا هو البرنامج الذي تبحث عنه، لأنه يختبر إحدى الأدوات المنزلية المألوفة وكيف تمت صناعتها، في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117123800 +0000" stop="20210117130200 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How It's Made</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو اتس ميد</title>
    <desc lang="en">More everyday items are put under the microscope as we discover how skeletal replicas are manufactured and ice buckets are made. إذا تساءلت يوماً: من أين أتى هذا؟ أو كيف قاموا بصنع ذلك؟ فهذا هو البرنامج الذي تبحث عنه، لأنه يختبر إحدى الأدوات المنزلية المألوفة وكيف تمت صناعتها، في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117130200 +0000" stop="20210117132600 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How It's Made</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو اتس ميد</title>
    <desc lang="en">More everyday items are put under the microscope as we discover how automatic sliding doors are manufactured and gin is produced. إذا تساءلت يوماً: من أين أتى هذا؟ أو كيف قاموا بصنع ذلك؟ فهذا هو البرنامج الذي تبحث عنه، لأنه يختبر إحدى الأدوات المنزلية المألوفة وكيف تمت صناعتها، في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117132600 +0000" stop="20210117135000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How It's Made</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو اتس ميد</title>
    <desc lang="en">How are everyday objects made? Common items including Thai barbeques, diving masks and fins, and bassoons go under the microscope. إذا تساءلت يوماً: من أين أتى هذا؟ أو كيف قاموا بصنع ذلك؟ فهذا هو البرنامج الذي تبحث عنه، لأنه يختبر إحدى الأدوات المنزلية المألوفة وكيف تمت صناعتها، في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117135000 +0000" stop="20210117141400 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How It's Made</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو اتس ميد</title>
    <desc lang="en">How are everyday objects made? Common items including Moccasins, Electronic Impact Drills go under the microscope. إذا تساءلت يوماً: من أين أتى هذا؟ أو كيف قاموا بصنع ذلك؟ فهذا هو البرنامج الذي تبحث عنه، لأنه يختبر إحدى الأدوات المنزلية المألوفة وكيف تمت صناعتها، في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117141400 +0000" stop="20210117150200 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Alaska Mega Machines</title>
    <title lang="ar">ألاسكا ميغا ماشينز</title>
    <desc lang="en">A mega fish factory churns out 3 million pounds of seafood a day. Plus, a flying ambulance saves lives at 14,000 feet above Alaska's wilderness. يفحص برنامج ألاسكا ميغا ماشين العلوم وراء كيفية تصميم هذه الآلات الضخمة للديمومة هكذا في الحدود الأخيرة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117150200 +0000" stop="20210117155000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Alaska Mega Machines</title>
    <title lang="ar">ألاسكا ميغا ماشينز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Only in Alaska can you find an airport made from nothing but water and ice. And next to a field of moose, 16 missiles stand by to prevent a nuclear disaster. يفحص برنامج ألاسكا ميغا ماشين العلوم وراء كيفية تصميم هذه الآلات الضخمة للديمومة هكذا في الحدود الأخيرة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117155000 +0000" stop="20210117164000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Incredible Engineering Blunders: Fixed</title>
    <title lang="ar">إنكريدل إنجنيرنغ بلاندرز: فيكسد</title>
    <desc lang="en">Former aerospace engineer Justin tries to keep the Glasgow Tower turning, and Tomo helps engineers in Osaka keep their airport from sinking into the sea. يتابع البرنامج الصحفي الهندي البارز جاستين كننغهام وفريقه من المراسلين الجريئين، حيث يكشفون عن الأخطاء الهندسية الأكثر غرابة في العالم ويكتشفون كيفية إصلاحها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117164000 +0000" stop="20210117173000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Incredible Engineering Blunders: Fixed</title>
    <title lang="ar">إنكريدل إنجنيرنغ بلاندرز: فيكسد</title>
    <desc lang="en">Justin climbs on top of a stadium roof that is held up by air and in danger of collapse. Plus, Jimena Gascon discovers why Mexico City's Metro project has been derailed. يتابع البرنامج الصحفي الهندي البارز جاستين كننغهام وفريقه من المراسلين الجريئين، حيث يكشفون عن الأخطاء الهندسية الأكثر غرابة في العالم ويكتشفون كيفية إصلاحها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117173000 +0000" stop="20210117182000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Incredible Engineering Blunders: Fixed</title>
    <title lang="ar">إنكريدل إنجنيرنغ بلاندرز: فيكسد</title>
    <desc lang="en">Justin uncovers the truth behind a landslide that wiped out a ski-jump resort in Turkey, before jetting off to Gibraltar to see an airport runway built across a road. يتابع البرنامج الصحفي الهندي البارز جاستين كننغهام وفريقه من المراسلين الجريئين، حيث يكشفون عن الأخطاء الهندسية الأكثر غرابة في العالم ويكتشفون كيفية إصلاحها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117182000 +0000" stop="20210117191000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Blowing Up History</title>
    <title lang="ar">بلوينغ أب هستوري</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Leaning Tower of Pisa is one of the world's most iconic buildings, but why does it lean? Investigators uncover the reasons for its tilt. يٌحقق برنامج بلوينغ أب هستوري في الأدلة الجديدة التي تكشف عن الأساطير والأسرار وراء الحضارات القديمة والبنى الضخمة التي بنوها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117191000 +0000" stop="20210117200000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Mysteries Of The Deep</title>
    <title lang="ar">Discovery Science HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jeremy Wade reveals the new deep-sea discoveries that might prove the existence of the infamous giant squid. Is this underwater monster the legendary kraken? إحدى قنوات شبكة ديسكفري، تأتيكم ببرامج وثائقية ممتعة وتثري المعرفة في مجالات الفضاء، التكنولوجيا والطقس.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117200000 +0000" stop="20210117205000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Unexplained &amp; Unexplored</title>
    <title lang="ar">Discovery Science HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">Justin and Emiliano investigate the possibility that the Knights Templar fled Europe and rebuilt their order in the Americas a century before Columbus. إحدى قنوات شبكة ديسكفري، تأتيكم ببرامج وثائقية ممتعة وتثري المعرفة في مجالات الفضاء، التكنولوجيا والطقس.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117205000 +0000" stop="20210117205000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Codes And Conspiracies</title>
    <title lang="ar">كودس أند كنسبيريسيز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Did aliens help build the Pyramids? Or does the "ancient astronauts" idea go back to Swiss author Erich von Daniken, whose books challenge religion and science? اكتشف الحقيقة وراء واحدة من أكثر مؤسسات المجتمع سرية. من بين هذه الأسرار تخص الرعاة، الحكومات وحتى الدين.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117205000 +0000" stop="20210117214000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Codes And Conspiracies</title>
    <title lang="ar">كودس أند كنسبيريسيز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Did aliens help build the Pyramids? Or does the "ancient astronauts" idea go back to Swiss author Erich von Daniken, whose books challenge religion and science? اكتشف الحقيقة وراء واحدة من أكثر مؤسسات المجتمع سرية. من بين هذه الأسرار تخص الرعاة، الحكومات وحتى الدين.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117214000 +0000" stop="20210117223000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Codes And Conspiracies</title>
    <title lang="ar">كودس أند كنسبيريسيز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Discovers which of America's founding fathers used sex as an instrument of diplomacy and which one secretly scoffed at the divinity of Jesus. اكتشف الحقيقة وراء واحدة من أكثر مؤسسات المجتمع سرية. من بين هذه الأسرار تخص الرعاة، الحكومات وحتى الدين.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210117223000 +0000" stop="20210118001000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How The Universe Works</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو ذا يونيفرس وركس</title>
    <desc lang="en">If an asteroid collides with the earth it could end life on our planet as we know it. Experts reveal just how close we are to an apocalypse. ذات يوم سوف تتسبب كارثة كونية في زوال الحياة على الرض. وللبقاء على قيد الحياة يجب علينا العثور على مكان آخر قابل للعيش فيه بين الكواكب الأخرى. سنتابع ذلك مع العلماء الذين يحاولون جعل ذلك ممكنا.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118001000 +0000" stop="20210118010000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Secret Space Escapes</title>
    <title lang="ar">سيكرت سبيس إسكيبس</title>
    <desc lang="en">A power failure occurs on the ISS forcing the crew to consider abandoning the station. Plus, during a spacewalk a cosmonaut is nearly stranded after a suit malfunction. شاهدوا القصص الحقيقية للإخفاقات الوشيكة، المكالمات السرية، المواجهات غير المتوقعة، والاكتشافات الخطيرة في تاريخ الإستكشافات الفضائية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118010000 +0000" stop="20210118014800 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Secret Space Escapes</title>
    <title lang="ar">سيكرت سبيس إسكيبس</title>
    <desc lang="en">A leak threatens the lives of astronauts upon re-entry. And a mission to the Salyut space station takes a surprise turn when the crew suffers from depressurisation. شاهدوا القصص الحقيقية للإخفاقات الوشيكة، المكالمات السرية، المواجهات غير المتوقعة، والاكتشافات الخطيرة في تاريخ الإستكشافات الفضائية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118014800 +0000" stop="20210118023600 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Man v The Universe</title>
    <title lang="ar">مان x ذا يونيفيرس</title>
    <desc lang="en">For the first time since the Cold War the Moon is inspiring a race. But this time around winning is not about proving military might - it's about cold hard cash. للمرة الأولى منذ الحرب الباردة، يلهم القمر المتسابقين. لا يتمثل الهدف من الفوز هذه المرة في إثبات القوة العسكرية بل في الحصول على العملة الصعبة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118023600 +0000" stop="20210118032400 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Man v The Universe</title>
    <title lang="ar">مان x ذا يونيفيرس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Asteroids have decimated life on Earth before and they will again. Across the globe, scientists, engineers and astronauts are gearing up for a cosmic battle. دمرت الكويكبات الحياة على الأرض منذ زمن وإن تُركت دون تقصٍ ستعيد الكرة مرة أخرى. يستعد العلماء، المهندسون، ورواد الفضاء في جميع أنحاء العالم لمعركة كونية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118032400 +0000" stop="20210118034800 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they make the world's softest duvets, drill for oil thousands of metres below ground, and put the stretch in rubber bands? يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118034800 +0000" stop="20210118041200 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they build a diesel engine that can fly, make cough sweets, turn clear plastic into bank notes, and whip up ice cream flavours? يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118041200 +0000" stop="20210118043600 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How It's Made</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو اتس ميد</title>
    <desc lang="en">More everyday items are put under the microscope as we discover how skeletal replicas are manufactured and ice buckets are made. إذا تساءلت يوماً: من أين أتى هذا؟ أو كيف قاموا بصنع ذلك؟ فهذا هو البرنامج الذي تبحث عنه، لأنه يختبر إحدى الأدوات المنزلية المألوفة وكيف تمت صناعتها، في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118043600 +0000" stop="20210118050000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How It's Made</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو اتس ميد</title>
    <desc lang="en">More everyday items are put under the microscope as we discover how automatic sliding doors are manufactured and gin is produced. إذا تساءلت يوماً: من أين أتى هذا؟ أو كيف قاموا بصنع ذلك؟ فهذا هو البرنامج الذي تبحث عنه، لأنه يختبر إحدى الأدوات المنزلية المألوفة وكيف تمت صناعتها، في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118050000 +0000" stop="20210118052400 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they turn a family car into a fortress on wheels, grow millions of perfect Christmas trees and hammer out the world's finest cymbals? يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118052400 +0000" stop="20210118054800 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they mine precious opals beneath one of the hottest deserts on earth? How do they build breath-taking stunt planes and how do they make nougat? سنتعرف على أسرار الإنتاج من خلال اكتشاف طريقة صنع الأشياء حول العالم، انطلاقا من مكوك الفضاء إلى القهوة الفورية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118054800 +0000" stop="20210118061200 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they farm the expensive spice saffron, how do they create giant roads made entirely from ice and how do they manufacture a muscle car? يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118061200 +0000" stop="20210118063600 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they turn trees into toilet paper? How do they make absinthe and how do they make cricket balls tough enough to face batsmen? يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118063600 +0000" stop="20210118070000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they cultivate green salad on scorching desert plains, how do they make rigging for ships and how do they produce lifesaving insulin from bread? يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118070000 +0000" stop="20210118072400 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they build one of the world's most powerful locomotives? And how do they turn cows' milk into clotted cream? يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118072400 +0000" stop="20210118081200 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Morgan Freeman's Through The Wormhole</title>
    <title lang="ar">مورغان فريمانز ثرو ذا وورمهول</title>
    <desc lang="en">The universe seems real, but what if it isn't? Scientists from all fields are exploring the possibility that life is virtual reality. إن الكون الذي نعيش فيه حقيقي. ولكن ماذا لو كان عكس ذلك ؟ هل سنتمكن من اكتشاف خلل في القانون الكوني غائب عنا قد يمكننا من فهم جوهره الخفي؟.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118081200 +0000" stop="20210118090000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Morgan Freeman's Through The Wormhole</title>
    <title lang="ar">مورغان فريمانز ثرو ذا وورمهول</title>
    <desc lang="en">If you think you see everyone as equal you are kidding yourself. No matter how open-minded we think we are stereotypes colour our judgment of others. إذا كنت ترى الجميع بنفس درجة المساواة، فإنك تخدع نفسك. مهما كانت درجة الإنفتاح لدينا فإن الصور النمطية هي التي تصدر أحكامنا على الآخرين.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118090000 +0000" stop="20210118094800 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Abandoned Engineering</title>
    <title lang="ar">أباندند إنجنيرنغ</title>
    <desc lang="en">A Nazi structure that changed history and a Soviet monolith known as the Tower of Death are deserted engineering projects. Experts examine their origins. البحث في أسباب وكيفية بناء المشاريع الكبيرة، التكاليف المالية والاجتماعية بعد فشلها، والعواقب على البيئة. يقدم الخبراء خططًا لصنع شيء جديد من تحت الأنقاض.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118094800 +0000" stop="20210118103600 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Abandoned Engineering</title>
    <title lang="ar">أباندند إنجنيرنغ</title>
    <desc lang="en">Experts investigate the story behind an underwater graveyard of unexpected American treasures, and a network of tunnels hiding a secret history of New York. البحث في أسباب وكيفية بناء المشاريع الكبيرة، التكاليف المالية والاجتماعية بعد فشلها، والعواقب على البيئة. يقدم الخبراء خططًا لصنع شيء جديد من تحت الأنقاض.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118103600 +0000" stop="20210118110000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How It's Made</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو اتس ميد</title>
    <desc lang="en">More everyday items go under the microscope, revealing their production. How are objects such as micro drill bits and skiffs made? إذا تساءلت يوماً: من أين أتى هذا؟ أو كيف قاموا بصنع ذلك؟ فهذا هو البرنامج الذي تبحث عنه، لأنه يختبر إحدى الأدوات المنزلية المألوفة وكيف تمت صناعتها، في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118110000 +0000" stop="20210118112400 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How It's Made</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو اتس ميد</title>
    <desc lang="en">More everyday items go under the microscope, revealing their production. How are objects such as ocean drone transformers and 3D puzzles made? إذا تساءلت يوماً: من أين أتى هذا؟ أو كيف قاموا بصنع ذلك؟ فهذا هو البرنامج الذي تبحث عنه، لأنه يختبر إحدى الأدوات المنزلية المألوفة وكيف تمت صناعتها، في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118112400 +0000" stop="20210118115000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How It's Made</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو اتس ميد</title>
    <desc lang="en">More everyday items go under the microscope, revealing their production. How are objects including Formula F race cars made? إذا تساءلت يوماً: من أين أتى هذا؟ أو كيف قاموا بصنع ذلك؟ فهذا هو البرنامج الذي تبحث عنه، لأنه يختبر إحدى الأدوات المنزلية المألوفة وكيف تمت صناعتها، في كل حلقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118115000 +0000" stop="20210118123800 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Storm Chasers</title>
    <title lang="ar">ستورم تشيزيرس</title>
    <desc lang="en">A tornado threatens havoc in team Dominator's backyard. The TIV team follows their navigator's prediction and tension threatens to derail team TWISTEX's chase. يهدد الأعاصير المتزايدة بنشر الفوضى في موطن فريق دومينيتور. يعتمد فريق تي آي في على تنبؤات جهاز الملاحة بينما تهدد حدة التوترات بعرقلة مهمة فريق تويستكس.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118123800 +0000" stop="20210118132600 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Futurescape With James Woods</title>
    <title lang="ar">فيوتشريسكيب ويذ جيمس وودز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Experiments have transformed machines into creatures with consciousness. Will this result in a world where man and machine are indistinguishable. يقوم جيمس بدراسة الحاضر والمستقبل البعيد لإلقاء نظرة على الأفكار والخلافات المستقبلية و التي تحدث فعليا اليوم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118132600 +0000" stop="20210118141400 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Futurescape With James Woods</title>
    <title lang="ar">فيوتشريسكيب ويذ جيمس وودز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Imagine a world where your most intimate memory is public domain. Scientists are reading minds with innovative methods that may put an end to privacy. يقوم جيمس بدراسة الحاضر والمستقبل البعيد لإلقاء نظرة على الأفكار والخلافات المستقبلية و التي تحدث فعليا اليوم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118141400 +0000" stop="20210118150200 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Abandoned Engineering</title>
    <title lang="ar">أباندند إنجنيرنغ</title>
    <desc lang="en">A deserted town in Spain with a bloody past and a ghost fleet heading nowhere are homes to dark American secrets. New discoveries reveal their origins. البحث في أسباب وكيفية بناء المشاريع الكبيرة، التكاليف المالية والاجتماعية بعد فشلها، والعواقب على البيئة. يقدم الخبراء خططًا لصنع شيء جديد من تحت الأنقاض.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118150200 +0000" stop="20210118155000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Abandoned Engineering</title>
    <title lang="ar">أباندند إنجنيرنغ</title>
    <desc lang="en">Experts reveal how a haunted lighthouse on Lake Michigan and a secret complex of tunnels beneath London were built and why they were abandoned. البحث في أسباب وكيفية بناء المشاريع الكبيرة، التكاليف المالية والاجتماعية بعد فشلها، والعواقب على البيئة. يقدم الخبراء خططًا لصنع شيء جديد من تحت الأنقاض.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118155000 +0000" stop="20210118164000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Morgan Freeman's Through The Wormhole</title>
    <title lang="ar">مورغان فريمانز ثرو ذا وورمهول</title>
    <desc lang="en">Are our brains wired for lying from a young age? The brains of pathological liars may provide insights. And how will technology impact upon our lies? هل أن أدمغتنا قد نشأت بالفطرة على الكذب منذ صغرنا؟ قد تجيب أدمغة الذين يعانون من مرض الكذب على هذا السؤال. وكيف سيكون تأثير التكنولوجيا على الأكاذيب لدينا؟.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118164000 +0000" stop="20210118173000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">Morgan Freeman's Through The Wormhole</title>
    <title lang="ar">مورغان فريمانز ثرو ذا وورمهول</title>
    <desc lang="en">We move around in space, but we are stuck in a prison of time moving ever forwards. Could science ever make the clock move backwards? سنتنقل بحرية في الفضاء، ولكن نحن عالقون في سجن الزمن الذي يدور فقط نحو الأمام. هل سيتمكن العلم في يوم ما من جعل عقارب الساعة تدور إلى الوراء؟.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118173000 +0000" stop="20210118175500 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at how products are manufactured around the world. Looking at sardine fishing, Piaggio scooters and erector sets. يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118175500 +0000" stop="20210118182000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at how products are manufactured around the world. Featuring plane painting, pasties and how clogs are made. يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118182000 +0000" stop="20210118184500 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">How do they cast bells fit for the world's greatest cathedrals? And how do they clear up the effect of one of America's biggest storms? يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118184500 +0000" stop="20210118191000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at how products are manufactured around the world. Featuring Titan Tires, espresso and how diamonds are cut. يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118191000 +0000" stop="20210118193500 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">A look at how products are manufactured around the world. Featuring the complex network of Paris sewers, Beretta's and cotton manufacture. يمنح برنامج "هاو دو ذاي دو إت" المشاهدين نظرة أخرى من وراء الكواليس حول كيفية صنع الأشياء العادية التي نعتبرها من المسلمات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118193500 +0000" stop="20210118200000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How Do They Do It?</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو دو ذاي دو إت</title>
    <desc lang="en">What is the secret of the lion dance, how are tunnels built, and what is a super sopper? Find out as more items are put under the microscope. سنتعرف على أسرار الإنتاج من خلال اكتشاف طريقة صنع الأشياء حول العالم، انطلاقا من مكوك الفضاء إلى القهوة الفورية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210118200000 +0000" stop="20210118205000 +0000" channel="Discovery Science HD">
    <title lang="en">How The Universe Works</title>
    <title lang="ar">هاو ذا يونيفرس وركس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Manned missions to Mars are the next frontier of human exploration and NASA wants to put boots on the Red Planet by 2035. But, is it mission impossible? الكون مكان عنيف وخطير. من النجوم المتفجرة والمجرات المتصادمة إلى الموجات الصادمة - ما هي أسوأ الأماكن في الكون؟.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>