<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB &amp; REX Postprocess -- version V3.1.5.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
  <channel id="OSN Series HD">
    <display-name lang="en">OSN Series HD</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/obg.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20210123000000 +0000" stop="20210123004500 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tension builds when a group of rabble-rousers attempt to lock down the firehouse. Brett is faced with a monumental decision. Cruz readies himself for a big day. Gallo and Ritter attempt to launch Firehouse 51 into the social media age. يزداد التوتر عندما محاولة مجموعة من الرعاع إغلاق مركز الإطفاءو يتخذ بريت قرار مهم بينما يهيئ كروز نفسه ليوم عظيم و يعلن جالو و ريتر عن مركز الإطفاء 51 في  وسائل التواصل الاجتماعي.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085481_LC_STB135335612.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E19</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123004500 +0000" stop="20210123013000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">When one of 51's own gets injured on a call, Lt. Severide becomes obsessed with helping out. Foster contemplates a big decision. Kidd is concerned for one of her high school trainees. عندما يُصاب أحد أفراد الـ51 بجروح  يسرع الملازم سيفرايد  لتقديم المساعدة و يفكر فوستر مليا  باتخاذ قرار كبير و كيد قلقة على إحدى المتدربات في المدرسة الثانوية.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085482_LC_STB135406110.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E20</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123013000 +0000" stop="20210123021500 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">When we last saw our heroes they were racing to rescue workers trapped inside of a burning mattress factory. As the fire spirals out of control, truck and squad lay it on the line in hopes of getting the trapped victims out alive. عندما رأينا أبطالنا آخر مرة كانوا يتسابقون لإنقاذ عمال محاصرين داخل مصنع فرشات محترق. مع خروج النار عن السيطرة، يبذل الفريق كل ما في وسعه على أمل إخراج الضحايا المحاصرين بشكل آمن.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085463_LC_STB173554423.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E1</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123021500 +0000" stop="20210123030000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">Casey struggles to get Chief Boden to sign off on an energetic new recruit. Foster extends an olive branch to her irritating new medic. Otis inspires Herrmann to seek new partners at Molly's. Brett realises life in Fowlerton will take some getting used to. يكافح كيسي لجعل الرئيس بودن يوافق على توظيف شخص نشيط. تمد فوستر غصن الزيتون إلى المسعف الجديد المزعج. يُلهم اوتيس، هيرمان للبحث عن شركاء جدد في موليز. يدرك بريت أن الحياة في فاولارتن ستستغرق بعض الوقت للتعود عليها.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085464_LC_STB173526158.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E2</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123030000 +0000" stop="20210123043000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Good Morning America</title>
    <title lang="ar">غود مورنينغ أميريكا</title>
    <desc lang="en">ABC News' popular morning programme. Tune in to the show's award-winning combination of breaking news, hard hitting interviews, exclusive investigations, cutting-edge medical information, and financial reporting. إنه البرنامج الصباحي الشهير اي بي سي نيوز. استمع إلى الأخبار العاجلة والمقابلات القوية والتحقيقات الحصرية والمعلومات الطبية المتطورة والتقارير المالية من هذا البرنامج الحائز على جوائز عديدة.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/GoodMorningAmerica-l.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E82</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123043000 +0000" stop="20210123051500 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">Brett and Foster question the suspicious circumstances surrounding a brutal attack at a juvenile detention centre. A convoluted new technology installed inside Firehouse 51 tests everyone's patience. Kidd gets chosen to represent the district at a leadership conference. يتساءل بريت وفوستر عن الظروف المريبة المحيطة بهجوم وحشي على مركز احتجاز الأحداث. تختبر تقنية جديدة معقدة مثبتة داخل فايرهاوس 51 صبر الجميع. يتم اختيار كيد لتمثيل المنطقة في مؤتمر القيادة.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085465_LC_STB125215483.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E3</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123051500 +0000" stop="20210123060000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">A deadly bacteria takes its toll on many victims around the city, leaving Chicago's first responders to work alongside the CDC to resolve the situation. Following a fire at a university that ties into the outbreak, Severide has suspicions something bigger is happening. تسبب بكتيريا قاتلة في وفاة العديد من الضحايا في جميع أنحاء المدينة ، تاركةً أول المستجيبين في شيكاغو للعمل جنبًا إلى جنب مع مركز السيطرة على الأمراض لحل الوضع. بعد حريق في جامعة ترتبط بالفاشية ، يشك سيفارايد في حصول شيء أكبر.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085466_LC_STB125249537.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E4</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123060000 +0000" stop="20210123064500 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kidd must prove herself at the National Firefighter Leadership Conference while the rest of Firehouse 51 is called to two eerily similar car wrecks. Mouch tries to keep everyone in the firehouse informed by starting a newsletter, but things quickly get out of hand. يجب أن تثبت كيد نفسها في المؤتمر الوطني لقيادة رجال الإطفاء بينما يتم استدعاء بقية فايرهاوس 51 إلى حادثي سيارات متشابهتين بشكل غريب. يحاول موش إبقاء الجميع في غرفة الإطفاء، ولكن الأمور تخرج عن السيطرة بسرعة.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085467_LC_STB125506552.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E5</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123064500 +0000" stop="20210123073000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cruz and Severide suspect foul play when a fire started by an elderly woman turns deadly. Kidd, Foster and Brett create a women's-only lounge. Firehouse 51 celebrates some good news. يشتبه كروز و سيفرايد في حصول تلاعب ما عندما يتحول حريق بدأته امرأة مسنة إلى حدث مميت. ينشئ كيد و فوستر و بريت صالة مخصصة للنساء فقط. يحتفل فايرهاوس 51 ببعض الأخبار الجيدة.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085468_LC_STB125538470.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E6</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123073000 +0000" stop="20210123081500 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">Severide must make a tough decision about the future of his career at Firehouse 51. Herrmann deals with the consequences of his temper after a run-in with a Chicago cop. Cruz is excited to demonstrate the Slamigan at the Firefighting Expo. Commissioner Grissom returns. يجب على سيفرايد اتخاذ قرار صعب بشأن مستقبل حياته المهنية في فايرهاوس 51. يتعامل هيرمان مع عواقب مزاجه بعد لقاء مع شرطي في شيكاغو. يسرّ كروز بعرض سلامغن في معرض مكافحة الحرائق. كما ونشهد عودة المفوض جريسوم.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085469_LC_STB125608484.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E7</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123081500 +0000" stop="20210123090000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">Severide begins his assignment at the Office of Fire Investigation and gets off on the wrong foot when, despite his orders, he reopens an old case. When the cause of an apartment fire hits close to home, Herrmann is on a mission to get to the bottom of it. يبدأ سيفارايد مهمته في مكتب التحقيق في الحرائق، حيث يعيد فتح قضية قديمة، على الرغم من أوامر بعدم القيام بذلك. عندما يتبين أن مسبب الحريق شخص قريب منه، يتعين على هيرمان الوصول إلى الحقيقة.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085470_LC_STB125635893.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E8</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123090000 +0000" stop="20210123094500 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">An unexpected visit throws Casey for a loop. Severide sets out to exonerate a wrongly convicted arsonist. Kidd pays the price for burning the candle at both ends. Cruz goes on a mission to fix one of Otis's old toys. زيارة غير متوقعة تضع كاسي في دوامة. يشرع سيفريد في تبرئة شخص متهم بافتعال حريق. يدفع كيد ثمن على جميع الأصعدة. يذهب كروز في مهمة لإصلاح إحدى ألعاب أوتيس القديمة.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085471_LC_STB125724347.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E9</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123094500 +0000" stop="20210123103000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">Members of Firehouse 51 are dismayed to learn their boundaries have been redrawn to overlap with an adjacent station and problems quickly arise. Casey and Gallo hunt a missing piece of equipment. Brett and Foster find themselves at odds. إن أعضاء فايرهاوس 51 مستاؤون من معرفة أن حدودهم قد أعيد رسمها لتتداخل مع محطة مجاورة وتظهر المشاكل بسرعة. كاسي وجالو يبحثان عن قطعة مفقودة من المعدات. يجد بريت وفوستر نفسيهما على خلاف.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085472_LC_STB125813939.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E10</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123103000 +0000" stop="20210123111500 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">A pest control problem forces the 51 team to temporarily bunk with Firehouse 20. All under the same roof, Casey clashes with Capt. Delaney while Foster, Kidd and Brett fear Capt. Leone has it out for them. Boden mulls a procedural overhaul. تخبر مشكلة في مكافحة الحشرات الفريق 51 على التوقّف مؤقتًا عن استخدام فايرهاوس 20. بعد أن أصبح الجميع تحت سقف واحد، يتصادم كيسي مع الكابتن ديلاني، بينما يخشى فوستر وكيد وبريت من الكابتن. بودن يفكر في إصلاح إجرائي.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085473_LC_STB135028935.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E11</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123111500 +0000" stop="20210123120000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">A series of false alarms at a private school hinders the firehouse's ability to respond to legitimate emergency calls. Kidd asks for ideas to surprise Severide on his birthday. Cruz and Brett rent out their extra room, but the new tenant is more than they bargained for. تعوق سلسلة من الإنذارات الكاذبة في مدرسة خاصة القدرة على الاستجابة لمكالمات الطوارئ الحقيقية. يطلب كيد أفكارًا لمفاجأة سيفارايد في عيد ميلاده. يقوم كروز وبريت بتأجيرغرفتهما الإضافية ، لكن المستأجر الجديد كان أسوأ مما ساوما عليه.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085474_LC_STB135115906.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E12</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123120000 +0000" stop="20210123124500 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">The surprising arrival of a new fire truck brings both joy and chaos to members of Firehouse 51. Boden and Severide are asked to make peace with an old foe for the greater good. Brett receives family news while Foster plans a party with friends. يجلب الوصول المفاجئ لشاحنة إطفاء جديدة الفرح والفوضى لأعضاء فايرهاوس 51. يُطلب من بودين و سيفرايد التصالح مع عدو قديم من أجل الصالح العام. يتلقى بريت أخبارًا عائلية بينما يخطط فوستر لحفلة مع الأصدقاء.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085475_LC_STB135233594.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E13</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123124500 +0000" stop="20210123133000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">A series of mysterious gas leaks has members of Firehouse 51 puzzled and spread thin. Brett's conflicted when her birth mother gets serious about tracking her down. Severide misunderstands his role as Cruz's best man. Mouch bites off more than he can chew. سلسلة من تسريبات الغاز الغامضة تضع أعضاء فايرهاوس 51 في حيرة من امرهم. تأخذ والدة بريت الحقيقية مسألها تعقبها على محمل الجد. سفرايد يسيء فهم دوره كأشبين لـ كروز. يقع ماوث على اكثر مما يستطيع تحمله.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085476_LC_STB135334684.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E14</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123133000 +0000" stop="20210123141500 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">A series of teen opioid overdoses sees Severide partner with Sean Roman; but Severide begins to suspect there's more to the story than his old friend is telling him. Casey tries to be there for Brett as she considers her birth mother's offer to meet. بعد التبليغ عن سلسلة من حالات الجرعات الزائدة من المواد الأفيونية لدى مراهقين، يعمل سيفرايد مع شون رومان ؛ لكن سيفرايد بدأ يشك في أن هناك المزيد من الأمور أكثر مما يخبره به صديقه القديم. تحاول كيسي أن تكون هناك من أجل بريت وهي تنظر في عرض والدتها للقاء معاً.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085477_LC_STB135412108.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E15</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123141500 +0000" stop="20210123145700 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">Boden is on edge after starting a new fad diet. Casey and Severide disagree on a call. Brett's birth mother shares life-altering news. A familiar face has a proposition for Herrmann. بودين في حالة تأهب بعد بدء نظام غذائي جديد. لا يتفق كيسي وسيفرايد على المكالمة. تشارك والدة بريت أخبارًا غيرت مجرى الحياة. وجه مألوف لديه اقتراح لهيرمان.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085478_LC_STB135444400.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E16</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123145700 +0000" stop="20210123154000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">Things get personal for Casey and Gallo in the aftermath of a suburban house fire involving a mother and her young son. Herrmann campaigns for more respect. Kidd has an idea for giving back to her community. تصبح الأمور شخصية بالنسبة لـ كايسي وغالو في أعقاب حريق منزل في إحدى الضواحي شمل أمًا وابنها الصغير. يطلق هيرمان حملات لمزيد من الاحترام. لدى كيد فكرة لرد الجميل لمجتمعها.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085479_LC_STB135244990.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E17</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123154000 +0000" stop="20210123162500 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">Lt. Severide teams up with Seager and the OFI when a motel structure fire turns suspicious. Firehouse 51 members become amateur sleuths following a Reddit post involving one of their own. Brett continues to get invested in her birth mother, Julie. يتعاون الملازم سيفرايد مع سيجر ومكتب تحقيقات الحرائق للتحقيق في حريق فندق مريب و يقوم أعضاء مركز الإطفاء 51 بالتجسس على رديت بعد نشره لخبر يخص أحدهم و تتولى بريت رعاية أمها جولي.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085480_LC_STB135308904.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E18</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123162500 +0000" stop="20210123171000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">Tension builds when a group of rabble-rousers attempt to lock down the firehouse. Brett is faced with a monumental decision. Cruz readies himself for a big day. Gallo and Ritter attempt to launch Firehouse 51 into the social media age. يزداد التوتر عندما محاولة مجموعة من الرعاع إغلاق مركز الإطفاءو يتخذ بريت قرار مهم بينما يهيئ كروز نفسه ليوم عظيم و يعلن جالو و ريتر عن مركز الإطفاء 51 في  وسائل التواصل الاجتماعي.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085481_LC_STB135335612.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E19</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123171000 +0000" stop="20210123180000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">When one of 51's own gets injured on a call, Lt. Severide becomes obsessed with helping out. Foster contemplates a big decision. Kidd is concerned for one of her high school trainees. عندما يُصاب أحد أفراد الـ51 بجروح  يسرع الملازم سيفرايد  لتقديم المساعدة و يفكر فوستر مليا  باتخاذ قرار كبير و كيد قلقة على إحدى المتدربات في المدرسة الثانوية.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085482_LC_STB135406110.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E20</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123180000 +0000" stop="20210123190000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Great</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غرايت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Catherine decides to move forward with the coup on her birthday. Peter isn't so easily overcome and holds Leo hostage as collateral. Marial betrays Catherine to Peter. Catherine realises the only chance for a greater Russia is to fight, without Leo. The battle begins. قررت كاثرين المضي قدمًا في الانقلاب في عيد ميلادها.ولكن ليس من السهل التغلب على بيتر خاصةً بعد احتجازه ليو كرهينة. تخون ماريال كاثرين مما جعلها تدرك أن الفرصة الوحيدة لروسيا العظيمة هي القتال. وبدون ليو تبدأ المعركة.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/the-great-s1-l.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E10</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123190000 +0000" stop="20210123200000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Industry</title>
    <title lang="ar">انداستري</title>
    <desc lang="en">After a tumultuous few months at Pierpoint, the graduates take vastly different approaches to prove they're worthy of permanent positions. After an unexpected meeting with a familiar face, Harper contends with a decision that could transform the culture of Pierpoint. بعد بضعة أشهر صاخبة في بيربوينت ، يتخذ الخريجون مناهج مختلفة إلى حد كبير لإثبات أنهم يستحقون مناصب دائمة. بعد لقاء غير متوقع مع وجه مألوف ، يواجه `` هاربر '' قرارًا قد يغير ثقافة `` بيربوينت ''.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR088879_LC_STB.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E8</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123200000 +0000" stop="20210123203000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Girls</title>
    <title lang="ar">غيرلز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Marni seeks out Ray's opinion of her, but her response is a bit pathetic and desperate, which ultimately proves Ray's point. Meanwhile, Caroline is creating tension in the apartment, and Hannah finds a new editor, but her previous publisher won't release her book. تحاول مارني معرفة رأي راي بها، ولكنها تبدي ردة فعل يائسة ومثيرة للشفقة، وهو ما يثبت صحة رأيه في نهاية المطاف. وفي هذه الأثناء، تتسبب كارولين بإثارة التوتر في المنزل، وتعثر هانا على محرر جديد، ولكن الناشر السابق الذي تعاملت معه يرفض نشر كتابها.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR052597_LC_STB.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E5</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123203000 +0000" stop="20210123210000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Girls</title>
    <title lang="ar">غيرلز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hannah quits the coffee shop to work in the advertorial section of GQ magazine. Meanwhile, Shoshanna is desperate to move on from Ray after stalking him and so gets herself a new boyfriend, whilst Jessa has begun work at the clothes shop. تستقيل هانا من العمل في المقهى وتنتقل إلى قسم الإعلانات في مجلة جي كيو. وفي هذه الأثناء، تحاول شوشانا بكل جهد التغلب على مشاعرها تجاه راي لذا تبحث عن صديق حميم جديد، بينما تلتحق جيسا في عملها الجديد في متجر ملابس.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR052597_LC_STB.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E6</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123210000 +0000" stop="20210123215000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Quarry</title>
    <title lang="ar">كواري</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mac gets a high-profile assignment from The Broker. A curfew is ordered in the wake of racial unrest. يحصل ماك على مهمة رفيعة المستوى من ذا بروكر، بينما يتم حظر التجول في أعقاب الاضطرابات العنصرية.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR049162_LC_STB.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E6</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123215000 +0000" stop="20210123223200 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">When we last saw our heroes they were racing to rescue workers trapped inside of a burning mattress factory. As the fire spirals out of control, truck and squad lay it on the line in hopes of getting the trapped victims out alive. عندما رأينا أبطالنا آخر مرة كانوا يتسابقون لإنقاذ عمال محاصرين داخل مصنع فرشات محترق. مع خروج النار عن السيطرة، يبذل الفريق كل ما في وسعه على أمل إخراج الضحايا المحاصرين بشكل آمن.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085463_LC_STB173554423.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E1</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123223200 +0000" stop="20210123231500 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">Casey struggles to get Chief Boden to sign off on an energetic new recruit. Foster extends an olive branch to her irritating new medic. Otis inspires Herrmann to seek new partners at Molly's. Brett realises life in Fowlerton will take some getting used to. يكافح كيسي لجعل الرئيس بودن يوافق على توظيف شخص نشيط. تمد فوستر غصن الزيتون إلى المسعف الجديد المزعج. يُلهم اوتيس، هيرمان للبحث عن شركاء جدد في موليز. يدرك بريت أن الحياة في فاولارتن ستستغرق بعض الوقت للتعود عليها.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085464_LC_STB173526158.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E2</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210123231500 +0000" stop="20210124000000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Killing Eve</title>
    <title lang="ar">كيلينغ إيف</title>
    <desc lang="en">Eve is reeling from her act of violence against Villanelle and doesn't know whether she is alive or dead. A paranoid and severely injured Villanelle manages to get herself to the hospital for treatment. Carolyn approaches Eve with an intriguing opportunity. تعاني إيف من أعمال العنف التي ارتكبتها ضد فيلانيل ولا تعرف ما إذا كانت على قيد الحياة أم ميتة. تتمكن فيلانيل المصابة بجروح خطيرة من نقل نفسها إلى المستشفى لتلقي العلاج. تقدم كارولين لـ إيف فرصة رائعة.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR081702_LC_STB134427498.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E1</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124000000 +0000" stop="20210124004500 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">A deadly bacteria takes its toll on many victims around the city, leaving Chicago's first responders to work alongside the CDC to resolve the situation. Following a fire at a university that ties into the outbreak, Severide has suspicions something bigger is happening. تسبب بكتيريا قاتلة في وفاة العديد من الضحايا في جميع أنحاء المدينة ، تاركةً أول المستجيبين في شيكاغو للعمل جنبًا إلى جنب مع مركز السيطرة على الأمراض لحل الوضع. بعد حريق في جامعة ترتبط بالفاشية ، يشك سيفارايد في حصول شيء أكبر.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085466_LC_STB125249537.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E4</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124004500 +0000" stop="20210124013000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kidd must prove herself at the National Firefighter Leadership Conference while the rest of Firehouse 51 is called to two eerily similar car wrecks. Mouch tries to keep everyone in the firehouse informed by starting a newsletter, but things quickly get out of hand. يجب أن تثبت كيد نفسها في المؤتمر الوطني لقيادة رجال الإطفاء بينما يتم استدعاء بقية فايرهاوس 51 إلى حادثي سيارات متشابهتين بشكل غريب. يحاول موش إبقاء الجميع في غرفة الإطفاء، ولكن الأمور تخرج عن السيطرة بسرعة.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085467_LC_STB125506552.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E5</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124013000 +0000" stop="20210124021500 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">Cruz and Severide suspect foul play when a fire started by an elderly woman turns deadly. Kidd, Foster and Brett create a women's-only lounge. Firehouse 51 celebrates some good news. يشتبه كروز و سيفرايد في حصول تلاعب ما عندما يتحول حريق بدأته امرأة مسنة إلى حدث مميت. ينشئ كيد و فوستر و بريت صالة مخصصة للنساء فقط. يحتفل فايرهاوس 51 ببعض الأخبار الجيدة.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085468_LC_STB125538470.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E6</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124021500 +0000" stop="20210124030000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">Severide must make a tough decision about the future of his career at Firehouse 51. Herrmann deals with the consequences of his temper after a run-in with a Chicago cop. Cruz is excited to demonstrate the Slamigan at the Firefighting Expo. Commissioner Grissom returns. يجب على سيفرايد اتخاذ قرار صعب بشأن مستقبل حياته المهنية في فايرهاوس 51. يتعامل هيرمان مع عواقب مزاجه بعد لقاء مع شرطي في شيكاغو. يسرّ كروز بعرض سلامغن في معرض مكافحة الحرائق. كما ونشهد عودة المفوض جريسوم.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085469_LC_STB125608484.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E7</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124030000 +0000" stop="20210124042000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Good Morning America - The Weekend</title>
    <title lang="ar">غود مورنينغ أميركا - ذا وييكأند</title>
    <desc lang="en">Broadcasting from the ABC studios in New York, this Emmy award-winning news show brings viewers daily, up-to-the-minute breaking news and weather, as well as topical feature stories. يقدم البرنامج في بث يومي مباشر من استوديوهات إي بي سي في نيويورك. يجلب هذا البرنامج الإخباري الفائز بجائزة إيمي الأخبار العاجلة يومياً وأخبار حالة الطقس، فضلاً عن الكثير من القصص المختلفة.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/OSN-Series.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E33</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124042000 +0000" stop="20210124050500 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">Severide begins his assignment at the Office of Fire Investigation and gets off on the wrong foot when, despite his orders, he reopens an old case. When the cause of an apartment fire hits close to home, Herrmann is on a mission to get to the bottom of it. يبدأ سيفارايد مهمته في مكتب التحقيق في الحرائق، حيث يعيد فتح قضية قديمة، على الرغم من أوامر بعدم القيام بذلك. عندما يتبين أن مسبب الحريق شخص قريب منه، يتعين على هيرمان الوصول إلى الحقيقة.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085470_LC_STB125635893.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E8</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124050500 +0000" stop="20210124055000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">An unexpected visit throws Casey for a loop. Severide sets out to exonerate a wrongly convicted arsonist. Kidd pays the price for burning the candle at both ends. Cruz goes on a mission to fix one of Otis's old toys. زيارة غير متوقعة تضع كاسي في دوامة. يشرع سيفريد في تبرئة شخص متهم بافتعال حريق. يدفع كيد ثمن على جميع الأصعدة. يذهب كروز في مهمة لإصلاح إحدى ألعاب أوتيس القديمة.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085471_LC_STB125724347.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E9</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124055000 +0000" stop="20210124063500 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Chicago Fire</title>
    <title lang="ar">شيكاغو فاير</title>
    <desc lang="en">Members of Firehouse 51 are dismayed to learn their boundaries have been redrawn to overlap with an adjacent station and problems quickly arise. Casey and Gallo hunt a missing piece of equipment. Brett and Foster find themselves at odds. إن أعضاء فايرهاوس 51 مستاؤون من معرفة أن حدودهم قد أعيد رسمها لتتداخل مع محطة مجاورة وتظهر المشاكل بسرعة. كاسي وجالو يبحثان عن قطعة مفقودة من المعدات. يجد بريت وفوستر نفسيهما على خلاف.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085472_LC_STB125813939.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E10</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124063500 +0000" stop="20210124072000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Baywatch Hawaii</title>
    <title lang="ar">باي واتش هاواي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Disaster hits the training centre when Zack accidentally knocks out all the power and telecommunications equipment while trying to load his new web site. Meanwhile, Jason must play wet nurse to a spoiled rich girl out to escape from her father's clutches. تحل كارثة في المركز عندما يضرب زاك عن طريق الخطأ جميع أجهزة الإتصال والطاقة أثناء تحميله لموقعه الإليكتروني الجديد. بينما يجب على جيسون أن تلعب دور الممرضة الرقيقة لفتاة ثرية مدللة للهروب من براثن والدها.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR082229_LC_STB.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E17</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124072000 +0000" stop="20210124085000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Voice</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا فويس</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Top 9 artists perform in front of Coaches Kelly Clarkson, John Legend, Blake Shelton and Gwen Stefani for their chance at a spot in the finale; the artists share special dedications and fans are featured throughout. يقدم أفضل 9 فنانين عرضًا أمام المدربين كيلي كلاركسون وجون ليجند وبليك شيلتون وجوين ستيفاني للحصول على فرصة في مكان في النهائي.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR083947_LC_STB.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E15</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124085000 +0000" stop="20210124093500 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Falling Skies</title>
    <title lang="ar">فولينغ سكايز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Attempting to dig out a shot-down Beamer, Tom and a small team follow the Volm to a supply cache in search of equipment to expedite the process. Back at camp, Ben teaches Maggie to hone her new skills, while Pope and Sara have a fight from which they may never recover. يلحق توم وفريق صغير بفولم إلى مخبأ الإمدادات بحثا عن تجهيزات لتسريع العملية. وبالعودة إلى المخيم، تتوطد العلاقة بين ماغي وبين بينما يعلمها طريقة صقل مهاراتها الجديدة، بينما تتواصل الصدامات بين بوب وسارة.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR041114_LC_STB.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E9</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124093500 +0000" stop="20210124102000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <title lang="ar">لوو أند أوردر: سبيشال فيكتمز يونيت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kat steps over the line when she suspects a trainer at her boxing gym is taking advantage of his students. تتخطى كات الخط عندما تشك في أن مدربًا في صالة الملاكمة يستغل طلابه.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085535_LC_STB.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E13</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124102000 +0000" stop="20210124110500 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Baywatch Hawaii</title>
    <title lang="ar">باي واتش هاواي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Disaster hits the training centre when Zack accidentally knocks out all the power and telecommunications equipment while trying to load his new web site. Meanwhile, Jason must play wet nurse to a spoiled rich girl out to escape from her father's clutches. تحل كارثة في المركز عندما يضرب زاك عن طريق الخطأ جميع أجهزة الإتصال والطاقة أثناء تحميله لموقعه الإليكتروني الجديد. بينما يجب على جيسون أن تلعب دور الممرضة الرقيقة لفتاة ثرية مدللة للهروب من براثن والدها.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR082229_LC_STB.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E17</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124110500 +0000" stop="20210124123500 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Voice</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا فويس</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Top 9 artists perform in front of Coaches Kelly Clarkson, John Legend, Blake Shelton and Gwen Stefani for their chance at a spot in the finale; the artists share special dedications and fans are featured throughout. يقدم أفضل 9 فنانين عرضًا أمام المدربين كيلي كلاركسون وجون ليجند وبليك شيلتون وجوين ستيفاني للحصول على فرصة في مكان في النهائي.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR083947_LC_STB.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E15</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124123500 +0000" stop="20210124130500 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Avenue 5</title>
    <title lang="ar">آفنيو 5</title>
    <desc lang="en">While Karen oversees an effort to jettison non-essential items, Billie tries to teach Ryan how to dock the ship. Matt learns of Judd's plan to make the "ultimate sacrifice" by returning to Earth. Meanwhile, the passengers suspect all is not as it seems with the journey. بينما تشرف كارين على محاولة التخلص من العناصر غير الضرورية ، تحاول بيلي تعليم ريان كيفية إرساء السفينة. مات يكتشف خطة جود لتنفيذ "التضحية النهائية" من خلال العودة إلى الأرض. في الوقت نفسه ، يشك الركاب في أن ليس كل شيء كما يبدو أثناء الرحلة.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR082052_LC_STB.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E8</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124130500 +0000" stop="20210124135500 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Good Morning America - The Weekend</title>
    <title lang="ar">غود مورنينغ أميركا - ذا وييكأند</title>
    <desc lang="en">Broadcasting from the ABC studios in New York, this Emmy award-winning news show brings viewers daily, up-to-the-minute breaking news and weather, as well as topical feature stories. يقدم البرنامج في بث يومي مباشر من استوديوهات إي بي سي في نيويورك. يجلب هذا البرنامج الإخباري الفائز بجائزة إيمي الأخبار العاجلة يومياً وأخبار حالة الطقس، فضلاً عن الكثير من القصص المختلفة.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/OSN-Series.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E34</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124135500 +0000" stop="20210124144000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Falling Skies</title>
    <title lang="ar">فولينغ سكايز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Attempting to dig out a shot-down Beamer, Tom and a small team follow the Volm to a supply cache in search of equipment to expedite the process. Back at camp, Ben teaches Maggie to hone her new skills, while Pope and Sara have a fight from which they may never recover. يلحق توم وفريق صغير بفولم إلى مخبأ الإمدادات بحثا عن تجهيزات لتسريع العملية. وبالعودة إلى المخيم، تتوطد العلاقة بين ماغي وبين بينما يعلمها طريقة صقل مهاراتها الجديدة، بينما تتواصل الصدامات بين بوب وسارة.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR041114_LC_STB.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E9</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124144000 +0000" stop="20210124153000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <title lang="ar">لوو أند أوردر: سبيشال فيكتمز يونيت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kat steps over the line when she suspects a trainer at her boxing gym is taking advantage of his students. تتخطى كات الخط عندما تشك في أن مدربًا في صالة الملاكمة يستغل طلابه.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085535_LC_STB.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E13</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124153000 +0000" stop="20210124162000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Supernatural</title>
    <title lang="ar">سوبرناتشورال</title>
    <desc lang="en">It's the final ride for saving people and hunting things. إنها الرحلة الأخيرة لإنقاذ الناس وصيد الأشياء.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR085558_LC_STB.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E20</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124162000 +0000" stop="20210124171000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Sinner</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا سينر</title>
    <desc lang="en">As Ambrose looks into Jamie and Nick's relationship before the crash, Jamie begins to unravel. بينما ينظر أمبروز في علاقة جيمي ونيك قبل التحطم ، يبدأ جيمي في الانهيار.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/the-sinner-s3-l.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E2</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124171000 +0000" stop="20210124180500 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Homeland</title>
    <title lang="ar">هوملاند</title>
    <desc lang="en">Upheaval in Washington brings an investigation to Kabul. اضطراب في واشنطن العاصمة يستدعي تحقيقاً إلى كابول.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR081091_LC_STB.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E6</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124180500 +0000" stop="20210124190000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">Game Of Thrones</title>
    <title lang="ar">غايم أوف ثرونز</title>
    <desc lang="en">At Castle Black, Thorne defends his treason while Edd and Davos defend themselves. Sansa and Theon race the cold and the hounds. Cersei sees her daughter again. في كاسل بلاك، يدافع ثرون عن خيانته بينما يدافع إد ودافوس عن أنفسهما. وفي مكان آخر، تحاول سانسا وثيون تحدي البرد ومن يقومون بمطاردتهما، بينما ترى سيرسي ابنتها مجددا.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/SR043772_LC_STB.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E1</episode-num>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20210124190000 +0000" stop="20210124200000 +0000" channel="OSN Series HD">
    <title lang="en">The Leftovers</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا ليفتاوفرز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Laurie and Tom Garvey's work to rescue lost souls takes a toll on theirs. Laurie seeks to spread the word about the Guilty Remnant's dangers, while Tom's infiltration of the cult uncovers a whole new nest of problems. عمل لوري وتوم غارفي على إنقاذ الأرواح التائهة يؤثر سلبا على روحيهما. تسعى لوري لنشر الخبر عن مخاطر البقية المذنبين، في حين يتسبب توم بكشف عدد جديد من المشاكل.</desc>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/bob/745x419/the-leftovers-s2-e03-l2.jpg" />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E3</episode-num>
  </programme>
</tv>