<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB &amp; REX Postprocess -- version V3.1.1.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
  <channel id="OSN Movies First HD">
    <display-name lang="en">OSN Movies First HD</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/OM1.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <display-name lang="en">OSN Movies First HD2</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/OMX.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <display-name lang="en">OSN Movies Action HD</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/AHD.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="OSN Movies HD">
    <display-name lang="en">OSN Movies HD</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/OPR.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="OSN POP">
    <display-name lang="en">OSN POP</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/POP.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="OSN Enigma">
    <display-name lang="en">OSN Enigma</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/OCM.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <display-name lang="en">OSN Movies Kids HD</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/OMK.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <display-name lang="en">OSN Movies Disney HD</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/OFM.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Paramount">
    <display-name lang="en">Paramount</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/PAR.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Star Movies HD">
    <display-name lang="en">Star Movies HD</display-name>
    <icon src="http://content.osn.com/logo/channel/cropped/STM.png" />
    <url>http://www.osn.com</url>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20201013000500 +0000" stop="20201013014000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">The Edge</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا إيدج</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Edge is a prime time technology news show produced by CNBC. The program targets long-term investors seeking emerging trends in technology and innovation. برنامج من إنتاج سي أن بي سي، يتعلق بآخر ما توصلت إليه التكنولوجيا حالياً. يستهدف برنامج ذا إيدج المستثمرين الذين يبحثون عن الاستثمارات طويلة المدى في الاتجاهات الناشئة المتعلقة بالتكنولوجيا والابداع.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013014000 +0000" stop="20201013031000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">Love At The Shore</title>
    <title lang="ar">لاف آت ذا شور</title>
    <desc lang="en">Single mom Jenna Thompson only five weeks to deliver her next teen novel to her publisher. So, this year's annual beach vacation with her kids will be a working vacation. Upon arrival, the family soon meets their new next-door neighbor, confident, Lucas McKinnon. تستعد جينا تومسون الأم العزباء والناجحة في مجال كتابة روايات المراهقين من أجل تسليم روايتها الجديدة ، ولكن تتغير كافة الأمور بعد ذهابها مع أبنائها لقضاء العطلة عندما تتقابل مع جارها لوكاس ماكينون.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013031000 +0000" stop="20201013043000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">The Addams Family</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا آدمز فاملي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. After relocating to suburban New Jersey, the Addams family prepares for a major celebration that involves their extended family while maneuvering around the machinations of a devious reality-television host. Oscar Isaac and Charlize Theron are voice talents. رسوم متحركة. بعد الانتقال إلى ريف نيوجيرسي، تستعد عائلة أدامز لاقامة إحتفال كبير يضم  أفراد الأسرة الممتدة. في الآن ذاته، يحاولون التخلص من مكائد مقدم لبرنامج تلفزيوني واقعي. بصوت أوسكار إسحاق وتشارليز ثيرون.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013043000 +0000" stop="20201013063000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">Sgt. Will Gardner</title>
    <title lang="ar">سيرجينت ويل غاردنر</title>
    <desc lang="en">A troubled Iraq War veteran struggling to reintegrate into society sets out on a cross-country journey with the hope of reuniting with his young son. ينطلق أحد المحاربين القدامى في حرب العراق  والذي كان يصارع لإعادة الإندماج في المجتمع في رحلة عبر البلاد على أمل الإجتماع مجدداً بإبنه الصغير.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013063000 +0000" stop="20201013075500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">A Dash Of Love</title>
    <title lang="ar">ايه داش أوف لاف</title>
    <desc lang="en">Drama. A young woman who dreams of opening her own restaurant lands a job at a prominent restaurant whose head chef becomes her unlikely ally when the owner plots to return the place to its former glory by presenting her new assistant's recipes as her own. دراما. تحلم فتاة شابة في تنفيذ مشروعها وإفتتاح مطعم خاص بها إلى أن تحصل على وظيفة في مطعم شهير وعندما يقوم صاحب المطاعم بسرقة وصفاتها، تتحالف مع رئيس الطهاة ويبدأن رحلتهما معاً إلى أن يتغير كل شىء.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013075500 +0000" stop="20201013092100 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">Truly, Madly, Sweetly</title>
    <title lang="ar">ترولي، مادلي، سويتلي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Romantic Drama. Natalie, a cupcake food truck owner has always dreamed of owning her own bakery. Eric has always wanted his own business. When an inheritance throws these two opposites together, neither could have imagined what fate had in store for them. دراما رومانسية.تحلم ناتالي صاحبة شاحنة الحلويات بإمتلاك مخبز خاص بها، بينما كان لدى إيريك طموحاته الخاصة المختلفة، ولكن حينما يلقي إرث الثنائي في طريق بعضهما البعض، يظهر القدر لهما ما لم يكن في الحسبان.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013092100 +0000" stop="20201013112500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">Captain Marvel</title>
    <title lang="ar">كابتن مارفل</title>
    <desc lang="en">The story follows Carol Danvers as she becomes one of the universe’s most powerful heroes when Earth is caught in the middle of a galactic war between two alien races. تدور القصة حول تحول كارول دانفيرز إلى أحد أقوى الأبطال الخارقين في الكون عندما يعلق كوكب الأرض بحرب مستعرة ومدمرة بين جنسين من المخلوقات الفضائية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013112500 +0000" stop="20201013130000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">Off The Menu</title>
    <title lang="ar">أوف ذا منيو</title>
    <desc lang="en">An unlikely heir to a Mexican fast-food franchise goes 'cuisine' hunting for the next culinary big thing, and finds himself in a small, dusty New Mexican town where foodies come from all over the world to salivate over the culinary treats of a local, authentic, and feis. يذهب وريث سلسلة المطاعم المكسيكية للوجبات السريعة في رحلة للبحث عن مشروع طبخ جديد ليجد نفسه في بلدة مكسيكية صغيرة يأتي إليها محبي الطعام من جميع أنجاء العالم لتذوق أطباق مطعم محلى أصلي تمتلكه فتاة مشاغبة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013130000 +0000" stop="20201013144500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">Rememory</title>
    <title lang="ar">ريميموري</title>
    <desc lang="en">Drama. The widow of a wise professor stumbles upon one of his inventions that's able to record and play a person's memory. دراما. تعثر أرملة البروفيسور الحكيم على أحد إختراعاته القادرة على تسجيل وتشغيل ذاكرة الشخص.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013144500 +0000" stop="20201013161500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">The Man Who Killed Hitler And Then The Bigfoot</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذي مان هو كيلد هتلر اند ذين ذي بيغ فوت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Decades after serving in WWII and assassinating Adolf Hitler, a legendary American war veteran Calvin Barr must now hunt down a mythical creature. Relying on the same skills that he honed during the war, Calvin must set out to save the world again. مغامرة. بعد عقود من الخدمة في الحرب العالمية الثانية واغتيال أدولف هتلر، يجب على الأمريكي الأسطوري المخضرم في الحرب كالفين بار أن يطارد مخلوقًا أسطوريًا. بالاعتماد على نفس المهارات التي شحذها خلال الحرب، يجب على كالفن الشروع في إنقاذ العالم مرة أخرى.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013161500 +0000" stop="20201013180000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">Cats</title>
    <title lang="ar">كاتس</title>
    <desc lang="en">A tribe of cats called the Jellicles must decide yearly which one will ascend to the Heaviside Layer and come back to a new Jellicle life. يجب أن تقرر قبيلة من القطط تسمى جيلكلس كل سنة أي واحدة منهم سترتقي إلى هافر سايد لاير وتعود إلى حياة جيلكلس جديدة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013180000 +0000" stop="20201013194500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">Killerman</title>
    <title lang="ar">كيلرمان</title>
    <desc lang="en">A New York City money launderer desperately searches for answers after waking up with no memory, millions in stolen cash and drugs, and an insane crew of dirty cops violently hunting him down. يبحث تاجر في غسيل الأموال في مدينة نيويورك بشكل يائس عن إجابات بعد الاستيقاظ ليجد نفسه فاقدا لذاكرته. الملايين من الأموال النقدية والمخدرات المسروقة، وفريق مجنون من رجال الشرطة القذرين يطاردونه بعنف.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013194500 +0000" stop="20201013194500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">The Lighthouse</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا لايتهاوس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Drama. Two lighthouse keepers try to maintain their sanity while living on a remote and mysterious New England island in the 1890s. يحاول حارسا منارة الحفاظ على سلامتهما أثناء العيش في جزيرة نيو إنجلاند النائية والغامضة في تسعينيات القرن التاسع عشر.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013194500 +0000" stop="20201013213000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">The Lighthouse</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا لايتهاوس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Drama. Two lighthouse keepers try to maintain their sanity while living on a remote and mysterious New England island in the 1890s. يحاول حارسا منارة الحفاظ على سلامتهما أثناء العيش في جزيرة نيو إنجلاند النائية والغامضة في تسعينيات القرن التاسع عشر.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013213000 +0000" stop="20201013230500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">The Festival</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا فستيفال</title>
    <desc lang="en">Comedy. After Nick's girlfriend dumps him, his best mate Shane has the perfect antidote to his break-up blues, three days at an epic music festival. كوميديا.يقوم شين أعز صديق لنيك بمساعدته في تخطي محنته بعد ترك حبيبته له عن طريق قضاء ثلاثة أيام في مهرجان موسيقي مذهل.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013230500 +0000" stop="20201014003500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">A Dash Of Love</title>
    <title lang="ar">ايه داش أوف لاف</title>
    <desc lang="en">Drama. A young woman who dreams of opening her own restaurant lands a job at a prominent restaurant whose head chef becomes her unlikely ally when the owner plots to return the place to its former glory by presenting her new assistant's recipes as her own. دراما. تحلم فتاة شابة في تنفيذ مشروعها وإفتتاح مطعم خاص بها إلى أن تحصل على وظيفة في مطعم شهير وعندما يقوم صاحب المطاعم بسرقة وصفاتها، تتحالف مع رئيس الطهاة ويبدأن رحلتهما معاً إلى أن يتغير كل شىء.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014003500 +0000" stop="20201014022000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">Tales From The Hood 2</title>
    <title lang="ar">تيلز فروم ذا هود 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Comedy. Mr. Simms returns to tell more eerie, unsettling tales involving dolls, psychics, possession and ghosts. كوميديا. يعود السيد سيمز ليحكي المزيد من القصص المخيفة والمقلقة حول الدمي، الأرواح والأشباح.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014022000 +0000" stop="20201014034500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">Truly, Madly, Sweetly</title>
    <title lang="ar">ترولي، مادلي، سويتلي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Romantic Drama. Natalie, a cupcake food truck owner has always dreamed of owning her own bakery. Eric has always wanted his own business. When an inheritance throws these two opposites together, neither could have imagined what fate had in store for them. دراما رومانسية.تحلم ناتالي صاحبة شاحنة الحلويات بإمتلاك مخبز خاص بها، بينما كان لدى إيريك طموحاته الخاصة المختلفة، ولكن حينما يلقي إرث الثنائي في طريق بعضهما البعض، يظهر القدر لهما ما لم يكن في الحسبان.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014034500 +0000" stop="20201014052000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">Off The Menu</title>
    <title lang="ar">أوف ذا منيو</title>
    <desc lang="en">An unlikely heir to a Mexican fast-food franchise goes 'cuisine' hunting for the next culinary big thing, and finds himself in a small, dusty New Mexican town where foodies come from all over the world to salivate over the culinary treats of a local, authentic, and feis. يذهب وريث سلسلة المطاعم المكسيكية للوجبات السريعة في رحلة للبحث عن مشروع طبخ جديد ليجد نفسه في بلدة مكسيكية صغيرة يأتي إليها محبي الطعام من جميع أنجاء العالم لتذوق أطباق مطعم محلى أصلي تمتلكه فتاة مشاغبة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014052000 +0000" stop="20201014070500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">Rememory</title>
    <title lang="ar">ريميموري</title>
    <desc lang="en">Drama. The widow of a wise professor stumbles upon one of his inventions that's able to record and play a person's memory. دراما. تعثر أرملة البروفيسور الحكيم على أحد إختراعاته القادرة على تسجيل وتشغيل ذاكرة الشخص.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014070500 +0000" stop="20201014083000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">Home By Spring</title>
    <title lang="ar">هوم باي سبرينغ</title>
    <desc lang="en">Romantic Drama. When an ambitious event planner gets an opportunity she can't refuse, she goes undercover as her boss and returns to her rural hometown. but will she discover home is where her heart is? دراما رومانسية. عندما تتاح الفرصة لمخططة حفلات طموحة لا يمكنها رفضها ، تتخفى بشخصية مديرها وتعود إلى مسقط رأسها في الريف. ولكن هل تكتشف أنها يجب أن تعيش حيث يكون قلبها؟.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014083000 +0000" stop="20201014101500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">Cats</title>
    <title lang="ar">كاتس</title>
    <desc lang="en">A tribe of cats called the Jellicles must decide yearly which one will ascend to the Heaviside Layer and come back to a new Jellicle life. يجب أن تقرر قبيلة من القطط تسمى جيلكلس كل سنة أي واحدة منهم سترتقي إلى هافر سايد لاير وتعود إلى حياة جيلكلس جديدة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014101500 +0000" stop="20201014115000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">Love Locks</title>
    <title lang="ar">لاف لوكس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Romance. Lindsey Wilson first found love in the romantic city of Paris when she was a university student studying art there. Now, twenty years later, she is returning to the City of Light to take her daughter on an adventure there. بعد عشرون عامًا من إبتعادها عن باريس، تعود ليندسي ويلسون مع ابنتها في مغامرة إلى مدينة الأضواء التي قابلت فيها حبها الأول عندما كانت تدرس هناك .</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014115000 +0000" stop="20201014133500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">Frozen II</title>
    <title lang="ar">فروزن 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. Elsa, Anna, Kristoff and Olaf leave Arendelle to travel to an ancient, autumn-bound forest of an enchanted land to know the truth about an ancient mystery of their kingdom. رسوم متحركة. يغادر كل من إلسا، أنا، كريستوف وأولاف مملكة أرندال ويتجهون نحو غابة سحرية غامضة لمعرفة حقيقة لغز قديم في مملكتهم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014133500 +0000" stop="20201014150500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">Teen Spirit</title>
    <title lang="ar">تين سبيريت</title>
    <desc lang="en">A shy teenager living on the Isle of Wight dreams of pop stardom. With the help of an unlikely mentor, she enters a singing competition that will test her integrity, talent, and ambition. تشارك الفتاة الخجولة والتي كانت تحلم بالنجومية بجزيرة وايت في مسابقة غنائية لإختبار لياقتها، موهبتها وطموحها بمساعدة مرشدتها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014150500 +0000" stop="20201014163500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">Finding Steve McQueen</title>
    <title lang="ar">فايندينغ ستيف ماكوين</title>
    <desc lang="en">Crime. In 1972, a gang of close-knit thieves from Youngstown, Ohio attempt to steal $30 million in illegal contributions. Based on the true story of the biggest bank heist in US history. تدور الأحداث في عام 1972 عندما حاولت مجموعة من اللصوص المترابطين من يونغزتاون، بولاية أوهايو سرقة 30 مليون دولار من التبرعات الغير قانونية،. يستند الفيلم على قصة سرقة أكبر بنك في تاريخ الولايات المتحدة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014163500 +0000" stop="20201014180000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">Here And Now</title>
    <title lang="ar">هير أند ناو</title>
    <desc lang="en">A singer in New York gets a grim diagnosis that puts her life and dreams into perspective. دراما. تتلقى مطربة شغوفة في نيويورك تشخيصاً مقبضاً لحالتها الصحية مما يضع حياتها وأحلامها في حيز التنفيذ.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014180000 +0000" stop="20201014200500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD">
    <title lang="en">Spider-Man: Far From Home</title>
    <title lang="ar">سبايدر-مان: فار فروم هوم</title>
    <desc lang="en">Peter Parker and his friends go on a summer trip to Europe. He will have to agree to help Nick Fury uncover the mystery of creatures that cause natural disasters and destruction throughout the continent. يذهب بيتر باركر وأصدقائه في رحلة صيفية إلى أوروبا. يجب على بيتر الموافقة على مساعدة نيك فيوري على كشف سر المخلوقات التي تسبب الكوارث الطبيعية والدمار في جميع أنحاء القارة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013002000 +0000" stop="20201013020500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">Backtrace</title>
    <title lang="ar">باكتريس</title>
    <desc lang="en">A violent robber battling chronic amnesia, an experimental drug designed to recuperate his memories of a bank heist, a local detective, and a hardened FBI agent. يدخل سارق عنيف في صراع مع مرض فقدان الذاكرة المزمن، عقار تجريبي مصمم لاستعادة ذكرياته عن سرقة أحد البنوك، محقق محلي، وعامل في مكتب التحقيقات الفيدرالي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013020500 +0000" stop="20201013034000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">The Edge</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا إيدج</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Edge is a prime time technology news show produced by CNBC. The program targets long-term investors seeking emerging trends in technology and innovation. برنامج من إنتاج سي أن بي سي، يتعلق بآخر ما توصلت إليه التكنولوجيا حالياً. يستهدف برنامج ذا إيدج المستثمرين الذين يبحثون عن الاستثمارات طويلة المدى في الاتجاهات الناشئة المتعلقة بالتكنولوجيا والابداع.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013034000 +0000" stop="20201013051000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">Love At The Shore</title>
    <title lang="ar">لاف آت ذا شور</title>
    <desc lang="en">Single mom Jenna Thompson only five weeks to deliver her next teen novel to her publisher. So, this year's annual beach vacation with her kids will be a working vacation. Upon arrival, the family soon meets their new next-door neighbor, confident, Lucas McKinnon. تستعد جينا تومسون الأم العزباء والناجحة في مجال كتابة روايات المراهقين من أجل تسليم روايتها الجديدة ، ولكن تتغير كافة الأمور بعد ذهابها مع أبنائها لقضاء العطلة عندما تتقابل مع جارها لوكاس ماكينون.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013051000 +0000" stop="20201013063000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">The Addams Family</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا آدمز فاملي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. After relocating to suburban New Jersey, the Addams family prepares for a major celebration that involves their extended family while maneuvering around the machinations of a devious reality-television host. Oscar Isaac and Charlize Theron are voice talents. رسوم متحركة. بعد الانتقال إلى ريف نيوجيرسي، تستعد عائلة أدامز لاقامة إحتفال كبير يضم  أفراد الأسرة الممتدة. في الآن ذاته، يحاولون التخلص من مكائد مقدم لبرنامج تلفزيوني واقعي. بصوت أوسكار إسحاق وتشارليز ثيرون.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013063000 +0000" stop="20201013083000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">Sgt. Will Gardner</title>
    <title lang="ar">سيرجينت ويل غاردنر</title>
    <desc lang="en">A troubled Iraq War veteran struggling to reintegrate into society sets out on a cross-country journey with the hope of reuniting with his young son. ينطلق أحد المحاربين القدامى في حرب العراق  والذي كان يصارع لإعادة الإندماج في المجتمع في رحلة عبر البلاد على أمل الإجتماع مجدداً بإبنه الصغير.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013083000 +0000" stop="20201013095500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">A Dash Of Love</title>
    <title lang="ar">ايه داش أوف لاف</title>
    <desc lang="en">Drama. A young woman who dreams of opening her own restaurant lands a job at a prominent restaurant whose head chef becomes her unlikely ally when the owner plots to return the place to its former glory by presenting her new assistant's recipes as her own. دراما. تحلم فتاة شابة في تنفيذ مشروعها وإفتتاح مطعم خاص بها إلى أن تحصل على وظيفة في مطعم شهير وعندما يقوم صاحب المطاعم بسرقة وصفاتها، تتحالف مع رئيس الطهاة ويبدأن رحلتهما معاً إلى أن يتغير كل شىء.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013095500 +0000" stop="20201013112100 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">Truly, Madly, Sweetly</title>
    <title lang="ar">ترولي، مادلي، سويتلي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Romantic Drama. Natalie, a cupcake food truck owner has always dreamed of owning her own bakery. Eric has always wanted his own business. When an inheritance throws these two opposites together, neither could have imagined what fate had in store for them. دراما رومانسية.تحلم ناتالي صاحبة شاحنة الحلويات بإمتلاك مخبز خاص بها، بينما كان لدى إيريك طموحاته الخاصة المختلفة، ولكن حينما يلقي إرث الثنائي في طريق بعضهما البعض، يظهر القدر لهما ما لم يكن في الحسبان.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013112100 +0000" stop="20201013132500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">Captain Marvel</title>
    <title lang="ar">كابتن مارفل</title>
    <desc lang="en">The story follows Carol Danvers as she becomes one of the universe’s most powerful heroes when Earth is caught in the middle of a galactic war between two alien races. تدور القصة حول تحول كارول دانفيرز إلى أحد أقوى الأبطال الخارقين في الكون عندما يعلق كوكب الأرض بحرب مستعرة ومدمرة بين جنسين من المخلوقات الفضائية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013132500 +0000" stop="20201013150000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">Off The Menu</title>
    <title lang="ar">أوف ذا منيو</title>
    <desc lang="en">An unlikely heir to a Mexican fast-food franchise goes 'cuisine' hunting for the next culinary big thing, and finds himself in a small, dusty New Mexican town where foodies come from all over the world to salivate over the culinary treats of a local, authentic, and feis. يذهب وريث سلسلة المطاعم المكسيكية للوجبات السريعة في رحلة للبحث عن مشروع طبخ جديد ليجد نفسه في بلدة مكسيكية صغيرة يأتي إليها محبي الطعام من جميع أنجاء العالم لتذوق أطباق مطعم محلى أصلي تمتلكه فتاة مشاغبة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013150000 +0000" stop="20201013164500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">Rememory</title>
    <title lang="ar">ريميموري</title>
    <desc lang="en">Drama. The widow of a wise professor stumbles upon one of his inventions that's able to record and play a person's memory. دراما. تعثر أرملة البروفيسور الحكيم على أحد إختراعاته القادرة على تسجيل وتشغيل ذاكرة الشخص.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013164500 +0000" stop="20201013181500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">The Man Who Killed Hitler And Then The Bigfoot</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذي مان هو كيلد هتلر اند ذين ذي بيغ فوت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Decades after serving in WWII and assassinating Adolf Hitler, a legendary American war veteran Calvin Barr must now hunt down a mythical creature. Relying on the same skills that he honed during the war, Calvin must set out to save the world again. مغامرة. بعد عقود من الخدمة في الحرب العالمية الثانية واغتيال أدولف هتلر، يجب على الأمريكي الأسطوري المخضرم في الحرب كالفين بار أن يطارد مخلوقًا أسطوريًا. بالاعتماد على نفس المهارات التي شحذها خلال الحرب، يجب على كالفن الشروع في إنقاذ العالم مرة أخرى.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013181500 +0000" stop="20201013200000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">Cats</title>
    <title lang="ar">كاتس</title>
    <desc lang="en">A tribe of cats called the Jellicles must decide yearly which one will ascend to the Heaviside Layer and come back to a new Jellicle life. يجب أن تقرر قبيلة من القطط تسمى جيلكلس كل سنة أي واحدة منهم سترتقي إلى هافر سايد لاير وتعود إلى حياة جيلكلس جديدة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013200000 +0000" stop="20201013200000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">Killerman</title>
    <title lang="ar">كيلرمان</title>
    <desc lang="en">A New York City money launderer desperately searches for answers after waking up with no memory, millions in stolen cash and drugs, and an insane crew of dirty cops violently hunting him down. يبحث تاجر في غسيل الأموال في مدينة نيويورك بشكل يائس عن إجابات بعد الاستيقاظ ليجد نفسه فاقدا لذاكرته. الملايين من الأموال النقدية والمخدرات المسروقة، وفريق مجنون من رجال الشرطة القذرين يطاردونه بعنف.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013200000 +0000" stop="20201013214500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">Killerman</title>
    <title lang="ar">كيلرمان</title>
    <desc lang="en">A New York City money launderer desperately searches for answers after waking up with no memory, millions in stolen cash and drugs, and an insane crew of dirty cops violently hunting him down. يبحث تاجر في غسيل الأموال في مدينة نيويورك بشكل يائس عن إجابات بعد الاستيقاظ ليجد نفسه فاقدا لذاكرته. الملايين من الأموال النقدية والمخدرات المسروقة، وفريق مجنون من رجال الشرطة القذرين يطاردونه بعنف.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013214500 +0000" stop="20201013233000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">The Lighthouse</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا لايتهاوس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Drama. Two lighthouse keepers try to maintain their sanity while living on a remote and mysterious New England island in the 1890s. يحاول حارسا منارة الحفاظ على سلامتهما أثناء العيش في جزيرة نيو إنجلاند النائية والغامضة في تسعينيات القرن التاسع عشر.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013233000 +0000" stop="20201014010500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">The Festival</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا فستيفال</title>
    <desc lang="en">Comedy. After Nick's girlfriend dumps him, his best mate Shane has the perfect antidote to his break-up blues, three days at an epic music festival. كوميديا.يقوم شين أعز صديق لنيك بمساعدته في تخطي محنته بعد ترك حبيبته له عن طريق قضاء ثلاثة أيام في مهرجان موسيقي مذهل.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014010500 +0000" stop="20201014023500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">A Dash Of Love</title>
    <title lang="ar">ايه داش أوف لاف</title>
    <desc lang="en">Drama. A young woman who dreams of opening her own restaurant lands a job at a prominent restaurant whose head chef becomes her unlikely ally when the owner plots to return the place to its former glory by presenting her new assistant's recipes as her own. دراما. تحلم فتاة شابة في تنفيذ مشروعها وإفتتاح مطعم خاص بها إلى أن تحصل على وظيفة في مطعم شهير وعندما يقوم صاحب المطاعم بسرقة وصفاتها، تتحالف مع رئيس الطهاة ويبدأن رحلتهما معاً إلى أن يتغير كل شىء.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014023500 +0000" stop="20201014042000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">Tales From The Hood 2</title>
    <title lang="ar">تيلز فروم ذا هود 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Comedy. Mr. Simms returns to tell more eerie, unsettling tales involving dolls, psychics, possession and ghosts. كوميديا. يعود السيد سيمز ليحكي المزيد من القصص المخيفة والمقلقة حول الدمي، الأرواح والأشباح.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014042000 +0000" stop="20201014054500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">Truly, Madly, Sweetly</title>
    <title lang="ar">ترولي، مادلي، سويتلي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Romantic Drama. Natalie, a cupcake food truck owner has always dreamed of owning her own bakery. Eric has always wanted his own business. When an inheritance throws these two opposites together, neither could have imagined what fate had in store for them. دراما رومانسية.تحلم ناتالي صاحبة شاحنة الحلويات بإمتلاك مخبز خاص بها، بينما كان لدى إيريك طموحاته الخاصة المختلفة، ولكن حينما يلقي إرث الثنائي في طريق بعضهما البعض، يظهر القدر لهما ما لم يكن في الحسبان.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014054500 +0000" stop="20201014072000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">Off The Menu</title>
    <title lang="ar">أوف ذا منيو</title>
    <desc lang="en">An unlikely heir to a Mexican fast-food franchise goes 'cuisine' hunting for the next culinary big thing, and finds himself in a small, dusty New Mexican town where foodies come from all over the world to salivate over the culinary treats of a local, authentic, and feis. يذهب وريث سلسلة المطاعم المكسيكية للوجبات السريعة في رحلة للبحث عن مشروع طبخ جديد ليجد نفسه في بلدة مكسيكية صغيرة يأتي إليها محبي الطعام من جميع أنجاء العالم لتذوق أطباق مطعم محلى أصلي تمتلكه فتاة مشاغبة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014072000 +0000" stop="20201014090500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">Rememory</title>
    <title lang="ar">ريميموري</title>
    <desc lang="en">Drama. The widow of a wise professor stumbles upon one of his inventions that's able to record and play a person's memory. دراما. تعثر أرملة البروفيسور الحكيم على أحد إختراعاته القادرة على تسجيل وتشغيل ذاكرة الشخص.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014090500 +0000" stop="20201014103000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">Home By Spring</title>
    <title lang="ar">هوم باي سبرينغ</title>
    <desc lang="en">Romantic Drama. When an ambitious event planner gets an opportunity she can't refuse, she goes undercover as her boss and returns to her rural hometown. but will she discover home is where her heart is? دراما رومانسية. عندما تتاح الفرصة لمخططة حفلات طموحة لا يمكنها رفضها ، تتخفى بشخصية مديرها وتعود إلى مسقط رأسها في الريف. ولكن هل تكتشف أنها يجب أن تعيش حيث يكون قلبها؟.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014103000 +0000" stop="20201014121500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">Cats</title>
    <title lang="ar">كاتس</title>
    <desc lang="en">A tribe of cats called the Jellicles must decide yearly which one will ascend to the Heaviside Layer and come back to a new Jellicle life. يجب أن تقرر قبيلة من القطط تسمى جيلكلس كل سنة أي واحدة منهم سترتقي إلى هافر سايد لاير وتعود إلى حياة جيلكلس جديدة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014121500 +0000" stop="20201014135000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">Love Locks</title>
    <title lang="ar">لاف لوكس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Romance. Lindsey Wilson first found love in the romantic city of Paris when she was a university student studying art there. Now, twenty years later, she is returning to the City of Light to take her daughter on an adventure there. بعد عشرون عامًا من إبتعادها عن باريس، تعود ليندسي ويلسون مع ابنتها في مغامرة إلى مدينة الأضواء التي قابلت فيها حبها الأول عندما كانت تدرس هناك .</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014135000 +0000" stop="20201014153500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">Frozen II</title>
    <title lang="ar">فروزن 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. Elsa, Anna, Kristoff and Olaf leave Arendelle to travel to an ancient, autumn-bound forest of an enchanted land to know the truth about an ancient mystery of their kingdom. رسوم متحركة. يغادر كل من إلسا، أنا، كريستوف وأولاف مملكة أرندال ويتجهون نحو غابة سحرية غامضة لمعرفة حقيقة لغز قديم في مملكتهم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014153500 +0000" stop="20201014170500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">Teen Spirit</title>
    <title lang="ar">تين سبيريت</title>
    <desc lang="en">A shy teenager living on the Isle of Wight dreams of pop stardom. With the help of an unlikely mentor, she enters a singing competition that will test her integrity, talent, and ambition. تشارك الفتاة الخجولة والتي كانت تحلم بالنجومية بجزيرة وايت في مسابقة غنائية لإختبار لياقتها، موهبتها وطموحها بمساعدة مرشدتها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014170500 +0000" stop="20201014183500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">Finding Steve McQueen</title>
    <title lang="ar">فايندينغ ستيف ماكوين</title>
    <desc lang="en">Crime. In 1972, a gang of close-knit thieves from Youngstown, Ohio attempt to steal $30 million in illegal contributions. Based on the true story of the biggest bank heist in US history. تدور الأحداث في عام 1972 عندما حاولت مجموعة من اللصوص المترابطين من يونغزتاون، بولاية أوهايو سرقة 30 مليون دولار من التبرعات الغير قانونية،. يستند الفيلم على قصة سرقة أكبر بنك في تاريخ الولايات المتحدة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014183500 +0000" stop="20201014200000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies First HD2">
    <title lang="en">Here And Now</title>
    <title lang="ar">هير أند ناو</title>
    <desc lang="en">A singer in New York gets a grim diagnosis that puts her life and dreams into perspective. دراما. تتلقى مطربة شغوفة في نيويورك تشخيصاً مقبضاً لحالتها الصحية مما يضع حياتها وأحلامها في حيز التنفيذ.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013002500 +0000" stop="20201013022500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">Blood Punch</title>
    <title lang="ar">بلاد بانش</title>
    <desc lang="en">Horror Thriller, Milton, The young man who lured into a dangerous love triangle that begins to take a series of shocking and grisly supernatural turns with no end...and no escape. إثارة ورعب.يُجذب ميلتون إلى مثلث حب خطير يبدأ في إتخاذ سلسلة من المنعطفات المروعة والخارقة للطبيعة التي لا تنتهي ولا مفر منها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013022500 +0000" stop="20201013044000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">The Magnificent Seven</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا ماغنيفيسنت سيفن</title>
    <desc lang="en">Action with Steve McQueen and Charles Bronson. Seven American mercenaries are hired to protect a Mexican village, terrorized by the bandit Calvera (Eli Wallach) and his gun blazing goons. The bandits suffer casualties, but regroup to capture the seven gunmen. أكشن من بطولة ماكوين، تشارلز برونسون، وإيلي والاش. يتم استئجار سبعة أفراد من المرتزقين الأمريكيين من أجل حماية قرية صغيرة بالمكسيك تتعرض لأعمال إرهابية من قبل العصابات المسلحة المغيرة.  ولكن بعد تعرض العصابات للإصابة يحاولون إستعادة قواتهم من أجل التخلص من الحماة المسلح.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013044000 +0000" stop="20201013064000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">Tai Chi 2: The Hero Rises</title>
    <title lang="ar">تاي تشي 2: ذا هيرو رايزز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Action. Lu Chan's is still trying to find his place in his new home but his presence in Chen Village invokes a curse on the town. أكشن. لايزال لو تشان يحاول العثور على مكانه في منزله الجديد ولكن يتسبب وجوده في قرية تشن في تعرض المدينة للعنة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013064000 +0000" stop="20201013091000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">Avengers: Age Of Ultron</title>
    <title lang="ar">أفنجرز: أيج أوف ألترون</title>
    <desc lang="en">The superheroes deal with a threat of their own making: a sentient robot called Ultron. Originally designed as part of a peacekeeping programme, Ultron believes peace can only be achieved by exterminating humanity. يتصدى الأبطال الخارقين لتهديد من صنع أيديهم، وهو روبوت ذكي يدعى ألترون، سبق أن تم تصميمه كجزء من برنامج لصنع السلام، لكن ألترون يعتقد أن السلام لا يمكن تحقيقه إلا من خلال القضاء على البشرية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013091000 +0000" stop="20201013111000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">War Of The Worlds</title>
    <title lang="ar">وور أوف ذا ووردز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Based on H.G Wells seminal classic, the adventure reveals the extraordinary battle for the future of human kind through the eyes of one family fighting to survive it. Sci-Fi starring Tom Cruise and Dakota Fanning. مقتبسة  عن رواية اتش جي ويلز الكلاسيكية، مغامرة تكشف عن المعركة الاستثنائية  التي تصور مستقبل النوع البشري من خلال رؤية أسرة تصارع للبقاء على قيد الحياة.خيال علمي من بطولة توم كروز و داكوتا فاننغ.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013111000 +0000" stop="20201013125500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">Escape Of Prisoner 614</title>
    <title lang="ar">إسكيب أوف بريزونر 614</title>
    <desc lang="en">Two inept, small-town Sheriff's Deputies catch an escaped prisoner that they believe was wrongly convicted. بعد تعيين رقيبين في بلدة صغيرة للقبض على سجين هارب، ولكن سرعان ما يشكان أنه بريء.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013125500 +0000" stop="20201013145500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">Ant-Man</title>
    <title lang="ar">آنت-مان</title>
    <desc lang="en">Superhero action. Armed with the astonishing ability to shrink in scale but increase in strength, con artist Scott Lang (Paul Rudd) and his mentor Pym (Michael Douglas) must plan and pull off a heist against seemingly insurmountable obstacles in order to save the world. إثارة خارقة. بعدما يتم تسليحه بقدرة مذهلة على التقلص بالحجم والتفوق بالقوة، يتوجب على المخادع سكوت لانغ (بول راد) وناصحه بيم (مايكل دوغلاس) تخطيط وتنفيذ عملية سرقة في ظل مجموعة من العقبات المستعصية لإنقاذ العالم. (آنت-مان).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013145500 +0000" stop="20201013170000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">Die Hard 2</title>
    <title lang="ar">داي هارد 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Action thriller starring Bruce Willis, William Sadler, Bonnie Bedelia. On Christmas Eve, one year after his heroics in L.A., detective John McClane attempts to avert disaster as rogue military operatives seize control of Dulles International Airport in Washington, D.C. أكشن وإثارة من بطولة بروس ويليس، ويليام سادلر وبوني بيديليا. عشية عيد الميلاد، وبعد مرور عام على أعماله البطولية في لوس أنجلوس، يحاول المحقق جون ماكلين تجنب وقوع كارثة بينما يسعى عملاء عسكريون محتالون للسيطرة على مطار دالاس الدولي في العاصمة واشنطون.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013170000 +0000" stop="20201013190000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">Escape Plan</title>
    <title lang="ar">إسكيب بلان</title>
    <desc lang="en">Action. A structural security expert (Sylvester Stallone) must escape from a prison built based on his own designs. At first it looks like he's finally been beaten at his own game, until he meets a con (Arnold Schwarzenegger) equally determined on regaining his freedom. آكشن. يجب على خبير أنظمة أمنية (سيلفستر ستالون) الهروب من سجن تم بناؤه اعتمادا على تصميماته. في البداية يبدو أنه قد هزم في لعبته، إلى أن يقابل محتال (آرنولد شوارزنيغر) لديه نفس القدر من الرغبة في الهروب واستعادة حريته.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013190000 +0000" stop="20201013205500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">Speed</title>
    <title lang="ar">سبيد</title>
    <desc lang="en">Fast paced action with Keanu Reeves, Sandra Bullock and Dennis Hopper. Seeking vengeance after his latest ransom scheme is thwarted, a bomber wires a city bus to detonate at the point the speedometer drops below 50mph. فيلم آكشن من بطولة كيانو ريفز، ساندرا بولوك ودينيس هوبر. في السعي وراء الإنتقام بعد أن تم إحباط خطة الفدية الأخيرة له، يقوم خبير متفجرات بوضع قنبلة في باص المواصلات، حيث تنفجر في حال قلت سرعة الباص عن 50 ميل في الساعة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013205500 +0000" stop="20201013205500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">The Mechanic</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا ميكانيك</title>
    <desc lang="en">Action. An aging hitman befriends a young man who wants to be a professional killer. Eventually it becomes clear that someone has betrayed them. إثارة. يصادق قاتل طاعن في السن شابًا يريد أن يكون قاتلًا محترفًا. لكن في النهاية، يتضح أن شخصًا ما قد خانهما.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013205500 +0000" stop="20201013223500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">The Mechanic</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا ميكانيك</title>
    <desc lang="en">Action. An aging hitman befriends a young man who wants to be a professional killer. Eventually it becomes clear that someone has betrayed them. إثارة. يصادق قاتل طاعن في السن شابًا يريد أن يكون قاتلًا محترفًا. لكن في النهاية، يتضح أن شخصًا ما قد خانهما.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013223500 +0000" stop="20201014002000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">The Viking War</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا فاينكنغ وور</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ingrid and her siblings must resist the invasion of the Beserkers who want to seize their village. However, they are caught off-guard when they realise that the Beserkers want to play a violent game. يجب أن تقاوم إنجريد وإخوتها غزو البيسركيرز الذين يريدون الاستيلاء على قريتهم ولكن يتفاجئون عندما يدركوا أن البيسركيرز يريدون اللعب بعنف.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014002000 +0000" stop="20201014014500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">Prey</title>
    <title lang="ar">براي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Horror Adventure. A young man must survive an island retreat while a sinister force hunts him, leaving bodies in its wake. رعب ومغامرة. يجب على شاب أن ينجو بنفسه بينما تطارده قوة شريرة، تاركة الجثث في أعقابها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014014500 +0000" stop="20201014034500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">Ant-Man</title>
    <title lang="ar">آنت-مان</title>
    <desc lang="en">Superhero action. Armed with the astonishing ability to shrink in scale but increase in strength, con artist Scott Lang (Paul Rudd) and his mentor Pym (Michael Douglas) must plan and pull off a heist against seemingly insurmountable obstacles in order to save the world. إثارة خارقة. بعدما يتم تسليحه بقدرة مذهلة على التقلص بالحجم والتفوق بالقوة، يتوجب على المخادع سكوت لانغ (بول راد) وناصحه بيم (مايكل دوغلاس) تخطيط وتنفيذ عملية سرقة في ظل مجموعة من العقبات المستعصية لإنقاذ العالم. (آنت-مان).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014034500 +0000" stop="20201014055000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">Die Hard 2</title>
    <title lang="ar">داي هارد 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Action thriller starring Bruce Willis, William Sadler, Bonnie Bedelia. On Christmas Eve, one year after his heroics in L.A., detective John McClane attempts to avert disaster as rogue military operatives seize control of Dulles International Airport in Washington, D.C. أكشن وإثارة من بطولة بروس ويليس، ويليام سادلر وبوني بيديليا. عشية عيد الميلاد، وبعد مرور عام على أعماله البطولية في لوس أنجلوس، يحاول المحقق جون ماكلين تجنب وقوع كارثة بينما يسعى عملاء عسكريون محتالون للسيطرة على مطار دالاس الدولي في العاصمة واشنطون.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014055000 +0000" stop="20201014074000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">Beyond White Space</title>
    <title lang="ar">بيوند وايت سبيس</title>
    <desc lang="en">When a deep space fishing vessel is robbed by a gang of pirates, the Captain makes a daring decision to go after a rare and nearly extinct species. His obsession propels them further into space as the crew spins toward mutiny and betrayal. عندما تتعرض سفينة فضاء للصيد  للسرقة من قبل عصابة من القراصنة عندها يتخذ القبطان قرارا  شجاعا بملاحقة نوع نادر وشبه منقرض و يدفعه هوسه إلى التوغل عميقا في الفضاء وهذا يسبب الى ميل الطاقم  الى التمرد والخيانة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014074000 +0000" stop="20201014094000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">Escape Plan</title>
    <title lang="ar">إسكيب بلان</title>
    <desc lang="en">Action. A structural security expert (Sylvester Stallone) must escape from a prison built based on his own designs. At first it looks like he's finally been beaten at his own game, until he meets a con (Arnold Schwarzenegger) equally determined on regaining his freedom. آكشن. يجب على خبير أنظمة أمنية (سيلفستر ستالون) الهروب من سجن تم بناؤه اعتمادا على تصميماته. في البداية يبدو أنه قد هزم في لعبته، إلى أن يقابل محتال (آرنولد شوارزنيغر) لديه نفس القدر من الرغبة في الهروب واستعادة حريته.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014094000 +0000" stop="20201014114000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">Speed</title>
    <title lang="ar">سبيد</title>
    <desc lang="en">Fast paced action with Keanu Reeves, Sandra Bullock and Dennis Hopper. Seeking vengeance after his latest ransom scheme is thwarted, a bomber wires a city bus to detonate at the point the speedometer drops below 50mph. فيلم آكشن من بطولة كيانو ريفز، ساندرا بولوك ودينيس هوبر. في السعي وراء الإنتقام بعد أن تم إحباط خطة الفدية الأخيرة له، يقوم خبير متفجرات بوضع قنبلة في باص المواصلات، حيث تنفجر في حال قلت سرعة الباص عن 50 ميل في الساعة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014114000 +0000" stop="20201014131000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">American Ninja II: The Confrontation</title>
    <title lang="ar">أميركن نينجا 2: ذا كنفرونتيشن</title>
    <desc lang="en">Action. On a remote Caribbean island, Army Ranger Joe Armstrong (Michael Dudikoff) saves an old friend from the clutches of "The Lion. آكشن. يقوم جندي أمريكي (مايكل دوديكوف) بإنقاذ إبنة كولونيل (جودي آرونسون)، ويحارب مقاتلي النينجا الذين يقومون بحماية تاجر أسلحة في الفيليبين.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014131000 +0000" stop="20201014154000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">Captain America: Civil War</title>
    <title lang="ar">كابتن أمريكا: سيفل وور</title>
    <desc lang="en">Political interference in the Avengers' activities causes a rift between former allies Captain America and Iron Man, forcing the denizens of the Marvel Universe to choose sides when the disagreement escalates into an all-out war. يتسبب التدخل السياسي في أنشطة فريق أفينجرز بحدوث انقسام بين الحليفين السابقين كابتن أميريكا وآيرون مان، الأمر الذي يجبر القاطنين في مارفل يونيفرس على الاختيار بين الطرفين.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014154000 +0000" stop="20201014172500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">Iceman</title>
    <title lang="ar">آيس مان</title>
    <desc lang="en">Action. An imperial guard from the Ming Dynasty and his three traitorous friends become buried and frozen in time. When they wake up 400 years later, they continue the battle they started centuries before. Donnie Yen, Baoqiang Wang and Shengyi Huang star. أكشن من بطولة دوني ين ، باوكيانج وانغ وشنيغي هوانغ.. أصبح حارس إمبراطوري من سلالة مينغ وأصدقائه الثلاثة الخائنين مدفونين ومجمدين في الوقت المناسب. وعندما يستيقظون بعد 400 عام ، يواصلون المعركة التي بدأوها قبل قرون.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014172500 +0000" stop="20201014190000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">Escape Plan 2: Hades</title>
    <title lang="ar">إسكيب بلان 2: هيدز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Action. Years after he fought his way out of an inescapable prison, Ray Breslin has organized a new top-notch security force. But when one of his team members goes missing, Breslin must return to the hell he once escaped from. أكشن. يقوم راي بريسلين بتنظيم قوة أمنية جديدة وممتازة بعد مرور سنين من مكافحته للخروج من سجن لا يمكن الهروب منه. ولكنه يضطر للعودة إلى ذلك الجحيم بعد إختفاء أحد أعضاء فريقه.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014190000 +0000" stop="20201014205000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Action HD">
    <title lang="en">The Rookies</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذي رووكيز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Extreme sport lover Zhou Feng got involved in an international illegal trade by accident. So he had to follow an international special agent Bruce to Budapest. تورط عاشق الرياضة تشو فنغ في تجارة دولية غير قانونية عن طريق الصدفة. لذلك كان عليه أن يتبع بروس, وكيل دولي خاص إلى بودابست.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013004000 +0000" stop="20201013021500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Penny Pincher</title>
    <title lang="ar">باني بينشر</title>
    <desc lang="en">Comedy, Franois Gautier is stingy! Saving puts the joy, it causes pay sweats. His life is set for the sole purpose of never spend anything. A life that will switch in one day, he falls in love and discovers he has a daughter he did not know existed. كوميدي. تتغير حياة الرجل البخيل عندما يقع في حب فتاة ويعلم بأن لديه ابنه لم يكن يعلم أي شىء عن وجودها من قبل.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013021500 +0000" stop="20201013035500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Indian Summer</title>
    <title lang="ar">إنديان سامر</title>
    <desc lang="en">Comedy. Seven friends reunite for a week-long reunion at a summer camp in Ontario they used to attend as children which is now threatened with being closed down. كوميديا. مجموعة أصدقاء يجتمعون لقضاء اسبوع تخييم في مكان مميز في أونتاريو حيث اعتادوا التخييم في طفولتهم, واللذي هو الآن مهدد بالإغلاق.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013035500 +0000" stop="20201013053500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Mr. Popper's Penguins</title>
    <title lang="ar">مستر بوبرز بنغوينز</title>
    <desc lang="en">A businessman, clueless when it comes to the important things in life, inherits six penguins that turn his swank apartment into a snowy winter wonderland and the rest of his life upside-down. يرث رجل أعمال، جاهل في الأمور الأساسية في الحياة، ستة بطاريق يقومون بتحويل شقته الفارهة إلى شتاء مُثلج، ويقلبون حياته رأسا على عقب.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013053500 +0000" stop="20201013074500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">The Express</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذي اكسبريس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Biopic starring Rob Brown and Dennis Quaid based on the life of college football hero Ernie Davis who was the first African-American to win the Heisman Trophy, in a time when the civil rights movement was gaining steam. دراما مقتبسة عن قصة حياة إيرني ديفس بطل دوري الجامعات في كرة القدم الأميريكية، وأول لاعب أميريكي من أصل أفريقي يفوز بكأس هايزمان. بطولة دنيس كايد وروب براون ومن إخراج غاري فليدر.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013074500 +0000" stop="20201013094000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Overboard</title>
    <title lang="ar">اوفربورد</title>
    <desc lang="en">Comedy with Goldie Hawn, Kurt Russell. When a snooty heiress falls overboard her yacht and develops amnesia, the redneck carpenter she haughtily dismissed without payment decides to seek his revenge and remedy his own domestic problems by claiming her as his wife. كوميدي من بطولة غولدي هون وكيرت راسل. عندما تسقط وريثة متعجرفة على سطح يختها وتفقد ذاكرتها، يقرر النجار الذي صرفته بغطرسة ومن دون أن تدفع له أتعابه أن ينتقم ويعالج مشاكله المنزلية الخاصة من خلال الإدعاء أنها زوجته.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013094000 +0000" stop="20201013112500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Mum's List</title>
    <title lang="ar">مامز ليست</title>
    <desc lang="en">Drama with Emilia Fox. A woman dying of incurable breast cancer creates a list of memories and lessons for the husband and sons she is about to leave behind. دراما من بطولة إيمليا فوكس. تترك الأم المحتضرة التي تعانى من سرطان الثدي قائمة من الذكريات ودروس في الحياة لزوجها وأبنائها قبل رحيلها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013112500 +0000" stop="20201013132500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">The Music Of Silence</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا ميوزيك أوف سايلنس</title>
    <desc lang="en">A biopic of world-renowned opera singer Andrea Bocelli (Toby Sebastian), depicting his struggle to pursue his passion for music, despite the fact that he was born with a severe eye condition that caused him to go blind at a young age. فيلم السيرة الذاتية لمغني الأوبرا العالمي المشهور أندريا بوتشيلي( توبي سيباستيان)، وكفاحه لتحقيق أحلامه والسعي وراء شغفه للموسيقى على الرغم من ولادته بمرض شديد في عيونه تسبب في إصابته بالعمى منذ سن مبكرة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013132500 +0000" stop="20201013151500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Endless Love</title>
    <title lang="ar">أندلاس لوف</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this adaptation of the 1979 novel by Scott Spencer, passion yields to tragedy when the parents of a privileged girl attempt to thwart her heated romance with a handsome valet. . في هذا الفيلم المقتبس من رواية سكوت سبنسر التي نشرها في عام 1979، تحل المأساة محل الشغف عندما يحاول والدا فتاة ثرية إفشال العلاقة الرومانسية التي تربطها بخادم وسيم .</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013151500 +0000" stop="20201013173000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">The Two Jakes</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا تو جيكس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Private eye Jake, now middle-aged, is about to marry a beautiful young lady until a voice from the past causes him to get involved again. 'Chinatown' sequel directed by and starring Jack Nicholson, with Harvey Keitel. المخبر السري جيك، الذي بلغ منتصف العمر،وعلى وشك الزواج بصبية حسناء،  سمع صوتاً من الماضي يناديه ليتورط بعمله من جديد. هارفي كيتل. إخراج وبطولة جاك نيكلسن الذي أخرج سلسة افلام تشاينا تاون.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013173000 +0000" stop="20201013193000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Collateral</title>
    <title lang="ar">كولاترل</title>
    <desc lang="en">A cab driver finds himself the hostage of an engaging contract killer as he makes his rounds from hit to hit during one night in LA. He must find a way to save both himself and one last victim. يقع سائق تاكسي رهينةَ قاتل مأجور بينما كان هذا الأخير ينتقل في إحدى الليالي من عملية إلى عملية أخرى في نيويورك.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013193000 +0000" stop="20201013193000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">The American</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا أميريكان</title>
    <desc lang="en">In the aftermath of a job gone awry, an American assassin retreats to the Italian countryside where he befriends a local priest and strikes up a romance while awaiting his next assignment. عقب سير العمل بشكل خاطئ، يقوم سفاح أمريكي بالانسحاب إلى الريف الإيطالي حيث يتصادق مع كاهن محلي ويبدأ قصة رومانسية بانتظار مهمته الجديدة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013193000 +0000" stop="20201013211500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">The American</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا أميريكان</title>
    <desc lang="en">In the aftermath of a job gone awry, an American assassin retreats to the Italian countryside where he befriends a local priest and strikes up a romance while awaiting his next assignment. عقب سير العمل بشكل خاطئ، يقوم سفاح أمريكي بالانسحاب إلى الريف الإيطالي حيث يتصادق مع كاهن محلي ويبدأ قصة رومانسية بانتظار مهمته الجديدة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013211500 +0000" stop="20201013225000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Romans</title>
    <title lang="ar">رومانز</title>
    <desc lang="en">An adult victim of childhood sexual abuse confronts the horrors of his past. يتناول الفيلم قصة شاب كان ضحية للإعتداء الجنسي في صغره، ويتحتم عليه الآن مواجهة أهوال الماضي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013225000 +0000" stop="20201014002000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Crazy People</title>
    <title lang="ar">كرايزي بيبول</title>
    <desc lang="en">Comedy. A bitter advertising executive Emory Leeson (Dudley Moore) who has reached his breaking point, finds himself in a mental institution where his career actually begins to thrive when he develops a crush on a fellow patient, Kathy Burgess (Daryl Hannah). كوميدي. إموري ليسن (دادلي مور)، مدير إعلاني يصل إلى نقطة الانهيار ويجد نفسه داخل مصح عقلي، لتنقلب حياته وتزدهر مهنته هناك بعدما يقع بإعجاب مريضة تدعى كاثي بيرغس (داريل هانا).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014002000 +0000" stop="20201014021000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Mum's List</title>
    <title lang="ar">مامز ليست</title>
    <desc lang="en">Drama with Emilia Fox. A woman dying of incurable breast cancer creates a list of memories and lessons for the husband and sons she is about to leave behind. دراما من بطولة إيمليا فوكس. تترك الأم المحتضرة التي تعانى من سرطان الثدي قائمة من الذكريات ودروس في الحياة لزوجها وأبنائها قبل رحيلها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014021000 +0000" stop="20201014041000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">The Music Of Silence</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا ميوزيك أوف سايلنس</title>
    <desc lang="en">A biopic of world-renowned opera singer Andrea Bocelli (Toby Sebastian), depicting his struggle to pursue his passion for music, despite the fact that he was born with a severe eye condition that caused him to go blind at a young age. فيلم السيرة الذاتية لمغني الأوبرا العالمي المشهور أندريا بوتشيلي( توبي سيباستيان)، وكفاحه لتحقيق أحلامه والسعي وراء شغفه للموسيقى على الرغم من ولادته بمرض شديد في عيونه تسبب في إصابته بالعمى منذ سن مبكرة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014041000 +0000" stop="20201014060000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Endless Love</title>
    <title lang="ar">أندلاس لوف</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this adaptation of the 1979 novel by Scott Spencer, passion yields to tragedy when the parents of a privileged girl attempt to thwart her heated romance with a handsome valet. . في هذا الفيلم المقتبس من رواية سكوت سبنسر التي نشرها في عام 1979، تحل المأساة محل الشغف عندما يحاول والدا فتاة ثرية إفشال العلاقة الرومانسية التي تربطها بخادم وسيم .</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014060000 +0000" stop="20201014073500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Penny Pincher</title>
    <title lang="ar">باني بينشر</title>
    <desc lang="en">Comedy, Franois Gautier is stingy! Saving puts the joy, it causes pay sweats. His life is set for the sole purpose of never spend anything. A life that will switch in one day, he falls in love and discovers he has a daughter he did not know existed. كوميدي. تتغير حياة الرجل البخيل عندما يقع في حب فتاة ويعلم بأن لديه ابنه لم يكن يعلم أي شىء عن وجودها من قبل.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014073500 +0000" stop="20201014095500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">The Two Jakes</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا تو جيكس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Private eye Jake, now middle-aged, is about to marry a beautiful young lady until a voice from the past causes him to get involved again. 'Chinatown' sequel directed by and starring Jack Nicholson, with Harvey Keitel. المخبر السري جيك، الذي بلغ منتصف العمر،وعلى وشك الزواج بصبية حسناء،  سمع صوتاً من الماضي يناديه ليتورط بعمله من جديد. هارفي كيتل. إخراج وبطولة جاك نيكلسن الذي أخرج سلسة افلام تشاينا تاون.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014095500 +0000" stop="20201014114000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">The Bachelors</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا باتشلورز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Comedy. Bill (J.K. Simmons) and his son, Wes struggle to cope with the death of their wife and mother. The pair move to Los Angeles, where Bill gets a job at a school that Wes is attending. Over time, the two men try to move forward via new romances. كوميديا. يكافح بيل وابنه ويس للتأقلم بعد وفاة زوجته وأم ابنه. وبعدها ينتقلان للعيش بلوس أنجلوس، وهناك يحصل بيل على وظيفة في المدرسة التي يدرس بها ابنه. ومع مرور الوقت، يحاول كل منهما إستكمال حياته والبدء في علاقة حب جديدة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014114000 +0000" stop="20201014132000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">The Prince Of Egypt</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا برينس اوف إيجيبت</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this animated retelling of the Book of Exodus, Egyptian Prince Moses, upon discovering his roots as a Jewish slave, embarks on a quest to free his people from bondage under the hand of the evil pharaoh Rameses. Voices of Val Kilmer, Ralph Fiennes, Michelle Pfeiffer. يكتشف امير مصري انه من اجل عبري ويكتشف انه مخلص شعبه الذي سيقوده الى الخلاص. رسوم متحركة مع اصوات فل كيلمر، رالف فيان وميشال فايفر.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014132000 +0000" stop="20201014154000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Get On Up</title>
    <title lang="ar">غيت أون أب</title>
    <desc lang="en">Biopic starring Chadwick Boseman, Viola Davis, Nelsan Ellis, Dan Aykroyd. From a childhood spent in poverty to his emergence as the Godfather of Soul, James Brown's incredible life story is one of talent, determination, and perseverance. سيرة ذاتية من بطولة تشادويك بوزيمان، فيولا ديفز، نيلسان إليس ودان أيكرويد. من طفولته التي قضاها في الفقر إلى ظهوره كعراب لـ سول، تابعوا قصة حياة جيمس براون الذي تميز بموهبته إلى جانب امتلاكه للعزيمة والمثابرة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014154000 +0000" stop="20201014173000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Nutty Professor II: The Klumps</title>
    <title lang="ar">ناتي بروفيسور 2: ذا كلامبز</title>
    <desc lang="en">The hilarity begins when professor Sherman Klump finds romance with fellow DNA specialist, Denise Gaines, and discovers a brilliant formula that reverses aging. تبدأ البهجة عندما يقع البروفيسور شيرمان كلامب في حب زميلته المتخصصة في الحمض النووي "دينيس جاينز" ، ويكتشف تركيبة رائعة تعكس الشيخوخة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014173000 +0000" stop="20201014193000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Spy</title>
    <title lang="ar">سباي</title>
    <desc lang="en">After years of doing work integral to the success of major missions, a deskbound CIA analyst is given the chance to go undercover in order to save her partner and thwart a global disaster at the hands of an arms dealer. بعد سنوات من القيام بوظيفة بالغة الأهمية ساهمت في إنجاح العديد من المهمات الكبيرة، تمنح موظفة سي آي أيه مكتبية فرصة التحول إلى عميلة ميدانية من أجل إنقاذ شريكها ومحاولة إحباط كارثة عالمية يخطط لتنفيذها تاجر سلاح.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013003000 +0000" stop="20201013014000 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">Tangent Room</title>
    <title lang="ar">تانجنت روم</title>
    <desc lang="en">Trapped in a mysterious room with no escape, four brilliant minds race against time to prevent a cosmic collapse of the universe. They must learn to work together and solve the puzzle before it's too late. يجد أربعة أشخاص عباقرة أنفسهم محاصرين داخل غرفة غامضة بدون أي مخرج منها على اﻹطلاق، ويصبح عليهم فعل المستحيل لحل اللغز قبل فوات الأوان من أجل الخروج من الغرفة ومنع انهيار الكون بالكامل.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013014000 +0000" stop="20201013034000 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">The Village</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا فيليدج</title>
    <desc lang="en">The population of a small, isolated countryside village believe that their alliance with the mythical creatures that inhabit the forest around them, is coming to an end. يعتقد سكان قرية ريفية منعزلة أن تحالفهم مع المخلوقات الاسطورية التي تعيش في الغاية المحيطة بهم قد قارب على نهايته.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013034000 +0000" stop="20201013052000 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">Baby Obsession</title>
    <title lang="ar">بيبي أوبسيشن</title>
    <desc lang="en">Thriller. Anna Gray (Linsey Godfrey) is starting a family with her loving husband Jon, but little does she know that Rachel (Alicia Leigh Willis), the mother of the baby who died under Anna's watch years ago, is determined to take back what Anna took from her. إثارة. تبدأ آنا غراي (لينسي غودفري) حياتها مع زوجها الحبيب جون. ولكنها لم تكن تعلم إصرار ريكال (أليشيا لي ويليس) أم الطفلة التي توفت منذ سنين على إستعادة كل ما أخذته آنا منها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013052000 +0000" stop="20201013070000 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">Murder At The Mansion</title>
    <title lang="ar">مردر آت ذا مانشن</title>
    <desc lang="en">Thriller. Deanna, a bride-to-be, becomes suspicious of her fiance's family, when she comes across some dark family secrets, while planning their wedding at his remote countryside estate. إثارة. تشك العروس ديانا بعائلة خطيبها عندما تكتشف بعض من الأسرار الخاصة بالعائلة أثناء تحضيرها هي وخطيبها لزواجهما في منزل خطيبها النائي في الريف.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013070000 +0000" stop="20201013083000 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">Dreamhouse Nightmare</title>
    <title lang="ar">دريمهاوس نايتمير</title>
    <desc lang="en">A young couple buy their dream home in New Orleans, only to be tormented by an obsessive mother who believes the house should be hers. يقوم زوجان شابان بشراء منزل أحلامهما في نيوأورلينز ولكنهما يتعذبان بسبب هوس أم تعتقد أن المنزل يجب أن يكون منزلها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013083000 +0000" stop="20201013100500 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">Deadly Shores</title>
    <title lang="ar">ديدلي شورز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Anna moves to a remote island as the new bride of a famous mystery writer. Once there, she uncovers secrets about her new husband's dead former wife and fears she may be the next victim. تتزوج آنا من كاتب رويات بوليسية مشهور وتنتقل إلى جزيرة نائية. تكتشف فور وصولها  أسرار عن زوجته السابقة المتوفية وتخاف من أن تكون الضحية القادمة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013100500 +0000" stop="20201013115500 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">The Village</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا فيليدج</title>
    <desc lang="en">The population of a small, isolated countryside village believe that their alliance with the mythical creatures that inhabit the forest around them, is coming to an end. يعتقد سكان قرية ريفية منعزلة أن تحالفهم مع المخلوقات الاسطورية التي تعيش في الغاية المحيطة بهم قد قارب على نهايته.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013115500 +0000" stop="20201013132000 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">Picture Perfect Mysteries: Dead Over Diamonds</title>
    <title lang="ar">بيكتشر بيرفكت ميستريز: ديد أوفر دايموندز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Crime. Photographer Allie and Detective Sam's investigation into a priceless stolen necklace leads to danger and an unexpected death. جريمة. يؤدي تحقيق المصورة آلى والمحقق سام في قضية العقد الثمين المسروق إلى خطر وموت غير متوقع.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013132000 +0000" stop="20201013151500 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">Tea With Mussolini</title>
    <title lang="ar">تي ويذ موسوليني</title>
    <desc lang="en">Following his mother's death, an illegitimate boy is brought up by an eclectic group of British and American expatriate women revelling the art and culture of Florence on the eve of WWII. Drama, Cher and Judi Dench. تقوم مجموعة من النساء المغتربات ومن بينهم سيدات مجتمع أمريكيات وبريطانيات بتربية صبي غير شرعي إثر وفاة والدته. وكانت هؤلاء النسوة يستمتعن بفن وثقافة مدينة فلورنسا، عشية اندلاع الحرب العالمية الثانية. دراما من بطولة شير وجودي دينش.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013151500 +0000" stop="20201013170000 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">Grey Gardens</title>
    <title lang="ar">غراي غاردنز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Biography based on the life stories of the eccentric aunt (Jessica Lange) and first cousin (Drew Barrymore) of Jackie Onassis who withdrew from New York society and were found living in squalor and isolation in the long-time family mansion in East Hampton, New York. سيرة ذاتية مبنية على قصص حياة العمة غريبة الأطوار (جيسيكا لانج) وقريبتها (درو بيريمور) اللتان انسحبتا من مجتمع نيويورك وذهبتا للعيش في قصر العائلة القديم في إيست هامبتون في نيويورك في ظروف مزرية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013170000 +0000" stop="20201013185000 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">A Mighty Heart</title>
    <title lang="ar">أيه مايتي هارت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dramatic account of the search for Wall Street Journal reporter Daniel Pearl kidnapped in Karachi, 2002, and the efforts of security forces and justice departments to track and bring the kidnappers to justice. Angelina Jolie, Dan Futterman, Irfan Khan star. تصوير درامي لعملية البحث عن مراسل صحيفة وول ستريت جورنال دانيل بيرل الذي اختطف في كراتشي في عام 2002، والجهود التي بذلتها قوات الأمن و وزارة العدال لتعقب الخاطفين وتقديمهم للعدالة. بطولة أنجيلينا جولي، دان فاترمان وإرفان خان.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013185000 +0000" stop="20201013205000 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">A Simple Favor</title>
    <title lang="ar">أيه سيمبل فيفر</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mommy vlogger Stephanie joins her best friend Emily’s husband, Sean, to investigate her sudden disappearance from their small town. تنضم المدونة في شؤون الأمومة ستيفاني إلى  شاين زوج صديقتها المقربة إيميلي التي اختفت بشكل مفاجئ في بلدتهم الصغيرة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013205000 +0000" stop="20201013205000 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">Good Time</title>
    <title lang="ar">غود تايم</title>
    <desc lang="en">Crime drama starring Robert Pattinson as a bank robber on the run with his developmentally disabled brother. Jennifer Jason Leigh co-stars. دراما وجريمة من بطولة روبرت باتينسون وجنيفر جيسون لي . يحاول  كوني إخراج أخيه المعاق من السجن بعد أن تسبب في حبسه بسبب عملية سرقة البنك الفاشلة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013205000 +0000" stop="20201013223500 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">Good Time</title>
    <title lang="ar">غود تايم</title>
    <desc lang="en">Crime drama starring Robert Pattinson as a bank robber on the run with his developmentally disabled brother. Jennifer Jason Leigh co-stars. دراما وجريمة من بطولة روبرت باتينسون وجنيفر جيسون لي . يحاول  كوني إخراج أخيه المعاق من السجن بعد أن تسبب في حبسه بسبب عملية سرقة البنك الفاشلة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013223500 +0000" stop="20201014003000 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">Above Suspicion</title>
    <title lang="ar">أبوف ساسبيشن</title>
    <desc lang="en">The chilling true story of an FBI poster boy assigned to an Appalachian mountain town in Kentucky. There he is drawn into an illicit affair with an impoverished local woman who becomes his star informant. يروي الفيلم القصة الحقيقية لشاب عامل بمكتب التحقيقات الفدرالي في بلدة جبلية في أبالاشيا، كنتاكي. هناك تربطه علاقة غرامية مع امرأة فقيرة من السكان المحليين والتي تصبح بعدها مُخبرة له.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014003000 +0000" stop="20201014021000 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">Deadly Shores</title>
    <title lang="ar">ديدلي شورز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Anna moves to a remote island as the new bride of a famous mystery writer. Once there, she uncovers secrets about her new husband's dead former wife and fears she may be the next victim. تتزوج آنا من كاتب رويات بوليسية مشهور وتنتقل إلى جزيرة نائية. تكتشف فور وصولها  أسرار عن زوجته السابقة المتوفية وتخاف من أن تكون الضحية القادمة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014021000 +0000" stop="20201014035000 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">Picture Perfect Mysteries: Dead Over Diamonds</title>
    <title lang="ar">بيكتشر بيرفكت ميستريز: ديد أوفر دايموندز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Crime. Photographer Allie and Detective Sam's investigation into a priceless stolen necklace leads to danger and an unexpected death. جريمة. يؤدي تحقيق المصورة آلى والمحقق سام في قضية العقد الثمين المسروق إلى خطر وموت غير متوقع.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014035000 +0000" stop="20201014055500 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">Tea With Mussolini</title>
    <title lang="ar">تي ويذ موسوليني</title>
    <desc lang="en">Following his mother's death, an illegitimate boy is brought up by an eclectic group of British and American expatriate women revelling the art and culture of Florence on the eve of WWII. Drama, Cher and Judi Dench. تقوم مجموعة من النساء المغتربات ومن بينهم سيدات مجتمع أمريكيات وبريطانيات بتربية صبي غير شرعي إثر وفاة والدته. وكانت هؤلاء النسوة يستمتعن بفن وثقافة مدينة فلورنسا، عشية اندلاع الحرب العالمية الثانية. دراما من بطولة شير وجودي دينش.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014055500 +0000" stop="20201014073000 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">Lethal Beauty</title>
    <title lang="ar">ليثال بيوتي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Thriller. A spa owner, Aya (Haley Webb), bumps into a distraught, heartbroken sorority sister, Taryn (Haley Pullos), and welcomes her into her home. Taryn, a former foster child, will stop at nothing to create the family bond she has desperately wanted her entire life. إثارة. تتقابل صاحبة النادي الصحي آيه (هالي ويب) صدفة بتارين (هالي بولوز) وتقوم بإستضافتها في منزلها وهي لا تدرك حقيقة تلك الفتاة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014073000 +0000" stop="20201014090500 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">Dating To Kill</title>
    <title lang="ar">ديتينغ تو كيل</title>
    <desc lang="en">Thriller. Jessica, a single mother, has a warm relationship with her teenage daughter - until Tessa starts dating an older man. The crisis becomes lethal when Jessica realises the man is someone who attacked her when she was in college - and he's now back for revenge. إثارة. تربط الأم الوحيدة بابنتها المراهقة علاقة قوية إلى أن تكتشف أن ابنتها تواعد شخصاً يكبرها سناً. وتصبح الأزمة قاتلة عندما تكتشف الأم أن هذا الرجل هو الشخص الذي هاجمها سابقاً وإنه قد عاد للإنتقام.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014090500 +0000" stop="20201014104000 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">A Daughter's Deception</title>
    <title lang="ar">ايه دوترز ديسبشن</title>
    <desc lang="en">Forced to give up her daughter for adoption when she's underage, a woman is thrilled to welcome her back into her life as an adult…. Then she discovers her daughter is a sociopath who has murderous tendencies and poses a danger to everyone. أجبرت الأم على التخلي عن ابنتها للتبني عندما كانت قاصرة، تشعر الأم بسعادة غامرة لاستقبال ابنتها البالغة مرة أخرى في حياتها. ولكنها سرعان ما تكتشف أن لإبنتها ميول قاتلة مما يشكل خطراً واضحاً على الجميع.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014104000 +0000" stop="20201014123000 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">Grey Gardens</title>
    <title lang="ar">غراي غاردنز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Biography based on the life stories of the eccentric aunt (Jessica Lange) and first cousin (Drew Barrymore) of Jackie Onassis who withdrew from New York society and were found living in squalor and isolation in the long-time family mansion in East Hampton, New York. سيرة ذاتية مبنية على قصص حياة العمة غريبة الأطوار (جيسيكا لانج) وقريبتها (درو بيريمور) اللتان انسحبتا من مجتمع نيويورك وذهبتا للعيش في قصر العائلة القديم في إيست هامبتون في نيويورك في ظروف مزرية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014123000 +0000" stop="20201014140500 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">Dating To Kill</title>
    <title lang="ar">ديتينغ تو كيل</title>
    <desc lang="en">Thriller. Jessica, a single mother, has a warm relationship with her teenage daughter - until Tessa starts dating an older man. The crisis becomes lethal when Jessica realises the man is someone who attacked her when she was in college - and he's now back for revenge. إثارة. تربط الأم الوحيدة بابنتها المراهقة علاقة قوية إلى أن تكتشف أن ابنتها تواعد شخصاً يكبرها سناً. وتصبح الأزمة قاتلة عندما تكتشف الأم أن هذا الرجل هو الشخص الذي هاجمها سابقاً وإنه قد عاد للإنتقام.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014140500 +0000" stop="20201014153500 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">The Stalker Club</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا ستوكر كلوب</title>
    <desc lang="en">A group of teenagers who take after their parents and join the stalker club during all this drama a mysterious person in a mask is coming after all of them. تقوم مجموعة من المراهقين باقتفاء أثر ذويهم حيث يقومون بالانضمام الى نادي مختص بذلك وخلال كل هذه الدراما يقوم رجل غامض يرتدي قناع بملاحقتهم جميعا.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014153500 +0000" stop="20201014170000 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">The Party</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا بارتي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Comedy Drama. Various individuals think they’re coming together for a party in a private home, but a series of revelations results in a huge crisis that throws their belief systems, and their values, into total disarray. دراما كوميدية. يعتقد العديد من الأفراد أنهم سيجتمعون معًا من أجل حفلة في منزل خاص ، لكن سلسلة من الاكتشافات الغريبة تؤدي إلى أزمة ضخمة تُلقي بمعتقداتهم وقيمهم في فوضى عارمة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014170000 +0000" stop="20201014184500 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">Death Becomes Her</title>
    <title lang="ar">ديث بيكمز هير</title>
    <desc lang="en">Two women, one an author of beauty books and the other a vain actress, constantly compete with each other over who is the more attractive. امرأتان إحداهن مؤلفة لكتب التجميل والأخرى ممثلة مغرورة، تتنافسان بصورة دائمة لإثبات من منهن أكثر جاذبية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014184500 +0000" stop="20201014202500 +0000" channel="OSN Enigma">
    <title lang="en">Albino Alligator</title>
    <title lang="ar">آلبينو آليغايتور (القاطور الأبيض)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kevin Spacey's directorial debut is a twisting tale of three small-time crooks hiding out in a seedy bar after bungling a bank raid. While the police surround them they can only argue about how they are going to escape. قصة ملتوية  وهي أول إخراج ل(كافن سبايسي) حول ثلاثة لصوص يختبئون في حانة عقب نهبهم بنكا و الآن تطاردهمالشرطة, فآخذوا من فيها رهائن.  ثم تحدث مشادة حادة بين المجرمين ونادلة (فايي دانوواي). فهل سينجحون من القانون؟.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013003000 +0000" stop="20201013015000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Micropolis</title>
    <title lang="ar">ميكروبوليس</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. Rafy, a shy mongoose, falls in love with celebrated mongoose diva Onin but their idyllic lives are threatened when Rascal, the leader of the shrews, decides to take control of their Micropolis city. فيلم رسوم متحركة. يقع رافي، النمس الخجول، في حب أونين، أنثى النمس ومغنية الأوبرا المشهورة، لكن يتم تهديد حياتهما العاطفية عندما يقرر راسكال، زعيم الجرذان، أن يسيطر على مدينة ميكروبوليس التي يعيشون فيها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013015000 +0000" stop="20201013032500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Catcher: Cat City 2</title>
    <title lang="ar">كاتشر: كات سيتي 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. Stanley Mouse, an investigative journalist, is searching for the legend from an ancient "cat tribe" lost in Africa. After finding them, it threatens the continued existence of mouse civilisation. Special Agent Grabowsky will try to save the day. رسوم متحركة. يبحث الصحفي ستانلي ماوس عن أسطورة تعود لـ "قبيلة قطط" قديمة، ضاعت في إفريقيا، وبعد العثور على تلك القبيلة يصبح وجود حضارة الفئران مهدداً، حيث سيحاول العميل الخاص غرابوسكي إنقاذ الموقف.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013032500 +0000" stop="20201013043500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Farm Friends</title>
    <title lang="ar">فارم فريندز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Blackie arrives at “Liberty” farm - a boring place where nothing ever happens. As soon as the black sheep gets there she already wants to leave and be free. But Blackie will soon find out that the farm is the best place for her. تصل بلاكي إلى مزرعة "ليبرتي" وهو مكان ممل لا يحدث فيه أي شيء على الإطلاق. فعندما يصل الخروف الأسود إلى هناك، تريد أن ترحل و تصبح حرة ولكنها سرعان ما تكتشف أن تلك المزرعة هي أفضل مكان لها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013043500 +0000" stop="20201013054500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Black Sheep Smile</title>
    <title lang="ar">بلاك شيب سمايل</title>
    <desc lang="en">Fancy, Cloe and Victoria are annoyed. Grumbo has his own theory. Blackie, of course, has other ideas. Everyone will have a laugh when she tries to put her theory into practice. ينزعج كل من فانسي ، كلو ي وفكتوريا . ولكن غرامبو  لديه نظريته الخاصة وبلاكي لديه أفكار أخرى. سيضحك الجميع عندما تحاول تطبيق نظريتها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013054500 +0000" stop="20201013071500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Operation Arctic</title>
    <title lang="ar">أوبيريشن آركتك</title>
    <desc lang="en">A large scale adventure story for the whole family! Three Norwegian kids, Julia and her twin siblings, Ida and Sindre, stow away on a military helicopter to visit their father, but become marooned on a deserted Half Moon island by a tragic mistake. مغامرة عائلية. يقوم ثلاثة أطفال من النرويج، جوليا، إيدا وسندري بالاختباء على متن طائرة هليكوبتر عسكرية لزيارة والدهم، لتتقطع بهم السبل على سطح جزيرة مهجورة بسبب خطأ مأساوي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013071500 +0000" stop="20201013083500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">The Secret Of Kells</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا سيكرت أوف كيلز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. Adventure awaits 12-year-old Brendan who must fight Vikings to find a crystal and complete the legendary Book of Kells. Brendan must overcome his deepest fears on a secret quest that will take him into the enchanted forest where mythical creatures hide. رسوم متحركة. ينتظر بريندن البالغ من العمر 12 عاماً العديد من المغامرات بينما يتوجب عليه قتال الفايكينغز للعثور على بلورة وإكمال بوك أوف كيلز الأسطوري، كما يتوجب عليه التغلب على أعظم مخاوفه خلال بحث سري سيأخذه إلى الغابة السحرية التي يختبىء داخلها مخلوقات أسطورية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013083500 +0000" stop="20201013094000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Bamse And The City Of Thieves</title>
    <title lang="ar">بامس آند ذا سيتي أوف ثيفز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. Sweden's most popular comic book character gets his very own first feature film: In "Bamse and the City of Thieves. رسوم متحركة. تحظى الشخصية الأبرز في الكتاب الكوميدي الأكثر شعبية في السويد على أول فيلم خاص بها، حيث يبين لنا أشجع دب في العالم وصديقيه ليتل هوب وشيلمان أن السلاح الأفضل ضد الشر هو الصداقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013094000 +0000" stop="20201013110000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Twigson Ties The Knot</title>
    <title lang="ar">تويغسان تايز ذا نوت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. When Lillebror's mother is mysteriously hurt in a biking accident, Lillebror and Knerten turn the town upside down trying to find the culprit. فيلم رسوم متحركة عائلي. عندما تصاب والدة ليليبرور بشكل غامض في حادث دراجة، يقلب ليليبرور ونيرتن البلدة رأسا على عقب للعثور على الجاني.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013110000 +0000" stop="20201013122500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Ivan The Incredible</title>
    <title lang="ar">ايفان ذا انكريدبل</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. Ivan (Thure Lindhardt) is constantly picked on by bullies until a witch mixes a magic potion that makes him the best at everything for one day. رسوم متحركة. يقع إيفان (ثور ليندهارت) دوما ضحية التنمر، لحين تقوم ساحرة بتحضير وصفة سحرية تجعله الأفضل في كل شيء لمدة يوم واحد فقط.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013122500 +0000" stop="20201013134000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Black Sheep Smile</title>
    <title lang="ar">بلاك شيب سمايل</title>
    <desc lang="en">Fancy, Cloe and Victoria are annoyed. Grumbo has his own theory. Blackie, of course, has other ideas. Everyone will have a laugh when she tries to put her theory into practice. ينزعج كل من فانسي ، كلو ي وفكتوريا . ولكن غرامبو  لديه نظريته الخاصة وبلاكي لديه أفكار أخرى. سيضحك الجميع عندما تحاول تطبيق نظريتها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013134000 +0000" stop="20201013144000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Funny Little Cars</title>
    <title lang="ar">فاني ليتل كارز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. Citizens of Doom Valley are not human beings but cars, trucks, boats, and scooters with strong human characteristics. Doom Valley is being destroyed by criminals and environmentally unsound businesses. Its up to the few residents left in town to fight back. رسوم متحركة. يعيش في دوم فالي سكان غير بشريين، وهم سيارات، شاحنات، قوارب ودراجات تتمتع بخصائص بشرية، لكن تلك البلدة تتعرض للتدمير من قبل المجرمين والأعمال المضرة بالبيئة، حيث يعود الأمر للسكان القلائل المتبقين في البلدة للتصدي لهم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013144000 +0000" stop="20201013155500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Bunny Tales</title>
    <title lang="ar">باني تيلز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. As Mother Bunny reads from her ancient story book, the little bunnies learn important lessons as they're transported into the enchanted &amp; colourful, magical &amp; wonderful worlds of six classical fairy tales. رسوم متحركة. بينما تقرأ الأرنب الأم  من كتاب قصصها القديم، يتعلم الأرانب الصغار دروسا مهمة حيث ينتقلون إلى عوالم رائعة، ملونة وساحرة لـ ست قصص كلاسيكية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013155500 +0000" stop="20201013172500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Operation Arctic</title>
    <title lang="ar">أوبيريشن آركتك</title>
    <desc lang="en">A large scale adventure story for the whole family! Three Norwegian kids, Julia and her twin siblings, Ida and Sindre, stow away on a military helicopter to visit their father, but become marooned on a deserted Half Moon island by a tragic mistake. مغامرة عائلية. يقوم ثلاثة أطفال من النرويج، جوليا، إيدا وسندري بالاختباء على متن طائرة هليكوبتر عسكرية لزيارة والدهم، لتتقطع بهم السبل على سطح جزيرة مهجورة بسبب خطأ مأساوي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013172500 +0000" stop="20201013185500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Ivan The Incredible</title>
    <title lang="ar">ايفان ذا انكريدبل</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. Ivan (Thure Lindhardt) is constantly picked on by bullies until a witch mixes a magic potion that makes him the best at everything for one day. رسوم متحركة. يقع إيفان (ثور ليندهارت) دوما ضحية التنمر، لحين تقوم ساحرة بتحضير وصفة سحرية تجعله الأفضل في كل شيء لمدة يوم واحد فقط.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013185500 +0000" stop="20201013202500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">The Secret Of Kells</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا سيكرت أوف كيلز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. Adventure awaits 12-year-old Brendan who must fight Vikings to find a crystal and complete the legendary Book of Kells. Brendan must overcome his deepest fears on a secret quest that will take him into the enchanted forest where mythical creatures hide. رسوم متحركة. ينتظر بريندن البالغ من العمر 12 عاماً العديد من المغامرات بينما يتوجب عليه قتال الفايكينغز للعثور على بلورة وإكمال بوك أوف كيلز الأسطوري، كما يتوجب عليه التغلب على أعظم مخاوفه خلال بحث سري سيأخذه إلى الغابة السحرية التي يختبىء داخلها مخلوقات أسطورية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013202500 +0000" stop="20201013202500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Funny Little Cars</title>
    <title lang="ar">فاني ليتل كارز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. Citizens of Doom Valley are not human beings but cars, trucks, boats, and scooters with strong human characteristics. Doom Valley is being destroyed by criminals and environmentally unsound businesses. Its up to the few residents left in town to fight back. رسوم متحركة. يعيش في دوم فالي سكان غير بشريين، وهم سيارات، شاحنات، قوارب ودراجات تتمتع بخصائص بشرية، لكن تلك البلدة تتعرض للتدمير من قبل المجرمين والأعمال المضرة بالبيئة، حيث يعود الأمر للسكان القلائل المتبقين في البلدة للتصدي لهم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013202500 +0000" stop="20201013212500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Funny Little Cars</title>
    <title lang="ar">فاني ليتل كارز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. Citizens of Doom Valley are not human beings but cars, trucks, boats, and scooters with strong human characteristics. Doom Valley is being destroyed by criminals and environmentally unsound businesses. Its up to the few residents left in town to fight back. رسوم متحركة. يعيش في دوم فالي سكان غير بشريين، وهم سيارات، شاحنات، قوارب ودراجات تتمتع بخصائص بشرية، لكن تلك البلدة تتعرض للتدمير من قبل المجرمين والأعمال المضرة بالبيئة، حيث يعود الأمر للسكان القلائل المتبقين في البلدة للتصدي لهم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013212500 +0000" stop="20201013224000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Black Sheep Smile</title>
    <title lang="ar">بلاك شيب سمايل</title>
    <desc lang="en">Fancy, Cloe and Victoria are annoyed. Grumbo has his own theory. Blackie, of course, has other ideas. Everyone will have a laugh when she tries to put her theory into practice. ينزعج كل من فانسي ، كلو ي وفكتوريا . ولكن غرامبو  لديه نظريته الخاصة وبلاكي لديه أفكار أخرى. سيضحك الجميع عندما تحاول تطبيق نظريتها.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013224000 +0000" stop="20201014000000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Bunny Tales</title>
    <title lang="ar">باني تيلز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. As Mother Bunny reads from her ancient story book, the little bunnies learn important lessons as they're transported into the enchanted &amp; colourful, magical &amp; wonderful worlds of six classical fairy tales. رسوم متحركة. بينما تقرأ الأرنب الأم  من كتاب قصصها القديم، يتعلم الأرانب الصغار دروسا مهمة حيث ينتقلون إلى عوالم رائعة، ملونة وساحرة لـ ست قصص كلاسيكية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014000000 +0000" stop="20201014012000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Ivan The Incredible</title>
    <title lang="ar">ايفان ذا انكريدبل</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. Ivan (Thure Lindhardt) is constantly picked on by bullies until a witch mixes a magic potion that makes him the best at everything for one day. رسوم متحركة. يقع إيفان (ثور ليندهارت) دوما ضحية التنمر، لحين تقوم ساحرة بتحضير وصفة سحرية تجعله الأفضل في كل شيء لمدة يوم واحد فقط.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014012000 +0000" stop="20201014025000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Operation Arctic</title>
    <title lang="ar">أوبيريشن آركتك</title>
    <desc lang="en">A large scale adventure story for the whole family! Three Norwegian kids, Julia and her twin siblings, Ida and Sindre, stow away on a military helicopter to visit their father, but become marooned on a deserted Half Moon island by a tragic mistake. مغامرة عائلية. يقوم ثلاثة أطفال من النرويج، جوليا، إيدا وسندري بالاختباء على متن طائرة هليكوبتر عسكرية لزيارة والدهم، لتتقطع بهم السبل على سطح جزيرة مهجورة بسبب خطأ مأساوي.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014025000 +0000" stop="20201014041500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">The Secret Of Kells</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا سيكرت أوف كيلز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. Adventure awaits 12-year-old Brendan who must fight Vikings to find a crystal and complete the legendary Book of Kells. Brendan must overcome his deepest fears on a secret quest that will take him into the enchanted forest where mythical creatures hide. رسوم متحركة. ينتظر بريندن البالغ من العمر 12 عاماً العديد من المغامرات بينما يتوجب عليه قتال الفايكينغز للعثور على بلورة وإكمال بوك أوف كيلز الأسطوري، كما يتوجب عليه التغلب على أعظم مخاوفه خلال بحث سري سيأخذه إلى الغابة السحرية التي يختبىء داخلها مخلوقات أسطورية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014041500 +0000" stop="20201014055500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Victor And The Secret Of Crocodile Mansion</title>
    <title lang="ar">فيكتور آند ذا سيكرت أوف كروكودايل مانشن</title>
    <desc lang="en">Adventure. Among African masks and stuffed crocodiles, Victor finds a diary in his great-uncle's mansion. The book and its drawings reveal a long-hidden secret about a young woman who died in the house many years earlier. مغامرة. وسط الأقنعة الإفريقية والتماسيح المحشوة، يعثر فيكتور على كتاب مذكرات في منزل عمه، ليكشف الكتاب وما في قلبه من رسومات عن سر قديم مخفي حول امرأة شابة توفيت في ذلك المنزل قبل سنوات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014055500 +0000" stop="20201014071500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Marvin Airlines</title>
    <title lang="ar">مارفن أيرلاينز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Marvin wants to leave the farm because he can't fly and feels that nobody loves him. His friend Grumbo has been offered a new job at the city aquarium and wants to leave too. Will the others tell Marvin and Grumbo they love them before it is too late? يريد مارفن أن يترك المزرعة لإنه لايستطيع أن يطيرولشعوره بعدم حب الآخرين له، بينما يحصل صديقه غرامبو على وظيفة جديدة في حوض أسماك المدينة. ولكن هل سيقوم الآخرين بإخبار مارفن وغرامبي بحبهم لهما قبل فوات الأوان؟.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014071500 +0000" stop="20201014085000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Blue Elephant 2</title>
    <title lang="ar">بلو إيليفانت 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">This animated sequel tells of Khan Kluay's two elephant children and the struggle whether to live with his wife or fight another attack by the Burmese as King Naresuan's war elephant. تروي هذه التتمة من فيلم الرسوم المتحركة هذا قصة خان كلواي وصغيريه الفيلين، وصراعه بين أن يعيش مع زوجته أو أن يحارب ضد هجوم آخر شنّه البورميين باعتباره فيل الملك ناريسوانت المحارب.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014085000 +0000" stop="20201014095000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Funny Little Cars</title>
    <title lang="ar">فاني ليتل كارز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. Citizens of Doom Valley are not human beings but cars, trucks, boats, and scooters with strong human characteristics. Doom Valley is being destroyed by criminals and environmentally unsound businesses. Its up to the few residents left in town to fight back. رسوم متحركة. يعيش في دوم فالي سكان غير بشريين، وهم سيارات، شاحنات، قوارب ودراجات تتمتع بخصائص بشرية، لكن تلك البلدة تتعرض للتدمير من قبل المجرمين والأعمال المضرة بالبيئة، حيث يعود الأمر للسكان القلائل المتبقين في البلدة للتصدي لهم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014095000 +0000" stop="20201014110000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Bunny Tales</title>
    <title lang="ar">باني تيلز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. As Mother Bunny reads from her ancient story book, the little bunnies learn important lessons as they're transported into the enchanted &amp; colourful, magical &amp; wonderful worlds of six classical fairy tales. رسوم متحركة. بينما تقرأ الأرنب الأم  من كتاب قصصها القديم، يتعلم الأرانب الصغار دروسا مهمة حيث ينتقلون إلى عوالم رائعة، ملونة وساحرة لـ ست قصص كلاسيكية.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014110000 +0000" stop="20201014122000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Marco Macaco</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماركو ماكاكو</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. Marco Macaco is a day dreamer but also a dedicated beach officer on an island where nothing seems to happen, until the charming Carlo arrives to build a gigantic casino right on Marco's beach. رسوم متحركة. ماركو ماكاكو هو شرطي سواحل متخصص على جزيرة خالية من المشاكل، لحين يصل الساحر كارلو ويقوم ببناء كازينو ضخم على شاطئ ماركو.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014122000 +0000" stop="20201014140000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Victor And The Secret Of Crocodile Mansion</title>
    <title lang="ar">فيكتور آند ذا سيكرت أوف كروكودايل مانشن</title>
    <desc lang="en">Adventure. Among African masks and stuffed crocodiles, Victor finds a diary in his great-uncle's mansion. The book and its drawings reveal a long-hidden secret about a young woman who died in the house many years earlier. مغامرة. وسط الأقنعة الإفريقية والتماسيح المحشوة، يعثر فيكتور على كتاب مذكرات في منزل عمه، ليكشف الكتاب وما في قلبه من رسومات عن سر قديم مخفي حول امرأة شابة توفيت في ذلك المنزل قبل سنوات.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014140000 +0000" stop="20201014152500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Emilie Jolie</title>
    <title lang="ar">إميلي جولي</title>
    <desc lang="en">This animated musical tells the tale of a little girl in the wonderful world of her book who must overcome her fears to save the baby blue rabbit kidnapped by an evil witch, and save her book from destruction. يروي هذا الفيلم الموسيقي المصوّر قصة فتاة صغيرة في العالم الرائع داخل كتابها، حيث عليها التغلب على مخاوفها لتتمكن من إنقاذ الأرنب الأزرق الصغير الذي خطفته الساحرة الشريرة، وإنقاذ كتابها من التدمير.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014152500 +0000" stop="20201014165000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Quest For A Heart</title>
    <title lang="ar">كويست فور أيه هارت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. A young troll and his friends are on a quest to find the magic heart that will save their village and the world from turning to stone. رسوم متحركة. يسعى قزم شاب وأصدقاءه للذهاب في رحلة بحث عن القلب السحري الذي سينقذ قريتهم والعالم من التحجر.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014165000 +0000" stop="20201014181500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Marvin Airlines</title>
    <title lang="ar">مارفن أيرلاينز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Marvin wants to leave the farm because he can't fly and feels that nobody loves him. His friend Grumbo has been offered a new job at the city aquarium and wants to leave too. Will the others tell Marvin and Grumbo they love them before it is too late? يريد مارفن أن يترك المزرعة لإنه لايستطيع أن يطيرولشعوره بعدم حب الآخرين له، بينما يحصل صديقه غرامبو على وظيفة جديدة في حوض أسماك المدينة. ولكن هل سيقوم الآخرين بإخبار مارفن وغرامبي بحبهم لهما قبل فوات الأوان؟.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014181500 +0000" stop="20201014193500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Kids HD">
    <title lang="en">Marco Macaco</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماركو ماكاكو</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. Marco Macaco is a day dreamer but also a dedicated beach officer on an island where nothing seems to happen, until the charming Carlo arrives to build a gigantic casino right on Marco's beach. رسوم متحركة. ماركو ماكاكو هو شرطي سواحل متخصص على جزيرة خالية من المشاكل، لحين يصل الساحر كارلو ويقوم ببناء كازينو ضخم على شاطئ ماركو.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013010000 +0000" stop="20201013024500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Freaky Friday</title>
    <title lang="ar">فريكي فرايدي</title>
    <desc lang="en">A girl and her mother wish they could be someone else. Their wish comes true and they exchange bodies, only to learn what it's like to be in the other person's shoes. Comedy with Jamie Lee Curtis and Lindsay Lohan. تتمنى بنت وأمها الأرملة أن تمتلك كل واحدة منهما شخصية أخرى، وبعدما تتحقق أمنيتهما وتصبح كل منهما في جسد الأخرى، تكتشفان صعوبة ما تقوم به كل منهما. كوميديا من بطولة جيمي لي كيرتيس وليندسي لوهان.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013024500 +0000" stop="20201013043000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Artemis Fowl</title>
    <title lang="ar">ارتيميس فول</title>
    <desc lang="en">Adventure. Artemis Fowl, a young criminal prodigy, hunts down a secret society of fairies to find his missing father. مغامرات. أرتميس فول ، وهو ولد عبقري، يلاحق جمعية سرية من الجنيات للعثور على والده المفقود.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013043000 +0000" stop="20201013061500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Finding Nemo</title>
    <title lang="ar">فايندينغ نيمو</title>
    <desc lang="en">Family animation. Marlin the clown fish embarks on a journey to find his son Nemo after losing him in the Great Barrier Reef. What Marlin doesn't know, however, is that while watching a boat passing, Nemo was caught in a net and given a new home in a dentist's aquarium. رسوم متحركة عائلي. عندما يبتعد نيمو فجأة عن منزله ويقع بيد غواص يأخذه إلى أستراليا، يشرع والده مارلن وسمكة ودودة تعاني من فقدان الذاكرة برحلة للبحث عنه، حيث يواجهون خلالها أسماك قرش نباتية، وسلاحف متأنقة، وقناديل منومة وطيور نورس جائعة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013061500 +0000" stop="20201013075500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">First Kid</title>
    <title lang="ar">فيرست كيد</title>
    <desc lang="en">A wise-cracking Secret Service Agent with hopes of one day being assigned to protect the President gets more than he bargained for when he's ordered instead to protect his precocious son. يتمنى عميل مخابرات سري أن ينال مهمة حراسة الرئيس، لكنه يحصل على أكثر من هذا عندما تأتيه الأوامر بحراسة ابن الرئيس المراهق.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013075500 +0000" stop="20201013093000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Freaky Friday</title>
    <title lang="ar">فريكي فرايدي</title>
    <desc lang="en">A girl and her mother wish they could be someone else. Their wish comes true and they exchange bodies, only to learn what it's like to be in the other person's shoes. Comedy with Jamie Lee Curtis and Lindsay Lohan. تتمنى بنت وأمها الأرملة أن تمتلك كل واحدة منهما شخصية أخرى، وبعدما تتحقق أمنيتهما وتصبح كل منهما في جسد الأخرى، تكتشفان صعوبة ما تقوم به كل منهما. كوميديا من بطولة جيمي لي كيرتيس وليندسي لوهان.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013093000 +0000" stop="20201013111500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Camp Nowhere</title>
    <title lang="ar">كامب نو وير</title>
    <desc lang="en">A has-been drama teacher is bribed by a group of kids to pose as a camp counsellor for their made-up summer camp. Mayhem ensues when the parents come to visit. Family comedy starring Christopher Lloyd. تتمكن مجموعة أطفال من إقناع مدرس كان يدرّسهم مادة الدراما، ويقدموا له رشوة  مقابل تمثيل دور المشرف على معسكرهم الصيفي. تبدأ المشاكل بوصول أهاليهم لزيارتهم. عائلي كوميدي، كريستوفر لويد.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013111500 +0000" stop="20201013124000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Lady And The Tramp</title>
    <title lang="ar">ليدي أند ذا ترامب</title>
    <desc lang="en">Experience the thrilling adventures of Lady, a lovingly pampered cocker spaniel, and Tramp, a freewheeling dog with a heart of gold. This heart-warming tale charmed a generation with its exquisite animation, unforgettable songs and timeless love story. استمتعوا بالمغامرات الشيقة التي تجمع بين الكلبة المدللة ليدي والكلب الطليق ترامب في هذه القصة التي سحرت جيلا كاملا من خلال رسومها المتحركة الرائعة، أغانيها التي لا تنسى وقصة الحب الخالدة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013124000 +0000" stop="20201013141500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Phineas &amp; Ferb Movie: Candace Against The Universe</title>
    <title lang="ar">فينس أند فيرب موفي: كانس أغينست ذا يونفيرس</title>
    <desc lang="en">The famed stepbrother inventors know what they're gonna do today. They're gonna rescue their sister from an alien abduction. يعلم المخترعون المشهورون علم اليقين بما سيفعلونه اليوم. سوف يحاولون انقاذ شقيقتهم من قبضة أحد المخلوقات الغريبة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013141500 +0000" stop="20201013160000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Maleficent</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماليفسنت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Family adventure with Angelina Jolie, Sharlto Copley, Elle Fanning. A powerful and respected fairy helps to rule a magical land, but a betrayal years later turns her pure heart to stone and twists her into a creature bent on revenge, driven to curse an infant princess. مغامرة عائلية من بطولة أنجيلينا جولي، شارلتو كوبلي وإيلي فانينغ. تساعد جنية قوية ومحترمة بحكم أرض سحرية، لكن وبعد تعرضها لسنوات من الخيانة يتحول قلبها النقي إلى حجر وتصبح مخلوقة مصممة على الانتقام، مما يدفعها لإلقاء لعنة على أميرة صغيرة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013160000 +0000" stop="20201013174000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Disney's Magic Camp</title>
    <title lang="ar">ديزني ماجيك كامب</title>
    <desc lang="en">Andy, at the urging of his former mentor and Magic Camp owner Roy Preston, returns to the camp of his youth hoping to reignite his career. Instead, he finds inspiration in his ragtag bunch of rookie magicians. يعود آندي ، بناءً على طلب مالك "ماجيك كامب" ومعلمه السابق "روي بريستون" ، إلى معسكر شبابه على أمل إعادة إشعال مسيرته المهنية. بدلاً من ذلك، يجد الإلهام في مجموعة من السحرة المبتدئين.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013174000 +0000" stop="20201013191000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Lady And The Tramp</title>
    <title lang="ar">ليدي أند ذا ترامب</title>
    <desc lang="en">Experience the thrilling adventures of Lady, a lovingly pampered cocker spaniel, and Tramp, a freewheeling dog with a heart of gold. This heart-warming tale charmed a generation with its exquisite animation, unforgettable songs and timeless love story. استمتعوا بالمغامرات الشيقة التي تجمع بين الكلبة المدللة ليدي والكلب الطليق ترامب في هذه القصة التي سحرت جيلا كاملا من خلال رسومها المتحركة الرائعة، أغانيها التي لا تنسى وقصة الحب الخالدة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013191000 +0000" stop="20201013205000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Phineas &amp; Ferb Movie: Candace Against The Universe</title>
    <title lang="ar">فينس أند فيرب موفي: كانس أغينست ذا يونفيرس</title>
    <desc lang="en">The famed stepbrother inventors know what they're gonna do today. They're gonna rescue their sister from an alien abduction. يعلم المخترعون المشهورون علم اليقين بما سيفعلونه اليوم. سوف يحاولون انقاذ شقيقتهم من قبضة أحد المخلوقات الغريبة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013205000 +0000" stop="20201013205000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Maleficent</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماليفسنت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Family adventure with Angelina Jolie, Sharlto Copley, Elle Fanning. A powerful and respected fairy helps to rule a magical land, but a betrayal years later turns her pure heart to stone and twists her into a creature bent on revenge, driven to curse an infant princess. مغامرة عائلية من بطولة أنجيلينا جولي، شارلتو كوبلي وإيلي فانينغ. تساعد جنية قوية ومحترمة بحكم أرض سحرية، لكن وبعد تعرضها لسنوات من الخيانة يتحول قلبها النقي إلى حجر وتصبح مخلوقة مصممة على الانتقام، مما يدفعها لإلقاء لعنة على أميرة صغيرة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013205000 +0000" stop="20201013223500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Maleficent</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماليفسنت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Family adventure with Angelina Jolie, Sharlto Copley, Elle Fanning. A powerful and respected fairy helps to rule a magical land, but a betrayal years later turns her pure heart to stone and twists her into a creature bent on revenge, driven to curse an infant princess. مغامرة عائلية من بطولة أنجيلينا جولي، شارلتو كوبلي وإيلي فانينغ. تساعد جنية قوية ومحترمة بحكم أرض سحرية، لكن وبعد تعرضها لسنوات من الخيانة يتحول قلبها النقي إلى حجر وتصبح مخلوقة مصممة على الانتقام، مما يدفعها لإلقاء لعنة على أميرة صغيرة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013223500 +0000" stop="20201014002000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Camp Nowhere</title>
    <title lang="ar">كامب نو وير</title>
    <desc lang="en">A has-been drama teacher is bribed by a group of kids to pose as a camp counsellor for their made-up summer camp. Mayhem ensues when the parents come to visit. Family comedy starring Christopher Lloyd. تتمكن مجموعة أطفال من إقناع مدرس كان يدرّسهم مادة الدراما، ويقدموا له رشوة  مقابل تمثيل دور المشرف على معسكرهم الصيفي. تبدأ المشاكل بوصول أهاليهم لزيارتهم. عائلي كوميدي، كريستوفر لويد.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014002000 +0000" stop="20201014013500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Lady And The Tramp</title>
    <title lang="ar">ليدي أند ذا ترامب</title>
    <desc lang="en">Experience the thrilling adventures of Lady, a lovingly pampered cocker spaniel, and Tramp, a freewheeling dog with a heart of gold. This heart-warming tale charmed a generation with its exquisite animation, unforgettable songs and timeless love story. استمتعوا بالمغامرات الشيقة التي تجمع بين الكلبة المدللة ليدي والكلب الطليق ترامب في هذه القصة التي سحرت جيلا كاملا من خلال رسومها المتحركة الرائعة، أغانيها التي لا تنسى وقصة الحب الخالدة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014013500 +0000" stop="20201014031500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Disney's Magic Camp</title>
    <title lang="ar">ديزني ماجيك كامب</title>
    <desc lang="en">Andy, at the urging of his former mentor and Magic Camp owner Roy Preston, returns to the camp of his youth hoping to reignite his career. Instead, he finds inspiration in his ragtag bunch of rookie magicians. يعود آندي ، بناءً على طلب مالك "ماجيك كامب" ومعلمه السابق "روي بريستون" ، إلى معسكر شبابه على أمل إعادة إشعال مسيرته المهنية. بدلاً من ذلك، يجد الإلهام في مجموعة من السحرة المبتدئين.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014031500 +0000" stop="20201014045500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Maleficent</title>
    <title lang="ar">ماليفسنت</title>
    <desc lang="en">Family adventure with Angelina Jolie, Sharlto Copley, Elle Fanning. A powerful and respected fairy helps to rule a magical land, but a betrayal years later turns her pure heart to stone and twists her into a creature bent on revenge, driven to curse an infant princess. مغامرة عائلية من بطولة أنجيلينا جولي، شارلتو كوبلي وإيلي فانينغ. تساعد جنية قوية ومحترمة بحكم أرض سحرية، لكن وبعد تعرضها لسنوات من الخيانة يتحول قلبها النقي إلى حجر وتصبح مخلوقة مصممة على الانتقام، مما يدفعها لإلقاء لعنة على أميرة صغيرة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014045500 +0000" stop="20201014063500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Camp Nowhere</title>
    <title lang="ar">كامب نو وير</title>
    <desc lang="en">A has-been drama teacher is bribed by a group of kids to pose as a camp counsellor for their made-up summer camp. Mayhem ensues when the parents come to visit. Family comedy starring Christopher Lloyd. تتمكن مجموعة أطفال من إقناع مدرس كان يدرّسهم مادة الدراما، ويقدموا له رشوة  مقابل تمثيل دور المشرف على معسكرهم الصيفي. تبدأ المشاكل بوصول أهاليهم لزيارتهم. عائلي كوميدي، كريستوفر لويد.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014063500 +0000" stop="20201014080500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Phineas &amp; Ferb Movie: Candace Against The Universe</title>
    <title lang="ar">فينس أند فيرب موفي: كانس أغينست ذا يونفيرس</title>
    <desc lang="en">The famed stepbrother inventors know what they're gonna do today. They're gonna rescue their sister from an alien abduction. يعلم المخترعون المشهورون علم اليقين بما سيفعلونه اليوم. سوف يحاولون انقاذ شقيقتهم من قبضة أحد المخلوقات الغريبة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014080500 +0000" stop="20201014094000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Disney's Magic Camp</title>
    <title lang="ar">ديزني ماجيك كامب</title>
    <desc lang="en">Andy, at the urging of his former mentor and Magic Camp owner Roy Preston, returns to the camp of his youth hoping to reignite his career. Instead, he finds inspiration in his ragtag bunch of rookie magicians. يعود آندي ، بناءً على طلب مالك "ماجيك كامب" ومعلمه السابق "روي بريستون" ، إلى معسكر شبابه على أمل إعادة إشعال مسيرته المهنية. بدلاً من ذلك، يجد الإلهام في مجموعة من السحرة المبتدئين.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014094000 +0000" stop="20201014112000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">101 Dalmatians</title>
    <title lang="ar">101 دالميشنز</title>
    <desc lang="en">Delightful live-action family comedy in which the dastardly Cruella de Vil  sets out to claim a huge brood of puppies for her own evil ends. Glenn Close stars in this classic Disney tale of puppy love and dog-napping. فيلم أكشن كوميدي عائلي ممتع، تستعد فيه الخسيسة كرويلا ديفيلا لسرقة مجموعة من الجراء النادرة من أجل مطامعها الشريرة. تمثل غلين كلوس في هذا الفيلم الكلاسيكي من ديزني عن الرفق بالحيوان.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014112000 +0000" stop="20201014130500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Lady And The Tramp</title>
    <title lang="ar">ليدي أند ذا ترامب</title>
    <desc lang="en">The love story between a pampered Cocker Spaniel named Lady and a streetwise mongrel named Tramp. Lady finds herself out on the street after her owners have a baby and is saved from a pack by Tramp, who tries to show her to live her life footloose and collar-free. تدور الأحداث حول قصة حب كلبة مدللة من فصيلة كوكر سبانيل تُدعى ليدي وكلب هجين لديه تجارب في الحياة اسمه ترامب. يتخلى أصحاب ليدي عنها بعد إنجابهم لطفل وتجد نفسها في الشارع ويتم إنقاذها من قبل ترامب الذي كان يحاول أن يعلمها كيف تعيش حياتها حرة طليقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014130500 +0000" stop="20201014141500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Stitch! The Movie</title>
    <title lang="ar">ستيتش! ذا موفي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. Following the further adventures of Stitch and his surrogate family in Hawaii, it seems that Dr. Jumba has brought his other 625 experiments to Earth. Now it's up to Stitch and company to make sure the villainous Dr. Hamsterviel doesn't get his hands on them. متابعة لإنتاج ديزني الشهير ليلو آند ستيتش، يأتيكم ستيتش! ذا موفي ليرصد مغامرات ستيتش وأصدقائه من المخلوقات الفضائية وهم يخوضون عملية إنقاذ لباقي التجارب. كرتوني، بأصوات كثيرة منها: كريس ساندرز.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014141500 +0000" stop="20201014160000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">The Good Dinosaur</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا غود دايناصور</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this enchanting computer-animated fantasy a young Apatosaurus named Arlo is swept away by a river current, stranding him in a frightening new place. Far from home he embarks on a journey to reunite with his family, befriending a prehistoric child along the way. فيلم رسوم متحركة عائلية يتحدث عن ديناصور صغير يدعى أرلو والذي يجرفه تيار مائي ويجعله عالقاً في مكان مخيف. لكن يبدأ رحلة شاقة للعودة والاتحاد مع عائلته لكنه يصادق طفل ما قبل التاريخ على طول الطريق.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014160000 +0000" stop="20201014174500 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Toy Story 4</title>
    <title lang="ar">توي ستوري 4</title>
    <desc lang="en">When a new toy called "Forky" joins Woody and the gang, a road trip alongside old and new friends reveals how big the world can be for a toy. عندما تنضم دمية جديدة اسمها "فوركي" إلى وودي ورفاقه، تكشف رحلة على الطرقات برفقة الأصدقاء القدامى والجدد مدى ضخامة هذا العالم بالنسبة إلى الدمى.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014174500 +0000" stop="20201014193000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Lady And The Tramp</title>
    <title lang="ar">ليدي أند ذا ترامب</title>
    <desc lang="en">The love story between a pampered Cocker Spaniel named Lady and a streetwise mongrel named Tramp. Lady finds herself out on the street after her owners have a baby and is saved from a pack by Tramp, who tries to show her to live her life footloose and collar-free. تدور الأحداث حول قصة حب كلبة مدللة من فصيلة كوكر سبانيل تُدعى ليدي وكلب هجين لديه تجارب في الحياة اسمه ترامب. يتخلى أصحاب ليدي عنها بعد إنجابهم لطفل وتجد نفسها في الشارع ويتم إنقاذها من قبل ترامب الذي كان يحاول أن يعلمها كيف تعيش حياتها حرة طليقة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014193000 +0000" stop="20201014204000 +0000" channel="OSN Movies Disney HD">
    <title lang="en">Stitch! The Movie</title>
    <title lang="ar">ستيتش! ذا موفي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Animation. Following the further adventures of Stitch and his surrogate family in Hawaii, it seems that Dr. Jumba has brought his other 625 experiments to Earth. Now it's up to Stitch and company to make sure the villainous Dr. Hamsterviel doesn't get his hands on them. متابعة لإنتاج ديزني الشهير ليلو آند ستيتش، يأتيكم ستيتش! ذا موفي ليرصد مغامرات ستيتش وأصدقائه من المخلوقات الفضائية وهم يخوضون عملية إنقاذ لباقي التجارب. كرتوني، بأصوات كثيرة منها: كريس ساندرز.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013000000 +0000" stop="20201013020000 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">A Case Of You</title>
    <title lang="ar">أيه كيس أوف يو</title>
    <desc lang="en">Quirky romantic comedy starring Justin Long, Evan Rachel Wood and Keir O'Donnell. A smitten writer creates an alternate online identity in order to charm a pretty barista, only to realise that maintaining his elaborate ruse is easier said than done. كوميديا رومانسية من بطولة جاستن لونغ، إيفان ريتشل وود وكير أودونيل. يخلق كاتب متيم شخصية بديلة له على الإنترنت من أجل إثارة إعجاب فتاة جميلة، لكنه يكتشف أن الحفاظ على تلك الشخصية أصعب مما كان يتوقع.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013020000 +0000" stop="20201013041000 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Dark Crimes</title>
    <title lang="ar">Star Movies HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">STAR Movies offers an exciting and unique mix of the best films from around the world. تقدم قناة ستار موفيز مجموعة رائعة وفريدة من أفضل الأفلام من جميع أنحاء العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013041000 +0000" stop="20201013054000 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Adult Life Skills</title>
    <title lang="ar">Star Movies HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">STAR Movies offers an exciting and unique mix of the best films from around the world. تقدم قناة ستار موفيز مجموعة رائعة وفريدة من أفضل الأفلام من جميع أنحاء العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013054000 +0000" stop="20201013070500 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Dark Crimes</title>
    <title lang="ar">Star Movies HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">STAR Movies offers an exciting and unique mix of the best films from around the world. تقدم قناة ستار موفيز مجموعة رائعة وفريدة من أفضل الأفلام من جميع أنحاء العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013070500 +0000" stop="20201013085000 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Jasper Jones</title>
    <title lang="ar">Star Movies HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">STAR Movies offers an exciting and unique mix of the best films from around the world. تقدم قناة ستار موفيز مجموعة رائعة وفريدة من أفضل الأفلام من جميع أنحاء العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013085000 +0000" stop="20201013104000 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Anywhere But Here</title>
    <title lang="ar">أنيويير بات هير</title>
    <desc lang="en">Thoughtful drama starring Susan Sarandon as an extravagant single mother who wants her beautiful daughter to make it big in the movies. Natalie Portman portrays the resentful teenager. دراما من بطولة سوزان ساراندوم التي تجسد دور أم عازبة مسرفة، ترغب في أن تصبح ابنتها الجميلة ممثلة مشهورة في الأفلام، حيث تجسد ناتالي بورتمان دور المراهقة البغيضة.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013104000 +0000" stop="20201013121500 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">The Wedding Ringer</title>
    <title lang="ar">ذا ويدينغ رينغر</title>
    <desc lang="en">Comedy starring Kevin Hart, Josh Gad, Kaley Cuoco-Sweeting. Fabricating the names of not only a best man but nine groomsmen as well, a socially challenged groom-to-be enters into a charade by hiring a surrogate best man to pull off the wedding. كوميدي من بطولة كيفن هارت، جوش غاد وكيلي كوكو-سويتينغ. بعدما يقوم عريس فاشل اجتماعياً باختلاق اسم لإشبينه ووصفائه التسعة، يدخل في تمثيلية من خلال التعاقد مع إشبين بديل من أجل إتمام حفل زفافه.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013121500 +0000" stop="20201013135500 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Did You Hear About The Morgans?</title>
    <title lang="ar">ديد يو هير أباوت ذا مورغانز؟</title>
    <desc lang="en">Delightful comedy with Hugh Grant and Sarah Jessica Parker as an estranged couple about to find love in the most unexpected place when relocated to small-town Wyoming as part of a witness protection program. زوجان منفصلان على وشك العثور على الحب في مكانٍ غير متوقع وخاصةً بعد انتقالهما إلى ولاية وايومنغ كجزء من برنامج حماية الشهود. كوميديا مرحة مع هيو غرانت وسارا جيسكا باركر.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013135500 +0000" stop="20201013153000 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">I Spy</title>
    <title lang="ar">آي سباي</title>
    <desc lang="en">Action adventure starring Eddie Murphy and Owen Wilson. Based on the popular 1960's television series a U.S. government agent recruits a professional boxer to help him recover a missing stealth fighter jet. مقتبس عن المسلسل التلفزيوني الشهير عن عميل فيدرالي يستعين بملاكم محترف ليساعده على استرداد الطائرة المقاتلة النفاثة. أكشن مغامرات بطولة إيدي ميرفي وأوين ويلسون.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013153000 +0000" stop="20201013170000 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Adult Life Skills</title>
    <title lang="ar">Star Movies HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">STAR Movies offers an exciting and unique mix of the best films from around the world. تقدم قناة ستار موفيز مجموعة رائعة وفريدة من أفضل الأفلام من جميع أنحاء العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013170000 +0000" stop="20201013183800 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Born To Dance</title>
    <title lang="ar">Star Movies HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">STAR Movies offers an exciting and unique mix of the best films from around the world. تقدم قناة ستار موفيز مجموعة رائعة وفريدة من أفضل الأفلام من جميع أنحاء العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013183800 +0000" stop="20201013203500 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Raising Helen</title>
    <title lang="ar">رايزينغ هيلين</title>
    <desc lang="en">STAR Movies offers an exciting and unique mix of the best films from around the world. تقدم قناة ستار موفيز مجموعة رائعة وفريدة من أفضل الأفلام من جميع أنحاء العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013203500 +0000" stop="20201013203500 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Diary Of A Wimpy Kid: The Long Haul</title>
    <title lang="ar">دايري أوف أي ويمبي كيد: ذا لونغ هول</title>
    <desc lang="en">Comedy. A Heffley family road trip to attend grandma's 90th birthday party goes hilariously off course thanks to young Greg's newest scheme to get to a video gaming convention. كوميدي. سرعان ما تنحرف خطط آل هافلي لزيارة الجدة في عيد ميلادها التسعين عن مسارها بفضل حيلة غريغ الصغير الذي يرغب بحضور مؤتمر لألعاب الفيديو.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013203500 +0000" stop="20201013220200 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Diary Of A Wimpy Kid: The Long Haul</title>
    <title lang="ar">دايري أوف أي ويمبي كيد: ذا لونغ هول</title>
    <desc lang="en">Comedy. A Heffley family road trip to attend grandma's 90th birthday party goes hilariously off course thanks to young Greg's newest scheme to get to a video gaming convention. كوميدي. سرعان ما تنحرف خطط آل هافلي لزيارة الجدة في عيد ميلادها التسعين عن مسارها بفضل حيلة غريغ الصغير الذي يرغب بحضور مؤتمر لألعاب الفيديو.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201013220200 +0000" stop="20201014000000 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Thumper</title>
    <title lang="ar">Star Movies HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">STAR Movies offers an exciting and unique mix of the best films from around the world. تقدم قناة ستار موفيز مجموعة رائعة وفريدة من أفضل الأفلام من جميع أنحاء العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014000000 +0000" stop="20201014013000 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Dark Crimes</title>
    <title lang="ar">Star Movies HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">STAR Movies offers an exciting and unique mix of the best films from around the world. تقدم قناة ستار موفيز مجموعة رائعة وفريدة من أفضل الأفلام من جميع أنحاء العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014013000 +0000" stop="20201014035500 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Jasper Jones</title>
    <title lang="ar">Star Movies HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">STAR Movies offers an exciting and unique mix of the best films from around the world. تقدم قناة ستار موفيز مجموعة رائعة وفريدة من أفضل الأفلام من جميع أنحاء العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014035500 +0000" stop="20201014053500 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Born To Dance</title>
    <title lang="ar">Star Movies HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">STAR Movies offers an exciting and unique mix of the best films from around the world. تقدم قناة ستار موفيز مجموعة رائعة وفريدة من أفضل الأفلام من جميع أنحاء العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014053500 +0000" stop="20201014072000 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Jasper Jones</title>
    <title lang="ar">Star Movies HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">STAR Movies offers an exciting and unique mix of the best films from around the world. تقدم قناة ستار موفيز مجموعة رائعة وفريدة من أفضل الأفلام من جميع أنحاء العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014072000 +0000" stop="20201014084500 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Thumper</title>
    <title lang="ar">Star Movies HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">STAR Movies offers an exciting and unique mix of the best films from around the world. تقدم قناة ستار موفيز مجموعة رائعة وفريدة من أفضل الأفلام من جميع أنحاء العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014084500 +0000" stop="20201014102500 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Did You Hear About The Morgans?</title>
    <title lang="ar">ديد يو هير أباوت ذا مورغانز؟</title>
    <desc lang="en">Delightful comedy with Hugh Grant and Sarah Jessica Parker as an estranged couple about to find love in the most unexpected place when relocated to small-town Wyoming as part of a witness protection program. زوجان منفصلان على وشك العثور على الحب في مكانٍ غير متوقع وخاصةً بعد انتقالهما إلى ولاية وايومنغ كجزء من برنامج حماية الشهود. كوميديا مرحة مع هيو غرانت وسارا جيسكا باركر.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014102500 +0000" stop="20201014115500 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Diary Of A Wimpy Kid: The Long Haul</title>
    <title lang="ar">دايري أوف أي ويمبي كيد: ذا لونغ هول</title>
    <desc lang="en">Comedy. A Heffley family road trip to attend grandma's 90th birthday party goes hilariously off course thanks to young Greg's newest scheme to get to a video gaming convention. كوميدي. سرعان ما تنحرف خطط آل هافلي لزيارة الجدة في عيد ميلادها التسعين عن مسارها بفضل حيلة غريغ الصغير الذي يرغب بحضور مؤتمر لألعاب الفيديو.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014115500 +0000" stop="20201014135000 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Raising Helen</title>
    <title lang="ar">رايزينغ هيلين</title>
    <desc lang="en">STAR Movies offers an exciting and unique mix of the best films from around the world. تقدم قناة ستار موفيز مجموعة رائعة وفريدة من أفضل الأفلام من جميع أنحاء العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014135000 +0000" stop="20201014152000 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Adult Life Skills</title>
    <title lang="ar">Star Movies HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">STAR Movies offers an exciting and unique mix of the best films from around the world. تقدم قناة ستار موفيز مجموعة رائعة وفريدة من أفضل الأفلام من جميع أنحاء العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014152000 +0000" stop="20201014170000 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Born To Dance</title>
    <title lang="ar">Star Movies HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">STAR Movies offers an exciting and unique mix of the best films from around the world. تقدم قناة ستار موفيز مجموعة رائعة وفريدة من أفضل الأفلام من جميع أنحاء العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014170000 +0000" stop="20201014182300 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">Kings</title>
    <title lang="ar">Star Movies HD</title>
    <desc lang="en">STAR Movies offers an exciting and unique mix of the best films from around the world. تقدم قناة ستار موفيز مجموعة رائعة وفريدة من أفضل الأفلام من جميع أنحاء العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20201014182300 +0000" stop="20201014195000 +0000" channel="Star Movies HD">
    <title lang="en">When In Rome</title>
    <title lang="ar">وين إن روم</title>
    <desc lang="en">STAR Movies offers an exciting and unique mix of the best films from around the world. تقدم قناة ستار موفيز مجموعة رائعة وفريدة من أفضل الأفلام من جميع أنحاء العالم.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>